Please,O
revert,O
over,O
this,O
concern!,O
Thank,O
"you,",O
Anand,B-per
Kumar.,I-per
#Delhi,B-art
A,I-art
#Doctor,I-art
who,O
was,O
on,O
COVID,B-org
duty,O
&works,O
as,O
CMO,B-org
in,O
a,O
Malviya,B-org
Nagar,I-org
hospital,O
alleged,O
he,O
is,O
being,O
#harassed,O
treated,O
as,O
'Corona,B-geo
carrier',O
in,O
his,O
Dwarka,B-org
society.,I-org
House,I-org
helps,O
not,O
being,O
allowed,O
despite,O
he,O
requested.,O
Police,O
have,O
received,O
complaint,O
but,O
no,O
FIR.https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.thehindu.com/news/cities/Delhi/doctor-harassed-by-his-dwarka-housing-society/article31513314.ece/amp/,O
…,O
"Sir,",O
you,O
have,O
let,O
loose,O
a,O
devil,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
by,O
allowing,O
liquor,O
vends,O
to,O
open.,O
I,O
am,O
sure,O
you,O
have,O
seen,O
videos,O
of,O
serpentine,O
queues,O
in,O
Malviya,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
outside,O
liquor,O
shops.,O
People,O
were,O
out,O
as,O
if,O
a,O
panacea,O
had,O
been,O
found,O
to,O
Covid-19.,B-org
Please,I-org
stop,O
this.,O
Save,O
us,O
please!,O
Some,O
photograph,O
click,O
during,O
lockdown,O
covid,O
-19,O
#stayhomestaysafe,O
.,O
@,O
Malviya,B-org
Nagar,I-org
South,I-org
Delhi,I-org
https://www.instagram.com/p/B_xuwaaF27q/?igshid=liv3wqtahjna,O
…,O
Delhi,B-per
govt,O
puts,O
stickers,O
outside,O
houses,O
in,O
Malviya,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
after,O
conducting,O
thermal,O
screening.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@CMODelhi,O
@DCPSouthDelhi,O
#COVID,O
pic.twitter.com/HW1ZpcJsqp,O
Delhi,B-org
Tally,I-org
Rises,I-org
to,O
"1,707",O
with,O
67,O
New,B-org
Covid-19,I-org
Cases;,I-org
Malviya,I-org
"Nagar,",I-org
Jahangirpuri,I-org
Among,I-org
New,I-org
https://is.gd/bxXiiP,O
#livenewsindia,O
@dominos,O
I,O
was,O
denied,O
delivery,O
in,O
Malviya,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
stating,O
my,O
area,O
has,O
COVID-19,O
cases..Look,O
who,O
is,O
safe,O
now?,O
God,O
saved,O
"me,",O
yor,O
Malviya,B-per
Nagar,I-per
team,O
was,O
actually,O
delivering,O
the,O
virus....,O
good,O
dat,O
I,O
didn’t,O
go,O
downstairs,O
to,O
receive,O
it,O
or,O
I,O
would’ve,O
been,O
the,O
73rd,O
positive,O
case,O
A,O
19-year-old,O
pizza,O
delivery,O
agent,O
in,O
South,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
has,O
COVID-19,O
and,O
has,O
been,O
admitted,O
to,O
RML,O
hospital.,O
This,O
has,O
resulted,O
in,O
72,B-tim
families,O
he,O
delivered,O
food,O
to,O
be,O
quarantined,O
in,O
areas,O
like,O
Hauz,B-per
"Khas,",I-per
Malviya,I-per
Nagar,I-per
and,O
Savitri,B-per
Nagar.,I-per
https://science.thewire.in/health/coronavirus-daily-updates-covid-19/,O
…,O
The,O
pizza,O
delivery,O
boy,O
is,O
a,O
resident,O
of,O
Savitri,B-per
Nagar,I-per
area,O
in,O
Malviya,B-geo
"Nagar,",I-geo
south,O
Delhi.,O
He,O
was,O
showing,O
symptoms,O
of,O
coronavirus,O
for,O
around,O
20,B-tim
days,O
when,O
he,O
was,O
finally,O
tested,O
recently.,O
His,O
Covid-19,O
test,O
results,O
came,O
out,O
on,O
April,B-tim
"14,",O
showing,O
him,O
positive,O
for,O
coronavirus.,O
@PMOIndia,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
Under,O
recent,O
case,O
of,O
#Covid_19,B-geo
spread,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
by,O
a,O
food,O
delivery,O
guy,O
which,O
affected,O
72,O
families,O
in,O
Malviya,B-geo
"nagar,",O
I,O
got,O
to,O
know,O
@Zomato,B-per
@ZomatoIN,O
hasnt,O
been,O
providing,O
basic,O
masks,O
or,O
sanitisers,O
or,O
gloves,O
to,O
its,O
delivery,O
guys.,O
They,O
should,O
be,O
taken,O
care,O
of,O
72,O
families,O
home-quarantined,O
in,O
Malviya,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
in,O
South,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
after,O
pizza,O
delivery,O
boy,O
tests,O
COVID-19,O
positive.,O
But,O
@drharshvardhan,O
will,O
still,O
have,O
you,O
believe,O
there's,O
no,O
community,O
transmission.https://mumbaimirror.indiatimes.com/coronavirus/news/72-families-home-quarantined-in-south-delhi-after-pizza-delivery-boy-tests-covid-19-positive/articleshow/75175446.cms,O
…,O
A,O
pizza,O
delivery,O
boy,O
tested,O
positive,O
for,O
covid,O
19,O
and,O
he,O
delivered,O
till,O
12th,B-tim
April,I-tim
near,O
south,O
Delhi,B-per
Malviya,I-per
"Nagar,",I-per
Hauz,I-per
khas,O
and,O
72,O
families,O
kept,O
quarantined,O
bcz,O
of,O
boy,O
.,O
Is,O
it,O
that,O
hard,O
to,O
live,O
without,O
pizza?,O
I,O
mean,O
shame,O
on,O
those,O
ppl,O
who,O
r,O
not,O
taking,O
this,O
pandemic,O
seriously,O
The,O
pizza,O
delivery,O
boy,O
a,O
resident,O
of,O
Malviya,B-geo
"Nagar,south",O
Delhi.tested,O
Covid,O
19,O
positive,O
on,O
April,B-tim
14,O
Authorities,O
",identified",O
72,O
families,O
of,O
Malviya,B-geo
"Nagar,Hauz",I-geo
khas.,O
where,O
he,O
visited,O
in,O
past,B-tim
20,I-tim
days.These,O
families,O
have,O
been,O
put,O
under,O
home,O
quarantine.,O
The,O
boy,O
never,O
visited,O
Markaz,B-per
pic.twitter.com/kzMFzBBA8E,O
#TBNNEWS,B-org
#DELHI,I-org
Delhi,I-org
pizza,O
delivery,O
boy,O
tests,O
positive,O
for,O
"Covid-19,",B-tim
72,I-tim
"families,",O
17,O
other,O
delivery,O
boys,O
quarantined.,O
A,O
pizza,O
delivery,O
boy,O
in,O
Delhi’s,O
Malviya,B-per
Nagar,I-per
area,O
has,O
tested,O
positive,O
for,O
coronavirus,O
after…,O
https://www.instagram.com/p/B_ClIlRF3Gu/?igshid=11w8n0dlwngbc,O
…,O
Video,O
Journalist,O
-53,O
working,O
with,O
DD,B-org
"News,",I-org
who,O
died,O
on,O
May,B-tim
"27,",O
tested,O
#NAME?,O
for,O
COVID-19,B-org
posthumously.,O
DD,B-org
News,I-org
shifts,O
operations,O
from,O
Mandi,B-org
House,I-org
to,O
Khelgaon,B-geo
studio.,O
#TheNewsInsight,O
#Delhi,B-per
#DelhiFightsCorona,I-per
@AamAadmiParty,O
Hello,B-per
sir,I-per
Sunny,I-per
Sharma,I-per
from,O
Mandi,B-geo
"house,",O
new,O
"delhi,",O
sir,O
I,O
and,O
my,O
father,O
had,O
done,O
covid,O
test,O
in,O
RML,B-org
hospital,O
on,O
dtd,O
13,O
"May,",B-geo
till,O
we,O
are,O
not,O
received,O
our,O
"reports,",O
now,O
we,O
both,O
are,O
fine.,O
Judiciary,O
is,O
dead.,O
Last,O
seen,O
at,O
Supreme,B-org
Court,I-org
of,I-org
"India,",I-org
Tilak,I-org
"Marg,",I-org
Mandi,I-org
"House,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
Kuch,I-org
bhi,I-org
ho,O
sakta,O
hai,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
mein,O
#Covid_19india,O
Bengali,B-org
Market,I-org
(Mandi,I-org
House),I-org
SEALED,I-org
.,O
Police,B-org
Staff,I-org
and,I-org
Delhi,I-org
Civil,I-org
Defense,I-org
Supplying,I-org
essentials,O
door,O
to,O
door.,O
Daily,O
Temperature,O
check,O
up,O
of,O
staff,O
by,O
Thermal,O
gun.,O
PPE,O
jackets,O
being,O
used,O
by,O
Pocket,B-org
staff,O
#coronavirus,O
#lockdown,O
#COVID__19,O
@mtnldelhi,O
hello,O
internet,O
20822101,O
Mayur,O
vihar,O
phase-3,O
down,O
since,O
6:30pm,O
"Friday,",O
please,O
repair,O
it,O
back,O
to,O
action,O
as,O
soon,O
as,O
possible,O
as,O
this,O
is,O
covid,O
period,O
needing,O
all,O
in,O
the,O
"family,",O
thanks,O
n,O
regards,O
praveen,O
Kumar,B-org
Garg,I-org
20822101,I-org
Vasundhara,I-org
Enclave,I-org
Delhi-110096,I-org
M-9910997490,I-org
@MTNLDEL,O
hello,O
internet,O
20822101,O
Mayur,O
vihar,O
phase-3,O
down,O
since,O
6:30pm,O
"Friday,",O
please,O
repair,O
it,O
back,O
to,O
action,O
as,O
soon,O
as,O
possible,O
as,O
this,O
is,O
covid,O
period,O
needing,O
all,O
in,O
the,O
"family,",O
thanks,O
n,O
regards,O
praveen,O
Kumar,B-org
Garg,I-org
20822101,I-org
Vasundhara,I-org
Enclave,I-org
Delhi-110096,I-org
M-9910997490,I-org
@CMD_MTNL,O
hello,O
internet,O
20822101,O
Mayur,O
vihar,O
phase-3,O
down,O
since,O
6:30pm,O
"Friday,",O
please,O
repair,O
it,O
back,O
to,O
action,O
as,O
soon,O
as,O
possible,O
as,O
this,O
is,O
covid,O
period,O
needing,O
all,O
in,O
the,O
"family,",O
thanks,O
n,O
regards,O
praveen,O
Kumar,B-org
Garg,I-org
20822101,I-org
Vasundhara,I-org
Enclave,I-org
Delhi-110096,I-org
M-9910997490,I-org
@MTNLOfficial,O
hello,O
internet,O
20822101,O
Mayur,O
vihar,O
phase-3,O
down,O
since,O
6:30pm,O
"Friday,",O
please,O
repair,O
it,O
back,O
to,O
action,O
as,O
soon,O
as,O
possible,O
as,O
this,O
is,O
covid,O
period,O
needing,O
all,O
in,O
the,O
"family,",O
thanks,O
n,O
regards,O
praveen,O
Kumar,B-org
Garg,I-org
20822101,I-org
Vasundhara,I-org
Enclave,I-org
Delhi-110096,I-org
M-9910997490,I-org
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@LtGovDelhi,O
@msisodia,O
@AamAadmiParty,O
@PMOIndia,O
Residents,O
of,O
SFS,B-org
"Flats,",I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
"PH-3,",I-org
Delhi,I-org
-,I-org
110096,B-tim
fed,O
up,O
with,O
MCD,B-org
support,O
&,B-org
GOVT,I-org
Support,O
No,O
sanitation,O
No,O
Fumigation.,B-per
Covid,I-per
cases,O
are,O
on,O
rise.,O
Cases,O
are,O
increasing,O
in,O
Parwana,B-org
"Apt,Mayur",I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase-1,I-org
delhi.,O
We,O
request,O
DM,O
to,O
initiate,O
investigation,O
and,O
do,O
contact,O
"mapping,",O
sanitization,O
here,O
also,O
to,O
avoid,O
further,O
spread.,O
Investigation,O
ordered,O
as,O
COVID-19,B-org
cases,O
rise,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
-,O
The,O
New,B-org
Indian,I-org
Express,I-org
https://www.newindianexpress.com/cities/delhi/2020/jun/06/investigation-ordered-as-covid-19-cases-rise-in-delhi-2152999.html,O
…,O
There,O
are,O
two,O
COVID-19,O
suspects,O
in,O
Mayur,B-geo
vihar,O
phase,O
3,O
east,O
delhi,O
kindly,O
help,O
@COVIDNewsByMIB,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@DelhiPolice,O
@SatyendarJain,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@PMOIndia,O
@help_delhi,O
@dmeastdelhi,O
kindly,O
send,O
your,O
sanitisation,O
team,O
in,O
pocket-1,O
Mayur,B-org
Vihar,I-org
phase-1,O
in,O
82-89,O
series.,O
Almost,B-tim
10,I-tim
COVID-19,I-tim
patients,O
are,O
in,O
this,O
area,O
so,O
kindly,O
sanitise,O
the,O
area,O
as,O
early,O
as,O
possible.,O
@msisodia,O
@GautamGambhir,O
In,O
Deputy,O
CM,O
own,O
constituency,O
Patparganj,B-tim
2,I-tim
Covid,I-tim
positive,O
cases,O
in,O
B,B-org
Block,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
II,I-org
So,O
far,O
no,O
responce,O
from,O
Delhi,B-org
Govt.,I-org
No,O
sanitisation,O
or,O
measures.,O
@_AjitTyagi,O
@TajinderBagga,O
@SanjayAzadSln,O
@rishibagree,O
sharam,O
karo,O
sharam,O
karo,O
sharam,O
karo.,O
@DDMADelhi1,O
Sir/Madam,B-per
After,O
one,O
resident,O
was,O
found,O
COVID+,O
directions,O
like,O
social,O
distancing,O
restriction,O
on,O
gathering,O
issued.,O
Some,O
persons,O
are,O
deliberately,O
violating,O
protocols.,O
Please,O
look,O
into,O
it,O
&,O
pass,O
requisite,O
directions,O
to,O
authorities.,O
Admn.,B-org
Parwana,I-org
CGHS,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
E,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
@dmeastdelhi,O
"Sir/Madam,",O
one,O
person,O
has,O
been,O
tested,O
positive,O
for,O
COVID-19,B-org
in,O
"A-66,",B-org
Parwana,I-org
Group,I-org
Housing,I-org
"Society,",I-org
Mayur,I-org
"Vihar,",I-org
East,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
The,O
person,O
is,O
admitted,O
to,O
Max,B-per
Hospital.,I-per
It,O
is,O
requested,O
to,O
instruct,O
designated,O
officials,O
to,O
sensitize,O
the,O
block,O
area,O
etc.,O
"Administrator,",B-per
PGHS,I-per
मोदी,O
जी,O
दिल्ली,O
की,O
स्तिथ,O
बेहद,O
दयनीय,O
हे।मेरे,O
ससुराल,O
में,O
मेरे,O
साले,O
अनिल,O
कुमार,O
का,O
टेस्ट,O
पोजिटिव,O
पाया,O
है।,O
"B6,gali",O
no.7,O
",shashi",O
garden,O
mayur,O
vihar,O
ph-1.,O
New,B-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
पूरे,O
परिवार,O
का,O
टेस्ट,O
अभी,O
तक,O
नहीं,O
हुआ।,O
बुखार,O
105,O
था,O
आज।,O
Shared,O
Communications,O
on,O
COVID-19.,O
More,O
details,O
at,O
/,O
@BBPSMV,O
@HRDMinistry,O
@msisodia,O
@DrRPNishank,O
@HMOIndia,O
@AmitShahOffice,O
@PMOIndia,O
@MODIfyingBHARAT,O
@ModiOnceMore,O
@narendramodi,O
@rekhaaryaoffice,O
@RekhaAryaBJP,O
@dkashyap24aonla,O
3D,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
STRUCTURE,I-org
Made,I-org
By:,I-org
Deepansh,I-org
Sethi,I-org
Bal,I-org
Bhavan,I-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
2,I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
110091,O
pic.twitter.com/xxq2GThL4F,O
@BBPSMV,O
@HRDMinistry,O
@msisodia,O
@DrRPNishank,O
@HMOIndia,O
@AmitShahOffice,O
@PMOIndia,O
@MODIfyingBHARAT,O
@ModiOnceMore,O
@narendramodi,O
@rekhaaryaoffice,O
@RekhaAryaBJP,O
@dkashyap24aonla,O
3D,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
STRUCTURE,I-org
Made,I-org
By:,I-org
Deepansh,I-org
Sethi,I-org
Bal,I-org
Bhavan,I-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
2,I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
110091,O
pic.twitter.com/qM62pngfvR,O
@BBPSMV,O
@HRDMinistry,O
@msisodia,O
@DrRPNishank,O
@HMOIndia,O
@AmitShahOffice,O
@PMOIndia,O
@MODIfyingBHARAT,O
@ModiOnceMore,O
@narendramodi,O
@rekhaaryaoffice,O
@RekhaAryaBJP,O
@dkashyap24aonla,O
3D,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
STRUCTURE,I-org
Made,I-org
By:,I-org
Deepansh,I-org
Sethi,I-org
Bal,I-org
Bhavan,I-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
2,I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
110091,O
pic.twitter.com/J1BDPDmLf7,O
@BBPSMV,O
@HRDMinistry,O
@msisodia,O
@DrRPNishank,O
@HMOIndia,O
@AmitShahOffice,O
@PMOIndia,O
@MODIfyingBHARAT,O
@ModiOnceMore,O
@narendramodi,O
@rekhaaryaoffice,O
@RekhaAryaBJP,O
@dkashyap24aonla,O
3D,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
STRUCTURE,I-org
Made,I-org
By:,I-org
Deepansh,I-org
Sethi,I-org
Bal,I-org
Bhavan,I-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
2,I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
110091,O
pic.twitter.com/y5S4xlSs6K,O
@BBPSMV,O
@HRDMinistry,O
@msisodia,O
@DrRPNishank,O
@HMOIndia,O
@AmitShahOffice,O
3D,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
STRUCTURE,I-org
Made,I-org
By:-,I-org
Deepansh,I-org
Sethi,I-org
Bal,I-org
Bhavan,I-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
2,I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
110091,O
pic.twitter.com/mXQXsHYxq6,O
@rekhaaryaoffice,O
@RekhaAryaBJP,O
@dkashyap24aonla,O
@PMOIndia,O
@narendramodi,O
@ModiOnceMore,O
@ModiforNewIndia,O
@MODIfyingBHARAT,O
@COVIDNewsByMIB,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
@santoshgangwar,O
3D,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
STRUCTURE,I-org
Made,I-org
By:-,I-org
Deepansh,I-org
Sethi,I-org
Bal,I-org
Bhavan,I-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
2,I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
110091,O
pic.twitter.com/tcFyYrhr91,O
@rekhaaryaoffice,O
@RekhaAryaBJP,O
@dkashyap24aonla,O
@PMOIndia,O
@narendramodi,O
@ModiOnceMore,O
@ModiforNewIndia,O
@MODIfyingBHARAT,O
@COVIDNewsByMIB,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
@santoshgangwar,O
3D,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
STRUCTURE,I-org
Made,I-org
By:-,I-org
Deepansh,I-org
Sethi,I-org
Bal,I-org
Bhavan,I-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
2,I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
110091,O
pic.twitter.com/IN0e3hKwON,O
@rekhaaryaoffice,O
@RekhaAryaBJP,O
@dkashyap24aonla,O
@PMOIndia,O
@narendramodi,O
@ModiOnceMore,O
@ModiforNewIndia,O
@MODIfyingBHARAT,O
@COVIDNewsByMIB,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
@santoshgangwar,O
3D,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
STRUCTURE,I-org
Made,I-org
By:-,I-org
Deepansh,I-org
Sethi,I-org
Bal,I-org
Bhavan,I-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
Mayur,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Phase,I-org
2,I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
110091,O
pic.twitter.com/ub6SbQU34M,O
@Manekagandhibjp,O
"mam,",O
there,O
two,O
innocent,O
strays,O
and,O
their,O
mom,O
outside,O
Medha,B-geo
apartments,O
(Mayur,B-geo
Vihar,I-geo
"Extension,",I-geo
East,I-geo
Delhi),I-geo
that,O
are,O
being,O
treated,O
bad,O
due,O
to,O
unjustified,O
fear,O
of,O
COVID-19.,B-org
Your,I-org
organization,O
could,O
help,O
them.,O
Two,O
of,O
their,O
siblings,O
have,O
already,O
died.,O
Dear,B-org
@airtelindia,I-org
@Airtel_Presence,I-org
",",O
kindly,O
assist,O
as,O
how,O
to,O
get,O
a,O
new,O
broadband,O
connection,O
in,O
Delhi.,B-geo
Pincode,I-geo
110091,B-tim
(mayur,O
"vihar,",O
pocket,O
"a,",O
phase,O
2).,O
Need,O
it,O
on,O
urgent,O
basis.,O
I,O
Understand,O
the,O
covid,O
"issue,",O
but,O
kindly,O
assist,O
if,O
something,O
can,O
be,O
worked,O
out.,O
@DC_Gurugram,O
@MunCorpGurugram,O
@cmohry,O
critical,O
situation,O
at,O
Vyapar,B-geo
Sadan,I-geo
Area,I-geo
between,O
MG,B-org
Road,I-org
and,I-org
Delhi,I-org
Road,I-org
",",O
slums,O
having,O
Refugee,O
......,O
Plz,O
take,O
appropriate,O
actions,O
#,O
Fight,O
Against,O
Covid,O
19,O
How,O
to,O
take,O
care,O
of,O
your,O
health,O
during,O
COVID-19,O
pandemic,O
Phone,B-art
No:,I-art
"01135213270,",I-art
1127674395,I-art
Address:,I-art
4C,I-art
Institutional,I-art
"Area,",I-art
North,I-art
Ex,I-art
Model,I-art
"Town,",I-art
"Delhi,",I-art
110009,B-tim
.,O
#mdcityhealthcare,O
#doctors,O
#hospital,O
#mdcityhospital,O
#covid,O
#superspecialty,O
#patientsatisfaction,O
#patientcarepic.twitter.com/y4XhyCn4Wm,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
@SatyendarJain,O
why,O
no,O
large,O
scale,O
COVID,O
quarantine,O
centres,O
being,O
developed..Model,O
Town,O
has,O
more,O
than,O
20,O
cases,O
but,O
it,O
is,O
not,O
a,O
containment,O
zone,O
yet..have,O
you,O
guys,O
decided,O
not,O
to,O
work,O
and,O
leave,O
Delhi,B-geo
to,O
God,O
I,O
think,O
covid-19,O
cases,O
n,O
deaths,O
are,O
more,O
punjabi,O
bagh,O
and,O
model,O
town,O
area,O
delhi,O
.,O
Plz,O
write,O
more,O
infected,O
areas,O
in,O
reply,O
.,O
Treatment,O
in,O
our,O
hospital,O
with,O
special,O
COVID-19,O
wards,O
We,O
have,O
100,O
Beds,O
for,O
COVID,B-org
Patients.,I-org
.,O
For,O
more:,O
Visit:,B-org
http://www.mdcityhealthcare.com,I-org
Call,I-org
us:011-27674395,I-org
Address:,I-org
4C,I-org
Institutional,I-org
"Area,",I-org
North,I-org
Ex,I-org
Model,I-org
"Town,",I-org
"110009,Delhi,India.",I-org
#healthcare,O
#health,O
#medical,O
#covid,O
#medicinepic.twitter.com/z40dqDmauY,O
One,O
of,O
my,O
client,O
resides,O
in,O
Model,B-per
Town....,I-per
His,O
entire,O
family,O
has,O
developed,O
COVID-19,O
"symptoms,",O
but,O
haven't,O
got,O
tested,O
due,O
to,O
stigma,O
attached.,O
They,O
have,O
just,O
resorted,O
to,O
Self,O
quarantine,O
for,O
past,B-tim
week,O
or,O
so.,O
If,O
there,O
is,O
any,O
casualty,O
will,O
it,O
be,O
a,O
fault,O
of,O
Delhi,B-geo
Government?,I-geo
It's,O
been,O
a,O
week,O
since,O
my,O
father,O
tested,O
covid+,O
and,O
had,O
to,O
be,O
admitted,O
to,O
a,O
hospital,O
in,O
Model,B-org
"Town,",I-org
Delhi.,I-org
Still,O
no,O
test,O
for,O
"me,",O
my,O
sister,O
or,O
my,O
mom,O
despite,O
numerous,O
calls,O
to,O
the,O
Delhi,B-geo
govt.,O
Request,O
the,O
govt,O
to,O
test,O
us,O
as,O
soon,O
as,O
possible.,O
@PreetyAgarwaal,O
@BDUTT,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@arunbothra,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@msisodia,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@drharshvardhan,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@drharshvardhan,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@msisodia,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@arunbothra,O
My,O
mother,O
is,O
covid,O
"+ve,",O
needs,O
dialysis.She’s,O
critical.,O
hospital,O
not,O
looking,O
after,O
her.,O
Admitted,O
in,O
M,B-org
D,I-org
city,O
hospital,O
model,O
town,O
delhi.,O
Also,O
tried,O
dialysis,O
in,O
lnjp,O
hospital,O
and,O
many,O
private,O
hospitals,O
plz,O
help,O
.,O
contact,O
no.,O
8376050492,O
name,O
farha,O
@DcpNorthDelhi,O
@CPDelhi,O
Sir,O
My,O
son,O
Annant,O
Bhagi,O
resident,O
of,O
D-3/3,B-org
Model,I-org
Town,I-org
Delhi,I-org
has,O
his,O
18th,B-tim
Bday,I-tim
on,O
9th,B-tim
May.,B-org
Due,I-org
to,O
covid,O
he,O
is,O
very,O
depressed,O
and,O
if,O
DP,O
can,O
wish,O
him,O
on,O
his,O
special,O
"day,",O
it,O
would,O
be,O
the,O
best,O
gift,O
for,O
him.,O
He,O
is,O
very,O
fond,O
of,O
joining,O
Police,O
force.,O
Sandeep,B-geo
Bhagi,I-geo
@CPDelhi,O
Sir,O
My,O
son,O
Annant,O
Bhagi,O
resident,O
of,O
D-3/3,B-org
Model,I-org
Town,I-org
Delhi,I-org
has,O
his,O
18th,B-tim
Bday,I-tim
on,O
9th,B-tim
May.,B-org
Due,I-org
to,O
covid,O
he,O
is,O
very,O
depressed,O
and,O
if,O
DP,O
can,O
wish,O
him,O
on,O
his,O
special,O
"day,",O
it,O
would,O
be,O
the,O
best,O
gift,O
for,O
him.,O
He,O
is,O
very,O
fond,O
of,O
joining,O
Police,O
force.,O
Sandeep,B-art
Bhagi,I-art
9999992772,I-art
@akhilesht84,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
My,O
landlord,O
wants,O
me,O
to,O
shift,O
to,O
another,O
place.,O
Is,O
it,O
safe,O
to,O
do,O
so,O
during,O
this,O
time?,O
please,O
provide,O
any,O
solution,O
or,O
contact,O
no.,O
to,O
resolve,O
this,O
issue,O
as,O
soon,O
as,O
possible.,O
I,O
live,O
in,O
Model,B-geo
Town,O
3,O
Delhi.#Covid_19india,O
@HMOIndia,O
@PMOIndia,O
@DelhiPolice,O
My,O
landlord,O
wants,O
me,O
to,O
shift,O
to,O
another,O
place.,O
Is,O
it,O
safe,O
to,O
do,O
so,O
during,O
this,O
time?,O
please,O
provide,O
any,O
solution,O
or,O
contact,O
no.,O
to,O
resolve,O
this,O
issue,O
as,O
soon,O
as,O
possible.,O
I,O
live,O
in,O
Model,B-geo
Town,O
3,O
Delhi.#Covid_19india,O
@PMOIndia,O
Respected,O
Sir,O
Not,O
getting,O
salary,O
of,O
MARCH,B-org
2020,B-tim
during,I-tim
Covid,I-tim
19,I-tim
crisis.,O
Working,O
@,O
UNITED,B-org
BIOTECH,I-org
(,O
P,B-org
),O
LTD,O
FC/B-1(,O
EXTN,O
"),",O
Mohan,B-per
Co,I-per
-,O
operative,O
industrial,O
"estate,",O
Mathura,B-geo
"road,",O
New,B-geo
Delhi-110044.,I-geo
facing,O
a,O
lots,O
of,O
problem,O
in,O
this,O
situation,O
kindly,O
look,O
into,O
the,O
matter.,O
Mam,O
my,O
area,O
is,O
dangerous,O
zone,O
to,O
covid,O
19,O
please,O
help,O
us,O
my,O
address,O
is,O
L-2C,B-org
17,O
MOHAN,O
GARDEN,O
UTTAM,B-org
Nagar,I-org
new,I-org
Delhi,I-org
59,O
Hi,O
I’m,O
Anuj,B-per
Saraswat,I-per
live,O
in,O
A,O
11,O
sidhatri,O
enclave,O
mohan,O
garden,O
uttam,O
nagar,O
new,O
delhi,O
110059,O
My,O
brother,O
is,O
suffering,O
form,O
Covid-19,O
his,O
report,O
was,O
positive,O
on,O
14,O
may,O
2020,B-tim
after,O
that,O
we,O
shift,O
my,O
brother,O
on,O
second,O
floor,O
in,O
home,O
isolation,O
and,O
after,O
the,O
positive,O
report,O
we,O
call,O
lot’s,O
Lockdown,O
should,O
be,O
implemented,O
with,O
full,O
force,O
this,O
time.,O
People,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
are,O
not,O
taking,O
it,O
seriously,O
that's,O
causing,O
increased,O
Covid,O
19,O
cases.,O
In,O
my,O
area,O
Mohan,B-org
"Garden,",I-org
Uttam,I-org
"Nagar,",I-org
N.D,I-org
people,O
are,O
moving,O
as,O
there,O
is,O
no,O
lockdown.,O
Shops,O
are,O
open,O
hawkers,O
of,O
all,O
types,O
are,O
moving.,O
#AskZee,O
Agar,O
pass,O
me,O
koi,O
Covid,O
19,O
ke,O
Sankarman,O
ke,O
dayre,O
me,O
hai,O
to,O
kya,O
krna,O
chahiye.,O
Agar,O
call,O
karte,O
bhi,O
hai,O
to,O
baad,O
me,O
ladi,O
karne,O
lagege.,O
Rahul,O
kumar,O
new,O
delhi,B-per
Mohan,I-per
garden,O
Uttam,B-per
Nagar,I-per
@LtGovDelhi,O
@DelhiVsCorona,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
maharashtra,O
govt,O
reduced,O
the,O
rate,O
of,O
covid,O
test,O
just,O
half.,O
Why,O
not,O
it,O
be,O
reduced,O
in,O
Delhi?,B-geo
pic.twitter.com/Dn1a2fkcyf,O
#Delhi,B-per
#URGENT,I-per
Need,I-per
A+,I-per
#blood,O
plasma,O
donor,O
of,O
covid,O
recovered,O
person,O
@,O
Moolchand,B-geo
"Hospital,",I-geo
near,O
Lajpat,B-org
Nagar.,B-per
Call,I-per
"9873242322,",O
7011138842,O
#BloodAid,O
via,O
@chowkidarAnup,O
cc,O
@TajinderBagga,O
@upma23,O
@crowngaurav,O
@ArvindGaur,O
#BloodMatters,O
.@aajtak,O
have,O
contacted,O
below,O
5,O
hospitals,O
&,O
interestingly,O
all,O
5,O
of,O
them,O
are,O
PRIVATE,O
hospital,O
Max,B-org
Batra,I-org
ISIC,I-org
Balaji,I-org
Action,I-org
Medical,I-org
Institute,I-org
Moolchand,I-org
Why,I-org
pvt,O
hospitals,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
are,O
denying,O
Covid,B-per
Patients?,I-per
Is,I-per
there,O
any,O
political,O
pressure,O
frm,O
opposition,O
to,O
create,O
CHAOS,B-org
in,O
Delhi?,B-geo
https://twitter.com/aajtak/status/1269301622426882048,O
…,O
Some,O
416,O
people,O
recovered,O
today,B-tim
in,O
delhi.,O
Sir,O
ganga,O
"ram,",O
moolchand,O
etc,O
converted,O
to,O
covid,O
hospital.,O
can,O
you,O
name,O
that,O
one,O
"person,",O
why,O
as,O
a,O
responsible,O
"person,",O
you,O
have,O
not,O
suggested,O
him,O
earlier,O
to,O
go,O
for,O
private,O
covid,O
19,O
test.,O
I,O
get,O
tested,O
in,O
24hrs.,O
4500,O
or,O
life?,O
Whats,O
important,O
Delhi,B-org
Corona,I-org
Update:,I-org
Ganga,I-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
to,O
be,O
made,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hospitals,O
|,O
Delhi,B-org
News,I-org
-,I-org
Times,I-org
of,I-org
India,I-org
https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/delhi/delhi-ganga-ram-moolchand-to-be-made-covid-19-hospitals/articleshow/76186544.cms,O
…,O
Delhi,B-org
Corona,I-org
Update:,I-org
Ganga,I-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
to,O
be,O
made,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hospitals,O
|,O
Delhi,B-org
News,I-org
-,I-org
Times,I-org
of,I-org
India,I-org
https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/delhi/delhi-ganga-ram-moolchand-to-be-made-covid-19-hospitals/articleshow/76186544.cms,O
…,O
More,O
hospitals,O
in,O
delhi,B-geo
to,O
convert,O
into,O
covid,O
hospital.These,O
are,O
Moolchand,B-org
Hospital-140,I-org
"beds,",I-org
Saroj,I-org
Super,I-org
Specialty,I-org
Hospital-154,I-org
beds,O
and,O
Sir,B-per
Ganga,I-per
Ram,I-per
"Hospital,508",I-per
beds.This,O
will,O
surely,O
hampers,O
the,O
rglr,O
or,O
other,O
needy,O
patients,O
flow.#delhifightcorona,O
#indiafightcorona#COVIDー19pic.twitter.com/gkeZeMvdyc,O
Delhi:,B-org
Ganga,I-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
to,O
be,O
made,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hospitals,O
http://www.weblivenews.com/delhi-ganga-ram-moolchand-to-be-made-covid-19-hospitals/,O
…,O
Ganga,B-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
and,I-org
Saroj,I-org
Hospitals,I-org
has,O
been,O
converted,O
into,O
complete,O
Covid,B-org
Hospitals,I-org
in,O
Delhi.,O
Total,O
800,O
Coronavirus,B-per
Private,I-per
Beds,I-per
(25%,O
Free,B-org
for,I-org
Economically,I-org
Weaker,I-org
Section),I-org
are,O
added,O
today.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@dilipkpandey,O
@ipathak25,O
@SanjayAzadSln,O
#coronavirus,O
#Covid_19,O
Delhi,B-org
Corona,I-org
Update:,I-org
Ganga,I-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
to,O
be,O
made,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hospitals,O
|,O
Delhi,B-org
News,I-org
-,I-org
Times,I-org
of,I-org
India,I-org
https://m.timesofindia.com/city/delhi/delhi-ganga-ram-moolchand-to-be-made-covid-19-hospitals/amp_articleshow/76186544.cms#referrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com&amp_tf=From%20%251%24s,O
…,O
Delhi,B-org
Corona,I-org
Update:,I-org
Ganga,I-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
to,O
be,O
made,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hospitals,O
|,O
Delhi,B-org
News,I-org
-,I-org
Times,I-org
of,I-org
India,I-org
https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/delhi/delhi-ganga-ram-moolchand-to-be-made-covid-19-hospitals/articleshow/76186544.cms,O
…,O
Delhi:,B-org
Ganga,I-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
to,O
be,O
made,O
Covid-19,B-per
hospitals.,I-per
Govt,I-per
says,O
they,O
they,O
are,O
built,O
on,O
land,O
given,O
on,O
concessational,O
rates,O
and,O
hence,O
the,O
decision,O
http://toi.in/aaYLab/a24gj,O
via,O
@timesofindia,O
@EconomicTimes,O
Delhi's,O
"Moolchand,",B-per
"Gangaram,",I-per
Saroj,I-per
hospitals,O
declared,O
Covid,O
hospitals,O
http://tinyurl.com/yc2uzvle,O
It,O
is,O
good,O
step,O
by,O
govt,O
of,O
"Delhi,",B-geo
but,O
other,O
serious,O
cases,O
must,O
not,O
be,O
"sufferer,",O
"apart,",O
rates,O
of,O
treatment,O
for,O
Sars,O
cov,O
2,O
must,O
be,O
fixed,O
by,O
govt,O
and,O
"advertised,",O
patients,O
must,O
not,O
be,O
"harassed,Delhi",O
Corona,B-org
Update:,I-org
Ganga,I-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
to,O
be,O
made,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hospitals,O
|,O
Delhi,B-org
News,I-org
-,I-org
Time,I-org
Delhi:,B-org
Ganga,I-org
"Ram,",I-org
Moolchand,I-org
to,O
be,O
made,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hospitals,O
https://health.economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/hospitals/delhi-ganga-ram-moolchand-to-be-made-covid-19-hospitals/76186740,O
…,O
-,O
shared,O
via,O
@ETHealthWorld,O
App:,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@SatyendarJain,O
Appreciate,B-org
Delhi,I-org
govt.,O
effort,O
for,O
making,O
"Moolchand,",B-per
Saroj,I-per
n,O
80%,O
SGRH,O
COVID,O
"hospitals,",O
since,O
the,O
land,O
is,O
given,O
on,O
concessional,O
rates,O
is,O
the,O
treatment,O
for,O
residents,O
of,O
Delhi,B-geo
free,O
or,O
DGEHS,B-org
rates,O
or,O
hospital,O
own,O
tariff.,O
Delhi's,O
"Moolchand,",B-per
"Gangaram,",I-per
Saroj,I-per
hospitals,O
declared,O
Covid,B-org
hospitals,I-org
#Delhi,I-org
#Moolchand,I-org
#Gangaram,I-org
#Sarojhospitals,I-org
#Covidhospitals,I-org
http://www.thehawk.in/cities/new-delhi/delhis-moolchand-gangaram-saroj-hospitals-declared-covid-hospitals-151001?utm_campaign=pubshare&utm_source=Twitter&utm_medium=957575197&utm_content=auto-link&utm_id=346,O
…,O
Delhi's,O
"Moolchand,",B-per
"Gangaram,",I-per
Saroj,I-per
hospitals,O
declared,O
Covid,O
hospitals,O
-,O
https://www.yuvnews.com/29685/delhi-s-moolchand-gangaram-saroj-hospitals-declared-covid-hospitals,O
…pic.twitter.com/J38xg0qCBu,O
Delhi's,O
"Moolchand,",B-per
"Gangaram,",I-per
Saroj,I-per
hospitals,O
declared,O
Covid,O
hospitals,O
https://www.nirogstreet.com/blog/coronavirus-updates/delhis-moolchand--gangaram--saroj-hospitals-declared-covid-hospitals,O
…,O
@NehaBansal31,O
We,O
non,O
covid,O
20,O
people,O
in,O
small,O
200,O
yards,O
containment,O
building,O
have,O
been,O
forced,O
to,O
live,O
with,O
4,O
corona,O
+,O
ve,O
people.,O
Save,O
us.,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
here.,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi.,O
8860590110,O
https://m.facebook.com/story.php?story_fbid=2559681337465901&id=100002721798546,O
…,O
@DrKumarVishwas,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Release,O
us,O
from,O
this,O
home,O
detention.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
in,O
this,O
small,O
building,O
with,O
no,O
food,O
and,O
vegetables,O
support,O
and,O
garbage,O
pile,O
lying,O
at,O
our,O
place,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi,O
8860590110,O
@RajatSharmaLive,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Release,O
us,O
from,O
this,O
home,O
detention.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
in,O
this,O
small,O
building,O
with,O
no,O
food,O
and,O
vegetables,O
support,O
and,O
garbage,O
pile,O
lying,O
at,O
our,O
place,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi,O
8860590110,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Release,O
us,O
from,O
this,O
home,O
detention.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
in,O
this,O
small,O
building,O
with,O
no,O
food,O
and,O
vegetables,O
support,O
and,O
garbage,O
pile,O
lying,O
at,O
our,O
place,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi,O
8860590110,O
@HMOIndia,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Release,O
us,O
from,O
this,O
home,O
detention.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
in,O
this,O
small,O
building,O
with,O
no,O
food,O
and,O
vegetables,O
support,O
and,O
garbage,O
pile,O
lying,O
at,O
our,O
place,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi,O
8860590110,O
@MVenkaiahNaidu,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Release,O
us,O
from,O
this,O
home,O
detention.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
in,O
this,O
small,O
building,O
with,O
no,O
food,O
and,O
vegetables,O
support,O
and,O
garbage,O
pile,O
lying,O
at,O
our,O
place,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi,O
8860590110,O
@SatyendarJain,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Release,O
us,O
from,O
this,O
home,O
detention.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
in,O
this,O
small,O
building,O
with,O
no,O
food,O
and,O
vegetables,O
support,O
and,O
garbage,O
pile,O
lying,O
at,O
our,O
place,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi,O
8860590110,O
@PMOIndia,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Release,O
us,O
from,O
this,O
home,O
detention.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
in,O
this,O
small,O
building,O
with,O
no,O
food,O
and,O
vegetables,O
support,O
and,O
garbage,O
pile,O
lying,O
at,O
our,O
place,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi,O
8860590110,O
@republic,O
@ArvindKejriwa,O
Release,O
us,O
from,O
this,O
home,O
detention.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
We,O
all,O
will,O
become,O
sick,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
sealed,O
in,O
this,O
small,O
building,O
with,O
no,O
food,O
and,O
vegetables,O
support,O
and,O
garbage,O
pile,O
lying,O
at,O
our,O
place,O
"B-59,",B-org
moti,O
nagar.,O
New,O
delhi,O
8860590110,O
Dont,O
book,O
jlr,O
i,O
have,O
booked,O
discovery,O
sport,O
with,O
5,O
lac,O
amp,O
motors,O
moti,O
nagar,O
delhi,O
in,O
the,O
name,O
of,O
m/s,O
lido,O
before,O
lockdown.,O
Due,O
to,O
covid-19,O
outbreak,O
we,O
have,O
lost,O
money,O
and,O
we,O
ask,O
for,O
refund,O
then,O
they,O
said,O
no,O
amount,O
will,O
be,O
Refund,O
.,O
so,O
do,O
not,O
buy,O
jlr,O
they,O
cheated,O
me,O
.,O
Dont,O
book,O
jlr,O
.,O
i,O
have,O
booked,O
discovery,O
sport,O
with,O
5,O
lac,O
amp,O
motors,O
moti,O
nagar,O
delhi,O
in,O
the,O
name,O
of,O
m/s,O
lido,O
before,O
lockdown.,O
Due,O
to,O
covid-19,O
outbreak,O
we,O
have,O
lost,O
money,O
and,O
we,O
ask,O
for,O
refund,O
then,O
they,O
said,O
no,O
amount,O
will,O
be,O
Refund,O
.,O
so,O
do,O
not,O
buy,O
jlr,O
they,O
cheated,O
me,O
.,O
@JLR_News,O
i,O
have,O
booked,O
discovery,O
sport,O
with,O
5,O
lac,O
amp,O
motors,O
moti,O
nagar,O
delhi,O
in,O
the,O
name,O
of,O
m/s,O
lido,O
before,O
lockdown.,O
Due,O
to,O
covid-19,O
outbreak,O
we,O
have,O
lost,O
money,O
and,O
we,O
ask,O
for,O
refund,O
then,O
they,O
said,O
no,O
amount,O
will,O
be,O
Refund,O
.,O
so,O
do,O
not,O
buy,O
jlr,O
they,O
cheated,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
please,O
sir,O
humble,O
request,O
..west,O
delhi,B-per
Moti,I-per
nagar.,O
",and",O
Sudershan,B-per
park,O
have,O
lots,O
of,O
covid,O
cases,O
which,O
are,O
increasing,O
day,O
by,O
day.,O
Please,O
do,O
something,O
and,O
declare,O
the,O
contnoment,O
area,O
...,O
please,O
sir,O
its,O
request,O
no,O
one,O
is,O
listening,O
u,O
please,O
do,O
something,O
AC,B-org
Moti,I-org
nagar,O
today:-,O
since,O
you,O
are,O
not,O
pre-registered,O
with,O
"us,",O
there,O
will,O
be,O
additional,O
rs.15000,O
emergency,O
charge.,O
Upon,O
asking,O
why-,O
management,O
policy,O
is,O
the,O
answer.,O
Its,O
time,O
of,O
national,O
healthcare,O
emergency,O
or,O
money,O
making?,O
20%,O
beds,O
are,O
mandated,O
for,O
covid,O
patients,O
across,O
Delhi.,B-geo
For,O
ur,O
kind,O
information,O
mcd,O
k,O
hospitals,O
ko,O
covid,O
hospitals,O
me,O
change,O
krne,O
ka,O
right,O
Delhi,B-per
Gov,I-per
ne,O
le,O
rkha,O
h,O
Here's,O
my,O
summary,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
handling,O
in,O
India.,B-org
1)Controlling:,I-org
Karnataka,I-org
2)Testing:,I-org
Tamilnadu,I-org
3)Helping,I-org
Migrants:,I-org
UP,I-org
4)Opposing,I-org
PM:,I-org
Bengal,I-org
5)PR:,I-org
Maharashtra,I-org
6)Screwing,I-org
things,O
up:,O
Delhi,B-geo
57,O
migrants,O
stranded,O
in,O
Delhi's,O
"Mundka,",O
borrowed,O
and,O
paid,O
over,O
Rs,B-geo
2,O
lakh,O
to,O
a,O
truck,O
driver,O
and,O
reached,O
native,O
places.,O
Shocked,O
when,O
they,O
"said,",O
if,O
@RailMinIndia,O
had,O
"allowed,",O
they,O
were,O
ready,O
to,O
book,O
whole,O
train,O
by,O
paying,O
Rs,O
"3,500",O
each.,O
#MigrantWorkers,O
#Covid_19,O
Amid,O
rise,O
in,O
coronavirus,O
COVID-19,O
"cases,",O
30,O
Tablighi,B-per
Jamaat,I-per
members,O
test,O
positive,O
in,O
quarantine,O
centre,O
of,O
Delhi`s,O
Mundka,B-geo
pic.twitter.com/DhNPLSaQaj,O
Amid,O
rise,O
in,O
coronavirus,O
COVID-19,O
"cases,",O
30,O
Tablighi,B-per
Jamaat,I-per
members,O
test,O
positive,O
in,O
quarantine,O
centre,O
of,O
Delhi's,O
Mundka,B-geo
https://zeenews.india.com/india/amid-rise-in-coronavirus-covid-19-cases-30-tablighi-jamaat-members-test-positive-in-quarantine-centre-of-delhis-mundka-2275713.html,O
…,O
Amid,O
rise,O
in,O
coronavirus,O
COVID-19,O
"cases,",O
30,O
Tablighi,B-per
Jamaat,I-per
members,O
test,O
positive,O
in,O
quarantine,O
centre,O
of,O
Delhi`s,O
Mundka,B-geo
https://india.timesofnews.com/political/political/amid-rise-in-coronavirus-covid-19-cases-30-tablighi-jamaat-members-test-positive-in-quarantine-centre-of-delhis-mundka.html,O
…,O
Amid,O
rise,O
in,O
coronavirus,O
COVID-19,O
"cases,",O
30,O
Tablighi,B-per
Jamaat,I-per
members,O
test,O
positive,O
in,O
quarantine,O
centre,O
of,O
Delhi`s,O
Mundka,B-geo
https://postofasia.com/amid-rise-in-coronavirus-covid-19-circumstances-30-tablighi-jamaat-members-check-constructive-in-quarantine-centre-of-delhis-mundka/,O
…pic.twitter.com/l9o2h6cyw2,O
Amid,O
rise,O
in,O
coronavirus,O
COVID-19,O
"cases,",O
30,O
Tablighi,B-per
Jamaat,I-per
members,O
test,O
positive,O
in,O
quarantine,O
centre,O
of,O
Delhi’s,O
Mundka,B-geo
|,O
India,B-org
News,I-org
https://newsattend.com/amid-rise-in-coronavirus-covid-19-cases-30-tablighi-jamaat-members-test-positive-in-quarantine-centre-of-delhis-mundka-india-news/,O
…,O
Amid,O
rise,O
in,O
coronavirus,O
COVID-19,O
"cases,",O
30,O
Tablighi,B-per
Jamaat,I-per
members,O
test,O
positive,O
in,O
quarantine,O
centre,O
of,O
Delhi's,O
Mundka,B-geo
https://zeenews.india.com/india/amid-rise-in-coronavirus-covid-19-cases-30-tablighi-jamaat-members-test-positive-in-quarantine-centre-of-delhis-mundka-2275713.html,O
…,O
"Hi,",O
in,O
purview,O
of,O
"COVID-19,",O
we,O
are,O
currently,O
operating,O
at,O
reduced,O
strength.,O
This,O
has,O
been,O
done,O
to,O
ensure,O
the,O
safety,O
of,O
our,O
staff.,O
We,O
encourage,O
you,O
to,O
use,O
#AirtelThanks,O
app,O
for,O
service,O
requests.,O
"Hi,",O
I,O
have,O
DM'ed,O
all,O
details.,O
Please,O
have,O
a,O
look,O
&,O
revert.,O
@AirAsia,O
@AirAsiaIndian,O
#airasia,O
#Covid_19india,O
#lockdown,O
#Corona,B-geo
@HardeepSPuri,O
@PMOIndia,O
@HMOIndia,O
@DGCAIndia,O
@AAI_Official,O
Grocery,O
shop,O
owners,O
hve,O
doubled/tripled,O
d,O
prices,O
wch,O
isn't,O
fair,O
in,O
sch,O
crisis,O
times.,O
Ppl,O
hve,O
sme,O
humanity,O
&,O
show,O
sme,O
"sense,",O
don't,O
try,O
2,O
earn,O
ur,O
bread,O
our,O
of,O
sch,O
situations.,O
@narendramodi,O
@PMOIndia,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
#IndiaFightsCorona,O
#JanataCurfew,O
#NarendraModi,O
#COVID,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Ayush,O
ministry,O
held,O
justbone,B-geo
Siddha,I-geo
camp,O
in,O
Munirka,B-geo
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
when,O
they,O
should,O
be,O
holding,O
100s,O
of,O
them,O
across,O
Delhi,B-geo
.,O
They,O
forgotten,O
that,O
"""Yogena",B-geo
chittasya,O
padena,O
vacham,O
malam,O
sharirasya,O
cha,O
"vaidyakena""",O
COVID,B-org
is,O
not,O
chitrasya,O
malam,O
to,O
be,O
deal,O
with,O
by,O
Yoga.,O
It,O
is,O
sharirasya,O
malam,O
#Delhi,B-per
gets,O
support,O
from,O
Siddha,B-geo
Medicine,I-geo
in,O
its,O
fight,O
against,O
Covid,B-per
19,O
The,O
Siddha,B-org
Clinical,I-org
Research,I-org
Unit,I-org
"(SCRU),",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
has,O
intensified,O
it's,O
activities,O
under,O
the,O
prophylatic,O
population,O
"study,",O
Today,B-tim
a,O
medical,O
camp,O
was,O
organised,O
by,O
SCRU,B-org
with,O
the,O
support,O
of,O
Munirka,B-geo
Welfare,I-geo
pic.twitter.com/7MIuEd35DR,O
Please,O
help,O
them,O
with,O
rations..,O
from,O
Manipur.,B-per
Not,I-per
giving,O
details,O
here,O
for,O
now.,O
They’re,O
staying,O
in,O
Munirka,B-org
"Vill,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
@NBirenSingh,O
@ManojTiwariMP,O
@BJP4Delhi,O
@AnilSharma4BJP,O
@TokasBhagat,O
#SOSCorona,O
#Lockdown5,O
#IndiaFightsCorona,O
#FeedTheNeedy,O
#Covid_19pic.twitter.com/Tab1g0OEdn,O
Please,O
help,O
them,O
with,O
rations..,O
from,O
Manipur.,B-per
Not,I-per
giving,O
details,O
here,O
for,O
now.,O
They’re,O
staying,O
in,O
Munirka,B-org
"Vill,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
@NBirenSingh,O
@ManojTiwariMP,O
@BJP4Delhi,O
@AnilSharma4BJP,O
@TokasBhagat,O
#SOSCorona,O
#Lockdown5,O
#IndiaFightsCorona,O
#FeedTheNeedy,O
#Covid_19pic.twitter.com/zndmoQfPlz,O
Please,O
help,O
them,O
with,O
rations..,O
from,O
Manipur.,B-per
Babulal,I-per
Chowk,I-per
munirka,O
"village,",O
New,B-org
Delhi-110067.,I-org
Cont,I-org
8586891645,O
@NBirenSingh,O
@ManojTiwariMP,O
@BJP4Delhi,O
@TajinderBagga,O
#Lockdown5,O
#IndiaFightsCorona,O
#FeedTheNeedy,O
#COVID,O
pic.twitter.com/31nvtJ7ROP,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@PMOIndia,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@DMSouthDelhi,O
@DMSouthWest1,O
a,O
covid,O
patient,O
in,O
Dda,B-geo
"flats,",O
"Munirka,",B-org
Delhi,I-org
died,O
yesterday,B-tim
and,I-tim
2,I-tim
covid,O
patients,O
are,O
in,O
home,O
"quarantine,",O
but,O
this,O
society,O
is,O
not,O
declared,O
as,O
a,O
containment,O
zone,O
and,O
no,O
restrictions,O
are,O
applied.,O
Why?,O
#delhi_hiding_covid_cases,O
Delhi,B-geo
govt,O
hiding,O
covid,O
cases,O
as,O
much,O
they,O
can,O
since,O
beginning.,O
Lot,O
of,O
such,O
incidents,O
happened,O
near,O
Munirka,B-geo
and,O
R,B-org
K,I-org
Puram.,I-org
#DelhiFightsCovid,O
#DelhiPolice,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@DCPSouthDelhi,O
https://youtu.be/gh3GS387fCc,O
#BoscoDelhi,O
distributed,O
"Masks,",B-org
"Soaps,",I-org
ORS,I-org
&,I-org
Vit,I-org
supplements,O
to,O
ppl,O
in,O
#slumareas,O
and,O
#shelterhome,O
of,O
"Munirka,",B-org
New,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
An,O
awareness,O
session,O
also,O
held,O
by,O
Medical,O
team,O
professionals,O
on,O
the,O
do's,O
and,O
don'ts,O
of,O
Covid-19.,O
There,O
were,O
around,O
70,O
ppl,O
benefited.,O
https://youtu.be/gh3GS387fCc,O
#BoscoDelhi,O
distributed,O
"Masks,",B-org
"Soaps,",I-org
ORS,I-org
&,I-org
Vit,I-org
supplements,O
to,O
ppl,O
in,O
#slumareas,O
and,O
#shelterhome,O
of,O
"Munirka,",B-org
New,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
An,O
awareness,O
session,O
also,O
held,O
by,O
Medical,O
team,O
professionals,O
on,O
the,O
do's,O
and,O
don'ts,O
of,O
Covid-19.,O
There,O
were,O
around,O
70,O
ppl,O
benefited.,O
#BoscoDelhi,O
distributed,O
"Masks,",B-per
"Soaps,",I-per
ORS,I-per
and,O
Vit,O
supplements,O
to,O
the,O
ppl,O
living,O
in,O
the,O
#slumarea,O
and,O
#shelterhome,O
at,O
Munirka,B-geo
"area,",O
New,O
Delhi.,O
An,O
awareness,O
session,O
also,O
held,O
by,O
the,O
Medical,O
team,O
professionals,O
on,O
the,O
do's,O
and,O
don'ts,O
of,O
Covid-19.,O
There,O
were,O
around,O
70,O
ppl,O
benefited.,O
pic.twitter.com/V9xsQk2x4T,O
#BoscoDelhi,O
distributed,O
"Masks,",B-per
"Soaps,",I-per
ORS,I-per
and,O
Vit,O
supplements,O
to,O
the,O
ppl,O
living,O
in,O
the,O
#slumarea,O
and,O
#shelterhome,O
at,O
Munirka,B-geo
"area,",O
New,O
Delhi.,O
An,O
awareness,O
session,O
also,O
held,O
by,O
the,O
Medical,O
team,O
professionals,O
on,O
the,O
do's,O
and,O
don'ts,O
of,O
Covid-19.,O
There,O
were,O
around,O
70,O
ppl,O
benefited.,O
pic.twitter.com/w45B5NooNe,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
Even,O
if,O
you,O
extend,O
the,O
"lockdown,",O
please,O
approve,O
to,O
open,O
closed,O
private,O
clinics,O
and,O
hospitals,O
for,O
non,O
COVID,O
cases.,O
I,O
am,O
living,O
in,O
Munirka,B-geo
"Village,",I-geo
South,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
and,O
I,O
suffered,O
a,O
lot,O
last,O
week,O
without,O
any,O
clinic,O
being,O
open.,O
Mohalla,B-geo
Clinic,I-geo
is,O
too,O
crowded,O
Feed,O
the,O
Daily,B-org
Wager,I-org
@FeedingIndia,I-org
[Delhi,I-org
Update],I-org
Kits,I-org
served:,O
"83,700",O
~,O
8.8,O
million,O
meals,O
Areas:,B-org
"Pitampura,",I-org
"Mangolpuri,",I-org
Madapur,I-org
"Khadar,",I-org
Karol,I-org
"Bagh,",I-org
"Seemapuri,",I-org
Malviya,I-org
"Nagar,",I-org
Nehru,I-org
"Nagar,",I-org
"Okhla,",I-org
Munirka,I-org
#dillwalonkidilli,O
#FeedtheDailyWager,O
#FeedingIndia,O
#COVID,O
#ZeroHunger,O
#SDG2pic.twitter.com/WP3czXaveT,O
Here,O
are,O
few,O
glimpses,O
of,O
yesterday’s,O
‘Covid,B-per
Helpline’,I-per
provided,O
in,O
Delhi.,B-org
My,I-org
Home,I-org
India,I-org
have,O
developed,O
small,O
kit,O
of,O
Ration,B-org
for,I-org
North,I-org
Eastern,I-org
Brothers,I-org
&,I-org
Sisters.,I-org
"Yesterday,",I-org
it,O
was,O
distributed,O
in,O
areas,O
of,O
Munirka,B-org
&,I-org
Maharani,I-org
Bagh,I-org
to,O
those,O
in,O
need,O
&,O
were,O
inaccessible.,O
@PIBImphalpic.twitter.com/f22WXEzbLi,O
Well,O
done.In,O
"Munirka,chirag",O
delhi,O
of,O
south,O
delhi,O
ppl,O
from,O
all,O
the,O
north-east,O
are,O
struggling,O
with,O
this,O
crisis.Come,O
on,O
one,O
step,O
for,O
them.,O
@AnilSharma4BJP,O
@rameshbidhuri,O
#RSSinAction,O
#RSSfightsCorona,O
#IndiaFightsCorona,O
#Covid_19https://twitter.com/friendsofrss/status/1246330010274869249,O
…,O
Distributed,O
food,O
packet,O
containing,O
"rice,dal,potato,oil,onion,",O
salt,O
and,O
sugar,O
to,O
north,O
east,O
student,O
and,O
other,O
"needy,",O
facing,O
problem,O
due,O
to,O
COVID,O
19,O
lockdown,O
with,O
Sewa,B-geo
Bharti,I-geo
at,O
Munirka,B-geo
in,O
New,B-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
@NBirenSingh,O
@KirenRijiju,O
@Neiphiu_Rio,B-geo
@DrJitendraSingh,O
@BJP4India,O
@BJP4Manipurpic.twitter.com/TCAHiE15Ih,O
@DMSouthWest1,O
It,O
has,O
been,O
15,O
days+,O
Street,O
locked,O
(A,B-org
267,I-org
Gopal,I-org
Nagar,I-org
A,I-org
Block,I-org
Near,I-org
Shyam,I-org
Mandir,I-org
Najafgarh),I-org
for,O
qurantine,O
COVID+ve,O
family.,O
Kindly,O
confirm,O
by,O
when,O
will,O
remove,O
seal.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
@ManchNajafgarh,O
@HMOIndia,O
@PMOIndia,O
@CMO_Delhi,O
pic.twitter.com/I1UwakMlGB,O
Will,O
power,O
is,O
mightier,O
than,O
COVID-19:,B-org
Tune,I-org
in,O
to,O
hear,O
Shri,B-org
Rohit,I-org
Rajbir,I-org
"Singh,",I-org
Addl.,I-org
"DCP,",I-org
"Najafgarh,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
narrate,O
his,O
personal,O
experience,O
of,O
getting,O
infected,O
and,O
coming,O
back,O
stronger,O
to,O
serve,O
the,O
nation,O
-,O
https://www.mygov.in/podcast/mygov-positive-stories-episode-103/,O
…,O
Will,O
power,O
is,O
mightier,O
than,O
COVID-19:,B-org
Tune,I-org
in,O
to,O
hear,O
Shri,B-org
Rohit,I-org
Rajbir,I-org
"Singh,",I-org
Addl.,I-org
"DCP,",I-org
"Najafgarh,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
narrate,O
his,O
personal,O
experience,O
of,O
getting,O
infected,O
and,O
coming,O
back,O
stronger,O
to,O
serve,O
the,O
nation,O
-,O
https://www.mygov.in/podcast/mygov-positive-stories-episode-103/,O
…,O
Delhi,B-geo
stopped,O
testing.,O
My,O
uncle,O
in,O
JJ,B-org
Colony,I-org
inderpuri,O
tested,O
covid,O
positive,O
and,O
admitted,O
in,O
a,O
najafgarh,O
centre.,O
Family,O
was,O
sent,O
back.,O
More,O
than,O
a,O
"week,",O
no,O
testing,O
of,O
family,O
members.,O
A,O
bada,O
scam,O
chal,O
rahe,O
hi,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
me....!,O
Health,O
Minister,O
@drharshvardhan,O
visited,O
a,O
dedicated,O
#COVID19,B-org
Health,I-org
Centre,I-org
at,O
Chaudhary,B-org
Brahm,I-org
Prakash,I-org
Ayurved,I-org
Charak,I-org
Sansthan,I-org
in,O
#Delhi's,O
"Najafgarh,",O
the,O
first,O
Ayurveda,B-geo
hospital,O
of,O
India,B-geo
to,O
provide,O
Covid,O
"care,where",O
he,O
interacted,O
with,O
doctors,O
&,O
sought,O
feedback,O
from,O
#COVID,B-org
patients.,O
pic.twitter.com/PO9NT2MjXN,O
Dr.,B-per
Harsh,I-per
"Vardhan,",I-per
the,O
Union,O
Minister,O
for,O
Health,B-org
&,I-org
Family,I-org
Welfare,I-org
today,B-tim
visited,O
the,O
Dedicated,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
Health,I-org
Centre,I-org
at,O
Chaudhary,B-org
Brahm,I-org
Prakash,I-org
Ayurved,I-org
Charak,I-org
Sansthan,I-org
"Najafgarh,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/xfn7ECg8Ii,O
#IndiaFightsCorona:,O
Health,O
Minister,O
@drharshvardhan,O
today,B-tim
visited,O
at,O
Chaudhary,B-org
Brahma,I-org
Prakash,I-org
Ayurved,I-org
Charak,I-org
"Sansthan,",I-org
in,O
"Najafgarh,",B-org
New,I-org
"Delhi,",I-org
which,O
is,O
functioning,O
as,O
a,O
COVID,B-org
Care,I-org
Centre,I-org
"(CCC),",I-org
to,O
oversee,O
the,O
preparedness,O
to,O
manage,O
#COVID19,O
cases.,O
#StayHome,O
#StaySafepic.twitter.com/JqG8dyrcIm,O
District,O
administration,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
thanks,O
the,O
people,O
of,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
for,O
appreciating,O
the,O
work,O
of,O
SDM,B-org
Najafgarh,I-org
@saumyasharma711,O
in,O
the,O
time,O
of,O
#Covid_19.,B-org
Our,I-org
team,O
at,O
district,O
#southwest,O
is,O
ever,O
ready,O
to,O
serve,O
the,O
people.,O
#IASpic.twitter.com/cLdxfNbmmD,O
They,O
are,O
"humans,",O
"too,",O
@narendramodi,O
sir!,O
.,O
#RedLightAreas,O
#India,B-org
#COVID_19,I-org
#Kamathipura,I-org
#Mumbai,I-org
#Kalighat,I-org
#Najafgarh,I-org
#Delhi,I-org
#Forbesganj,I-org
#Bihar,I-org
#Sonagachhi,I-org
#Kolkata,I-org
#Lockdown,I-org
#Poverty,I-org
#CSWpic.twitter.com/Qz77C2scca,O
@narendramodi,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@RahulGandhi,O
@AmitShah,O
@myogiadityanath,O
Hi,O
sir,O
myself,O
lado,O
from,O
Najafgarh,B-org
New,I-org
Delhi-43.I,I-org
am,O
stuck,O
in,O
Wardha,B-geo
Maharashtra,I-geo
due,O
to,O
covid-19,O
lockdown.I'm,O
in,O
a,O
lot,O
of,O
trouble.I,O
am,O
from,O
poor,O
family,O
so,O
please,O
help,O
me,O
a,O
little,O
and,O
help,O
me,O
get,O
to,O
my,O
house.,O
In,O
continuation,O
to,O
civic,O
action,O
program,O
to,O
help,O
people,O
against,O
menace,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
-19,O
",today",O
food,O
to,O
775,O
beneficiaries,O
(lunch,O
to,O
455,O
and,O
dinner,O
to,O
320,O
),O
were,O
distributed,O
in,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
area,O
of,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
GC,B-org
NEW,I-org
DELHI,I-org
CRPF.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/apkkex9p6f,O
In,O
continuation,O
to,O
civic,O
action,O
program,O
to,O
help,O
people,O
against,O
menace,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
-19,O
",today",O
food,O
to,O
790,O
beneficiaries,O
(lunch,O
to,O
440,O
and,O
dinner,O
to,O
350,O
),O
were,O
distributed,O
in,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
area,O
of,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
GC,B-org
NEW,I-org
DELHI,I-org
CRPF.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/WVE9pASBrp,O
In,O
continuation,O
to,O
civic,O
action,O
program,O
to,O
help,O
people,O
against,O
menace,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
-19,O
",today",O
food,O
to,O
780,O
beneficiaries,O
(lunch,O
to,O
450,O
and,O
dinner,O
to,O
330,O
),O
were,O
distributed,O
in,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
area,O
of,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
GC,B-org
NEW,I-org
DELHI,I-org
CRPF.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/xjIqyfMYGo,O
In,O
continuation,O
to,O
civic,O
action,O
program,O
to,O
help,O
people,O
against,O
menace,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
-19,O
",today",O
food,O
to,O
760,O
beneficiaries,O
(lunch,O
to,O
420,O
and,O
dinner,O
to,O
340,O
),O
were,O
distributed,O
in,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
area,O
of,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
GC,B-org
NEW,I-org
DELHI,I-org
CRPF.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/Vsv9YSGTuo,O
In,O
continuation,O
to,O
civic,O
action,O
program,O
to,O
help,O
people,O
against,O
menace,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
-19,O
",today",O
food,O
to,O
840,O
beneficiaries,O
(lunch,O
to,O
475,O
and,O
dinner,O
to,O
365,O
),O
were,O
distributed,O
in,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
area,O
of,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
GC,B-org
NEW,I-org
DELHI,I-org
CRPF.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/leD7JgIR8r,O
In,O
continuation,O
to,O
civic,O
action,O
program,O
to,O
help,O
people,O
against,O
menace,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
-19,O
",today",O
food,O
to,O
775,O
beneficiaries,O
(lunch,O
to,O
425,O
and,O
dinner,O
to,O
350,O
),O
were,O
distributed,O
in,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
area,O
of,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
GC,B-org
NEW,I-org
DELHI,I-org
CRPF.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/q0GSHMaiFp,O
In,O
continuation,O
to,O
civic,O
action,O
program,O
to,O
help,O
people,O
against,O
menace,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
-19,O
",today",O
food,O
to,O
835,O
beneficiaries,O
(lunch,O
to,O
465,O
and,O
dinner,O
to,O
370,O
),O
were,O
distributed,O
in,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
area,O
of,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
GC,B-org
NEW,I-org
DELHI,I-org
CRPF.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/2XKH2PAv2a,O
In,O
continuation,O
to,O
civic,O
action,O
program,O
to,O
help,O
people,O
against,O
menace,O
of,O
COVID,B-org
-19,O
",today",O
food,O
to,O
820,O
beneficiaries,O
(lunch,O
to,O
450,O
and,O
dinner,O
to,O
370,O
),O
were,O
distributed,O
in,O
Najafgarh,B-geo
area,O
of,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
GC,B-org
NEW,I-org
DELHI,I-org
CRPF.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/kOmShud1hw,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
request,O
for,O
urgently,O
Mr,O
Arvind,O
KejriwalJi,O
We,O
are,O
staying,O
in,O
Niranjan,B-org
"Park,",I-org
Nangli,I-org
"Dairy,",I-org
Najafgarh,I-org
"Road,",I-org
NEW,I-org
Delhi-110043.,I-org
Requesting,I-org
you,O
to,O
kindly,O
make,O
arrangements,O
for,O
Sanitizeration,O
to,O
safe,O
fro,O
Covid-19,B-per
Virus.,I-per
We,I-per
will,O
very,O
grateful,O
to,O
you,O
for,O
this,O
action,O
–,O
at,O
Nangli,B-org
Dairy,I-org
Bus,I-org
Stand,I-org
@GulabMatiala,O
Garbage,O
car,O
does,O
not,O
come,O
here,O
in,O
our,O
street,O
-,O
3,O
"only,",O
We,O
can't,O
go,O
out,O
because,O
of,O
covid-19.,O
Nangli,B-per
vihar,I-per
extension,O
part,O
"1,",O
Najafgarh,O
new,O
delhi,O
110043,O
Plz,O
resolve,O
this,O
problem,O
This,O
is,O
what,O
I,O
am,O
sharing,O
about,O
the,O
situation,O
at,O
one,O
of,O
my,O
friend's,O
relative,O
in,O
Nangloi,B-geo
-,O
Delhi.,O
They,O
are,O
a,O
joint,O
family,O
of,O
five,O
and,O
one,O
of,O
then,O
tested,O
COVID,O
+,O
and,O
it's,O
been,O
now,O
3,B-tim
days,O
no,O
action,O
as,O
for,O
as,O
house,O
"sanitation,",O
no,O
sample,O
collection,O
of,O
other,O
members,O
of,O
the,O
house.,O
Hello,O
"sir,",O
@AamAadmiParty,O
@SatyendarJain,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
One,O
of,O
friend,O
lives,O
in,O
A-86,B-org
chander,O
Vihar,B-per
nilothi,I-per
extn.,O
nangloi,O
Delhi-41,O
facing,O
covid,O
sympt.,O
from,O
past,B-tim
2,I-tim
days.his,O
father,O
and,O
mother,O
also,O
having,O
the,O
same,O
symtoms,O
.please,O
do,O
the,O
needful,O
and,O
contact,O
him,O
asap,O
Mohit,O
8860796632,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Sir,O
aap,O
bata,O
sakte,O
ho?Ke,O
ab,O
kin,O
logo,O
ka,O
COVID,B-org
TEST,I-org
ho,O
raha,O
h.or,O
pahle,O
kitna,O
logo,O
ke,O
test,O
ho,O
chuke,O
h?,O
Delhi,B-geo
sarkar,O
ne,O
COVID,B-org
POSITIVE,I-org
family,O
ko,O
ghar,O
me,O
eise,O
hi,O
chhod,O
"diya,na",O
hi,O
uske,O
Ghar,B-geo
ko,O
seal,O
kiya,O
or,O
na,O
aas-pass,O
ke,O
logo,O
ka,O
test,O
hua.Area,O
L,B-org
block,O
Nangloi,O
phase-3,O
Sir...Koi,O
bata,O
sakta,O
h?,O
Ke,O
ab,O
kin,O
logo,O
ka,O
COVID,B-org
TEST,I-org
ho,O
raha,O
h...or,O
pahle,O
kitna,O
logo,O
ke,O
test,O
huye,O
h,O
koi,O
bata,O
sakta,O
h?,O
Delhi,B-geo
sarkar,O
ne,O
COVID,B-org
POSITIVE,I-org
family,O
ko,O
ghar,O
me,O
eise,O
hi,O
chhod,O
"diya,",O
na,O
hi,O
uske,O
Ghar,B-geo
ko,O
seal,O
kiya,O
or,O
na,O
aas-pass,O
ke,O
logo,O
ka,O
test,O
hua.Area,O
L,B-org
block,O
Nangloi,O
phase-3,O
We,O
are,O
running,O
two,O
Covid,O
centres,O
in,O
Delhi.,B-geo
Nangloi,I-geo
and,O
SDA,B-org
I,O
doubt,O
there,O
is,O
a,O
potential,O
covid,O
19,O
infected,O
patient,O
who,O
runs,O
a,O
grocery,O
store,O
in,O
my,O
neighborhood,O
in,O
Nangloi,B-org
Delhi.,I-org
Can,I-org
he,O
be,O
tested,O
for,O
this,O
pandemic.,O
Really,B-org
Scared.,I-org
Please,I-org
Suggest,I-org
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
@COVIDNewsByMIB,O
@DharampalLakra,O
"Sir,",O
in,O
my,O
family,O
5,O
members,O
are,O
tested,O
covid,O
"positive,in",O
which,O
my,O
parents,O
are,O
admitted,O
in,O
army,O
hospital,O
Delhi,B-geo
"cantt,",O
kindly,O
sanitize,O
my,O
house,O
and,O
vehicles,O
as,O
soon,O
as,O
"possible,",O
in,O
nangloi,O
"extn,",O
m.,O
No.,O
9289358511/9667781999,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
sir,O
namaste,O
me,O
"nangloi,",O
west,O
delhi-110041,O
se,O
bol,O
rha,O
hu,O
meri,O
gali,O
me,O
shahshi,O
rehte,O
h,O
jinko,O
vajah,O
se,O
yha,O
lockdown,O
ka,O
ulanghan,O
ho,O
rha,O
h.,O
Yha,B-per
daily,O
600-700,O
person,O
ate,O
h,O
Jisse,O
covid-19,O
k,O
phelne,O
ka,O
daar,O
bna,O
rhehta,O
Pls,O
aap,O
jald,O
se,O
jald,O
action,O
le,O
Thank,O
you,O
Krishna,B-geo
youth,O
club,O
of,O
Nehru,B-org
Yuva,I-org
Kendra,I-org
#Nangloi,I-org
",",I-org
#Delhi,I-org
relating,O
to,O
awareness,O
and,O
other,O
activities,O
on,O
COVID-19.They,O
have,O
distributed,O
food,O
and,O
other,O
essential,O
items.,O
@KirenRijiju,O
|,O
@RijijuOffice,O
|,O
@YASMinistry,O
|,O
@PMOIndiapic.twitter.com/rDkq6Epabe,O
Sir,B-org
Delhi,I-org
west,O
Nangloi,B-geo
me,O
jo,O
gehu,O
aur,O
chabal,O
bitran,O
ho,O
raha,O
hai,O
usme,O
lockdown,O
ka,O
palan,O
nahi,O
ho,O
raha,O
hai,O
mohalla,O
wise,O
karna,O
chahiye,O
anytha,O
covid.19,O
ka,O
chain,O
torane,O
ka,O
prayas,O
Delhi,B-geo
sarkar,O
ka,O
bifal,O
ho,O
jaega,O
@RaghuvinderMLA,O
In,O
Gali,B-org
No.,I-org
-,I-org
5,I-org
Block,I-org
Rzr,I-org
Nihal,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Nangloi,I-org
Everyone,I-org
ignores,O
the,O
COVID-19,B-org
and,O
and,O
doesn't,O
maintain,O
social,O
distancing,O
and,O
doesn't,O
wear,O
any,O
kind,O
of,O
masks,O
please,O
take,O
action,O
for,O
this,O
Name,B-org
-,I-org
Shiva,I-org
Mob,I-org
No.,I-org
-,I-org
7836003684,I-org
Address,I-org
-,I-org
Gali,I-org
No.,I-org
5,I-org
Block,I-org
Rzr,I-org
Nihal,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Delhi,I-org
@DCPWestDelhi,O
In,O
Nangloi,B-org
Nihal,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Block,I-org
Rzr,I-org
Gali,I-org
No.,I-org
5,I-org
Everyone,I-org
ignores,O
the,O
COVID-19,B-org
And,O
doesn't,O
maintain,O
social,O
Distancing,O
and,O
doesn't,O
wear,O
any,O
kind,O
of,O
masks.,O
please,O
take,O
a,O
action,O
for,O
this,O
Name,B-org
-,I-org
Shiva,I-org
Mob,I-org
No.,I-org
-,I-org
7836003684,I-org
Address,I-org
-,I-org
Gali,I-org
No.,I-org
-5,I-org
Nihal,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Nangloi,I-org
Delhi,I-org
-41,O
#BreakingNews,O
Number,O
of,O
#Delhi's,O
Corona,B-org
Containment,I-org
Zones,I-org
rise,O
to,O
"66,",O
six,O
more,O
added,O
today.,O
1.Sangam,B-geo
vihar,I-geo
L,I-geo
block,O
2.Tuglakabad,O
exten,O
3.C,B-org
block,O
hari,O
nagar,O
4.B,B-org
block,O
hari,O
nagar,O
5.Nangloi,B-org
6.Nihal,I-org
vihar,I-org
#DelhiFightsCorona,I-org
#Covid_19,I-org
#coronavirusinindia,I-org
#Covid_19,I-org
#Corona,I-org
#hotspotspic.twitter.com/6YvRc0NK7Q,O
Pratishtha,B-per
youth,O
club,O
and,O
Tau,B-org
Devi,I-org
lal,I-org
Youth,I-org
club,I-org
of,I-org
Nehru,I-org
Yuva,I-org
Kendra,I-org
#West,I-org
(Nangloi),I-org
",",I-org
Delhi,I-org
preparation,I-org
and,I-org
Distribution,I-org
of,I-org
Face,I-org
masks,O
for,O
prevention,O
of,O
COVID-19.,B-org
@KirenRijiju,O
|,O
@RijijuOffice,O
|,O
@YASMinistry,O
|,O
@PMOIndiapic.twitter.com/upqTOyWjvP,O
03-APR-,O
2020,O
#COVID-19,B-org
Nikal,I-org
Vihar,I-org
#Nangloi,I-org
#DELHI,I-org
Responding,I-org
quickly,O
to,O
all,O
requests.,O
Good,O
Samaritans,B-org
&,I-org
Volunteers,I-org
delivering,O
dry,O
snacks,O
to,O
people,O
at,O
OLD,B-art
AGE,I-art
HOME,I-art
(Vridhashram),I-art
LET,I-art
US,I-art
JOIN,I-art
HANDS,I-art
TO,B-org
SAVE,I-org
HOMELESS,I-org
https://www.facebook.com/childrensjamghat/photos/a.159499977927964/659756251235665/,O
…,O
http://www.jamghat.org,O
pic.twitter.com/8vWfUaq1XO,O
Follow,O
these,O
rules,O
and,O
"stay,",O
safe,O
and,O
sound.,O
The,O
only,O
way,O
we,O
can,O
defeat,O
covid,O
19,O
Stay,O
home,O
and,O
save,O
all.,O
@,O
"Nangloi,",B-org
"Delhi,",I-org
India,I-org
https://www.instagram.com/p/B-q11qmlYaE/?igshid=hx0c5g9yw21f,O
…,O
Operation,O
of,O
freight,O
trains,O
is,O
continuing,O
while,O
passenger,O
train,O
services,O
are,O
suspended,O
in,O
wake,O
of,O
COVID-19.,B-org
Station,I-org
Master,I-org
on,O
duty,O
at,O
Nangloi,B-geo
railway,O
station,O
of,B-org
Delhi,I-org
Division,I-org
wearing,O
mask,O
and,O
maintaining,O
social,O
distancing.,O
@RailMinIndia,O
@RailwayNorthernpic.twitter.com/Yyv9xsPFVR,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Covid,O
19,O
ke,O
Chalte,O
kiranewalo,O
ne,O
agar,O
nagar,O
nangloi,O
mein,O
Delhi,B-geo
area,O
mein,O
atta,O
etyadi,O
jaruri,O
saman,O
ke,O
rate,O
bada,O
diye,O
hai.,O
Aap,O
se,O
anurodh,O
hai,O
is,O
tarah,O
ke,O
dukandaro,O
par,O
karwahi,O
ki,O
jaye.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Delhi-41,B-org
Nangloi,I-org
Nihal,I-org
Vihar,I-org
Rzr,I-org
-,I-org
Block,I-org
K.G.,I-org
Property's,I-org
Gali,I-org
No.,I-org
5,I-org
had,O
no,O
effect,O
of,O
Lockdown,O
all,O
the,O
people,O
gathering,O
together,O
and,O
some,O
crowd,O
in,O
this,O
Street.,B-per
Do,I-per
police,O
petroling,O
in,O
Same,B-geo
Gali,I-geo
otherwise,O
COVID,B-tim
-,I-tim
19,I-tim
is,O
Spread,O
people,O
didn't,O
understand,O
Lockdown,O
meaning,O
Operation,O
of,O
freight,O
trains,O
is,O
continuing,O
while,O
passenger,O
train,O
services,O
are,O
suspended,O
in,O
wake,O
of,O
COVID-19.,B-org
Station,I-org
Master,I-org
on,O
duty,O
at,O
Nangloi,B-geo
railway,O
station,O
of,B-org
Delhi,I-org
Division,I-org
wearing,O
mask,O
and,O
maintaining,O
social,O
distancing.,O
@RailMinIndia,O
@RailwayNorthernpic.twitter.com/Yyv9xsPFVR,O
@DelhiPolice,O
A,O
guy,O
in,O
I-,B-org
Block,I-org
naraina,O
vihar,O
",",O
new,O
delhi,O
who,O
is,O
living,O
with,O
his,O
mother,O
",",O
his,O
mother,O
is,O
a,O
COVID,B-org
pateint.,O
That,O
guy,O
is,O
roaming,O
freely,O
in,O
the,O
area.,O
Can,O
you,O
please,O
take,O
some,O
actions??,O
4,O
positive,O
cases,O
of,O
COVID-19,B-org
in,O
Naraina,B-org
"Vihar,",I-org
"(E-25,",I-org
Naraina,I-org
"Vihar,",I-org
Delhi),I-org
admitted,O
in,O
Safdurjang.,B-geo
Still,O
3,O
people,O
from,O
the,O
place,O
are,O
going,O
to,O
there,O
shops,O
in,O
a,O
HOTSPOT,O
region,O
(Budh,B-org
"Nagar,",I-org
Inderpuri).,I-org
Please,I-org
sanitize,O
and,O
seal,O
the,O
area.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@DelhiPolice,O
@msisodia,O
Covid,O
19,O
positive,O
case,O
in,O
Naraina,B-org
Vihar,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
Need,I-org
urgent,O
support.,O
Please,O
call,O
9716061455,O
@officeofbagga,O
@NatashaGambhi02,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
@PMOIndia,O
@indiatvnews,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@TajinderBagga,O
sir,O
one,O
of,O
my,O
known,O
one,O
is,O
covid-19,O
#NAME?,O
No,O
team,O
has,O
arrived,O
at,O
home.,O
Contacted,O
helpline,O
they,O
said,O
a,O
Team,B-org
will,O
arrive,O
but,O
no,O
one,O
has,O
come.,O
Pls,O
helo,O
the,O
family.,O
#coronavirusinindia,O
@DelhiPolice,O
location-,O
"Nawada,",B-org
Delhi,I-org
Thanks,O
for,O
help,O
of,O
Bihari,B-geo
migrants.,O
Sir,O
I,O
am,O
Naveen,B-per
Yadav,I-per
requesting,O
from,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
belongs,O
to,O
Dist,B-org
Nawada,I-org
Bihar,I-org
unable,O
to,O
contact,O
covid-19,O
helpline,O
no,O
which,O
is,O
given,O
by,O
Bihar,B-geo
govt.,O
sir,O
plz,O
request,O
how,O
to,O
go,O
our,O
Bihar,O
sir,O
plz,O
suggest.,O
#BiharFightsCorona,O
update,O
of,O
the,O
day.1,O
more,O
covid-19,O
positive,O
case,O
in,O
bihar,O
taking,O
the,O
total,O
to,O
39,O
male,O
38,O
from,O
nawada,O
with,O
a,O
travel,O
history,O
to,O
delhi.we,O
are,O
further,O
ascertaining,O
his,O
travel,O
history,O
and,O
contacts,O
A,O
general,O
view,O
of,O
Nehru,B-geo
Place,I-geo
market,O
after,O
the,O
government,O
eased,O
a,O
nationwide,O
lockdown,O
imposed,O
as,O
a,O
preventive,O
measure,O
against,O
the,O
spread,O
of,O
the,O
COVID-19,B-org
coronavirus,O
in,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
on,O
Tuesday.,B-org
(ANI,I-org
Photo/Prabhat,I-org
Mehrotra),I-org
#DelhiLockdown,O
#Lockdown4pic.twitter.com/tJHdr2pD3b,O
@AAPDelhi,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@PMOIndia,O
delhi,O
is,O
going,O
insane,O
today.,O
We,O
need,O
to,O
i,O
trospect,O
our,O
decision,O
to,O
open,O
thhings,O
abruptly.,O
Few,O
images,O
of,O
liquor,O
stores,O
parking,O
and,O
roads,O
around,O
nehru,O
place.,O
No,O
rules,O
followed,O
with,O
473,O
cases,O
in,O
24,O
hrs.,O
#covid-19,O
#kejriwal,O
#dangerousdelhipic.twitter.com/AcQw7OMuwr,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
If,O
commercial,O
hub,O
office,O
space,O
in,O
delhi,O
like,O
Nehru,B-geo
"place,NSP",O
get,O
open,O
does,O
it,O
not,O
increase,O
the,O
covid,O
-19,O
cases.,O
As,O
many,O
buildings,O
are,O
centralize,O
AC...@PMOIndia,O
@narendramodi,O
@msisodiahttps://twitter.com/ArvindKejriwal/status/1256924603143733248,O
…,O
New,B-org
Service,I-org
Rate,I-org
for,O
CORONAVIRUS,B-org
time,O
Please,O
cooperate,O
Management,O
LYNX,B-org
Hair,I-org
Skin,I-org
"Clinic,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
"G-20,",I-org
Krishna,I-org
Apra,I-org
"Building,",I-org
Near,I-org
Fun,I-org
"Cinema,",I-org
Netaji,I-org
Subhash,I-org
"Place,",I-org
"Pitampura,",I-org
Delhi,I-org
110034,O
#coronavirus,O
#Covid_19,O
#Covid_19india,O
#Lockdown2pic.twitter.com/fviMLHM9Zd,O
One,O
person,O
is,O
suffering,O
from,O
fever,O
and,O
his,O
current,O
address,O
is,O
"B1/203,",B-org
Ground,I-org
"floor,",O
Street,O
no,O
"6,",O
New,B-org
Ashok,I-org
"Nagar,",I-org
Delhi,I-org
Name,I-org
-,I-org
Nilotpal,I-org
Contact,I-org
No.,I-org
8809801100,O
He,O
visited,O
ILBS,B-org
but,O
they,O
refuse,O
to,O
do,O
covid,O
19,O
test,O
.,O
Pls,O
help,O
him,O
.,O
@Ikumar7,O
A,O
person,O
-8860230275,O
lives,O
in,O
new,O
Ashok,O
"nagar,",O
east,O
delhi,O
came,O
in,O
contact,O
with,O
covid,O
19,O
patient.,O
Pls,O
help.@hrypr,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
Covid,B-org
Positive,I-org
in,O
New,B-org
Ashok,I-org
Nagar,I-org
"(A-Block,",I-org
Gali,I-org
No.9),I-org
Covid-19,I-org
positive,O
board,O
put,O
in,O
front,O
of,O
the,O
house,O
and,O
whole,O
family,O
has,O
been,O
home,O
quarantined,O
!,O
No,O
of,O
positives,O
not,O
confirmed,O
till,O
now,O
but,O
locals,O
suspect,O
more,O
then,O
5,O
members,O
of,O
the,O
family,O
!,O
#Delhi,B-per
#CoronavirusIndia,O
@Rahul_Gupta_IPS,O
Sir,O
I,O
am,O
writing,O
directly,O
to,O
you,O
because,O
the,O
situation,O
is,O
being,O
critical,O
in,O
"delhi,",O
delhi,O
slum,O
like,O
new,O
Ashok,O
nagar,O
",",O
where,O
no,O
social,O
distancing,O
is,O
followed,O
also,O
the,O
covid-19,O
positive,O
patient,O
no,O
sealing,O
being,O
done.,O
Please,O
respond,O
or,O
contact,O
on,O
my,O
8467822414,O
Agar,O
aap,O
action,O
lelogey,O
to,O
kuch,O
hoga,O
hi,O
nahi,O
covid-19,O
area,O
New,B-org
Ashok,I-org
nagar,O
gali,O
no.,O
17,O
delhi,O
#COVID19India,O
#containmentzone,O
@CPDelhipic.twitter.com/pde7Lwy3Lj,O
Sir,O
regret,O
to,O
say,O
your,O
are,O
not,O
a,O
key,O
player,O
to,O
take,O
necessary,O
action,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@CMODelhi,O
@DCPEastDelhi,O
@dmeastdelhi,O
@dmgbnagar,O
@BJP4Delhi,O
@katakshfor,O
@GautamGambhir,O
covid-19,O
area,O
New,B-org
Ashok,I-org
nagar,O
new,O
delhi,O
gali,O
no.,O
17,O
pic.twitter.com/yLTVrwbOzg,O
"SIR,",O
Why,O
are,O
you,O
not,O
understanding,O
the,O
situation,O
here,O
please,O
help,O
a,O
block,O
New,O
Ashok,O
nagar,O
gali,O
no.17,O
delhi,O
containment,O
zone,O
covid-19,O
positive,O
pic.twitter.com/ldKgTNqwZT,O
Please,O
highlight,O
this,O
issue,O
which,O
is,O
much,O
critical,O
as,O
it,O
will,O
create,O
delhi,O
dharawi,O
",",O
New,B-org
Ashok,I-org
nagar,O
new,O
delhi,O
Covid-19,O
area.,O
@AnkushNarang_,O
@msisodia,O
@CMODelhi,O
@ANTISECULAR,O
@myogiadityanath,O
@katakshfor,O
@CPDelhi,O
@DelhiPolice,O
@rjraunacpic.twitter.com/8Ne420sx3k,O
Sir,O
yha,O
pey,O
madad,O
karwa,O
do,O
sab,O
khula,O
hua,O
h,O
covid-19,O
area,O
h,O
a,O
block,O
gali,O
no.,O
17,O
New,B-org
Ashok,I-org
nagar,O
new,O
delhi,O
pic.twitter.com/PJL6JrD1ek,O
Yha,B-per
pr,O
koi,O
action,O
nhi,O
liya,O
jaa,O
rha,O
covid-19,O
area,O
h,O
aur,O
sab,O
open,O
h,O
a,O
block,O
gali,O
no.,O
17,O
New,B-org
Ashok,I-org
nagar,O
new,O
delhi,O
pic.twitter.com/TvCFUcOax8,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
#Help#,B-per
SHO,I-per
number,O
required,O
New,B-org
Ashok,I-org
nagar,O
delhi,O
no,O
action,O
being,O
taken,O
by,O
them,O
for,O
postive,O
covid-19,O
patient,O
@msisodia,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@Republic_Bharat,B-org
@DCPNewDelhi,I-org
@CPDelhi,I-org
@CMODelhi,I-org
@DCPEastDelhi,I-org
@PMOIndia,O
@ShraddhaKapoor,O
@ABPNews,O
Covid-19,O
positive,O
patient,O
found,O
in,O
gali,B-tim
no.,I-tim
17,I-tim
New,I-tim
Ashok,I-tim
nagar,O
new,O
delhi,O
no,O
one,O
taking,O
response,O
to,O
quarantine,O
or,O
isolate,O
him,O
on,O
calling,O
helpline,O
number,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@CMODelhi,O
@CPDelhi,O
@DCPEastDelhi,O
Whom,O
I,O
contact,O
to,O
opened,O
my,O
street,O
due,O
to,O
covid,O
19,O
patient,O
found,O
in,O
our,O
area.,O
Mla,B-geo
and,O
aho,O
and,O
dm,O
office,O
no,O
ne,O
take,O
"responsibility,",O
and,O
our,O
area,O
is,O
not,O
listed,O
in,O
containment,O
"zones,",O
I,O
am,O
living,O
in,O
new,O
ashok,O
nagar,O
"delhi,",O
now,O
21,B-tim
days,O
completed,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Sir,B-org
Great,I-org
"work,",O
Please,O
help,O
me,O
also,O
as,O
I,O
have,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
rent,O
INR,O
6000,O
and,O
am,O
running,O
Short,O
of,O
money,O
.,O
I,O
live,O
in,O
new,O
ashok,O
Nagar,B-geo
delhi,I-geo
but,O
got,O
stuck,O
in,O
bihar,O
due,O
to,O
covid,O
19,O
Mobile,O
no,O
8285294157,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Sir,B-org
Great,I-org
"work,",O
Please,O
help,O
me,O
also,O
as,O
I,O
have,O
to,O
pay,O
the,O
rent,O
INR,O
6000,O
and,O
am,O
running,O
Short,O
of,O
money,O
.,O
I,O
live,O
in,O
new,O
ashok,O
Nagar,B-geo
delhi,I-geo
but,O
got,O
stuck,O
in,O
bihar,O
due,O
to,O
covid,O
19,O
Covid,O
19,O
patient,O
found,O
in,O
our,O
area,O
18,B-tim
april,I-tim
2020,O
I,O
am,O
living,O
in,O
new,O
ashok,O
nagar,O
delhi,O
110096,O
Now,O
15,O
days,O
completed,O
and,O
no,O
one,O
take,O
the,O
test,O
was,O
done,O
"yet,",O
and,O
we,O
didn't,O
understand,O
the,O
systems.,O
So,O
highlight,O
this,O
matters.,O
@ShahiPratap,O
"Sir,",O
Most,O
humbly,O
and,O
respectfully,O
I,O
beg,O
to,O
state,O
that,O
Currently,O
*I,B-org
am,O
living,O
in,O
Ashok,B-org
"Nagar,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
of,I-org
Nation,I-org
capital,O
Territory,O
for,O
Study,B-org
Purpose.*,I-org
Due,I-org
to,O
Covid-19,B-org
Pandemic,I-org
"Lockdown,",I-org
I,I-org
have,O
been,O
stucked,O
here,O
and,O
facing,O
so,O
many,O
difficulties.,O
@JharkhandCMO,O
@dc_garhwa,O
"Sir,",O
Most,O
humbly,O
and,O
respectfully,O
I,O
beg,O
to,O
state,O
that,O
Currently,O
*I,B-org
am,O
living,O
in,O
Ashok,B-org
"Nagar,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
of,I-org
Nation,I-org
capital,O
Territory,O
for,O
Study,B-org
Purpose.*,I-org
Due,I-org
to,O
Covid-19,B-org
Pandemic,I-org
"Lockdown,",I-org
I,I-org
have,O
been,O
stucked,O
here,O
and,O
facing,O
so,O
many,O
difficulties.,O
@dc_garhwa,O
"Sir,",O
Most,O
humbly,O
and,O
respectfully,O
I,O
beg,O
to,O
state,O
that,O
Currently,O
*I,B-org
am,O
living,O
in,O
Ashok,B-org
"Nagar,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
of,I-org
Nation,I-org
capital,O
Territory,O
for,O
Study,B-org
Purpose.*,I-org
Due,I-org
to,O
Covid-19,B-org
Pandemic,I-org
"Lockdown,",I-org
I,I-org
have,O
been,O
stucked,O
here,O
and,O
facing,O
so,O
many,O
difficulties.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
nigam,O
pratibha,O
vidhyalay(girls),O
new,O
ashok,O
nagar,O
delhi,O
110096,O
Kisi,B-per
kobhi,I-per
rqtion,O
nhi,O
diya,O
ja,O
rha,O
h.,O
Or,O
misbehave,O
kr,O
rhe,O
h.,O
Ration,O
kb,O
milega,O
koi,O
pta,O
nhi.,O
Mai,B-geo
khud,O
3,O
din,O
se,O
line,O
m,O
lga,O
hu.,O
Ese,O
to,O
yahi,O
pr,O
covid-19,O
hotspot,O
bn,O
jayega.,O
Help,O
kro,O
sir.,O
Ese,O
nhi,O
chalega.,O
pic.twitter.com/3sexfPE4wQ,O
FILE,O
-,O
In,O
this,O
April,B-tim
"9,",O
2020,O
file,O
"photo,",O
a,O
chemist,O
displays,O
hydroxychloroquine,O
tablets,O
in,O
New,B-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
India.,I-geo
U.S.,I-geo
regulators,O
are,O
revoking,O
emergency,O
authorization,O
for,O
malaria,O
drugs,O
promoted,O
by,O
President,B-per
Donald,I-per
Trump,I-per
for,O
treating,O
COVID-19.,O
https://cultureshock.website/2020/06/15/the-us-revokes-emergency-use-of-drugs-touted-by-trump-vs-virus/,O
…pic.twitter.com/7AE3fKIgJv,O
Delhi’s,O
10k-bed,O
facility,O
to,O
be,O
ready,O
by,O
"June-end,",O
Health,B-org
"News,",I-org
ET,I-org
"HealthWorld,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi:,I-org
A,I-org
"10,000-bed",O
makeshift,O
facility,O
coming,O
up,O
at,O
Chhatarpur,B-geo
in,O
South,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
to,O
tackle,O
the,O
capital’s,O
surging,O
Covid-19,O
cases,O
will,O
...,O
",http://medicalnewser.com/delhis-10k-bed-facility-to-be-ready-by-june-end-health-news-et-healthworld.html",O
…pic.twitter.com/yyTOVa83o2,O
Totay,O
a,O
CRPF,B-org
jawan,O
martyr,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
due,O
to,O
covid,O
19....,O
He,O
was,O
father,O
of,O
my,O
best,O
friend...Dr,O
Abhishek,O
kumar...,O
One,O
more,O
corona,O
warrior,O
martyr,O
in,O
New,B-geo
Delhi...,I-geo
Lockdown,I-geo
is,O
urgently,O
required,O
in,O
Delhi.,B-geo
#NarendraModi,O
#ArvindKejriwal,O
#AmitShahpic.twitter.com/YlKCNhtDTU,O
Coronavirus,B-org
USA,I-org
Criticism,I-org
mounts,O
as,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
hospital,O
beds,O
run,O
out,O
amid,O
COVID-19,O
surge,O
-,O
https://www.coronavirusworldnews.com/coronavirus-usa-criticism-mounts-as-new-delhi-hospital-beds-run-out-amid-covid-19-surge/,O
…pic.twitter.com/MsQRuRxEJg,O
Criticism,O
mounts,O
as,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
hospital,O
beds,O
run,O
out,O
amid,O
COVID-19,O
surge,O
https://in.reuters.com/article/health-coronavirus-india-delhi-idINKBN23M1WY?taid=5ee7d31d9cfd9b00017a2136&utm_campaign=trueAnthem%3A+Trending+Content&utm_medium=trueAnthem&utm_source=twitter,O
…pic.twitter.com/PXm4H4UyzM,O
New,B-org
Delhi:,I-org
AIIMS,I-org
sets,O
up,O
24x7,O
COVID-19,O
helpline,O
number,O
https://www.dnaindia.com/india/report-new-delhi-aiims-sets-up-24x7-covid-19-helpline-number-2828036,O
…,O
RT,B-org
@Reuters:,I-org
Criticism,I-org
mounts,O
as,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
hospital,O
beds,O
run,O
out,O
amid,O
COVID-19,O
surge,O
https://reut.rs/37ySuVq,O
pic.twitter.com/vbcEiXQbTy,O
I,O
appreciate,O
efforts,O
of,O
Indian,B-gpe
government,O
wrt,O
COVID,O
19,O
however,O
International,O
passengers,O
landing,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
r,O
facing,O
a,O
lot,O
of,O
challenge,O
at,O
the,O
Airport.,O
No,O
social,O
distancing,O
norms,O
followed.,O
@narendramodi,O
@AmitShah,O
@AjeetDoval,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
It's,O
spoiling,O
our,O
country's,O
image,O
CHIEFSWORLD,B-org
CHIEFSWORLD,I-org
Criticism,I-org
mounts,O
as,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
hospital,O
beds,O
run,O
out,O
amid,O
COVID-19,O
surge,O
http://dlvr.it/RYhHfD,O
Criticism,O
mounts,O
as,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
hospital,O
beds,O
run,O
out,O
amid,O
COVID-19,O
surge,O
http://dlvr.it/RYhG15,O
My,O
mother,O
admitted,O
in,O
central,O
hospital,O
of,O
northern,O
railways,O
at,O
new,O
Delhi,B-geo
(bed,O
"no.8,",O
ward,O
no.15),O
since,O
08-06-2020,O
#NAME?,O
for,O
covid,O
thrice.,O
1st,O
report,O
"+ve,",O
2nd,O
#NAME?,O
&,O
3rd,O
#NAME?,O
Pvt.,O
lab,O
are,O
not,O
giving,O
correct,O
results.Need,O
to,O
think,O
why,O
labs,O
are,O
giving,O
different,O
results.,O
M-,B-org
8527303344,O
https://twitter.com/Ijm1972/status/1272481675566411777,O
…,O
My,O
mother,O
admitted,O
in,O
central,O
hospital,O
of,O
northern,O
railways,O
at,O
new,O
Delhi,B-geo
(bed,O
"no.8,",O
ward,O
no.15),O
since,O
08-06-2020,O
#NAME?,O
for,O
covid,O
thrice.,O
1st,O
report,O
"+ve,",O
2nd,O
#NAME?,O
&,O
3rd,O
#NAME?,O
Pvt.,O
lab,O
are,O
not,O
giving,O
correct,O
results.Need,O
to,O
think,O
why,O
labs,O
are,O
giving,O
different,O
results.,O
M-,B-org
8527303344,O
https://twitter.com/Ijm1972/status/1272482537986613248,O
…,O
My,O
mother,O
admitted,O
in,O
central,O
hospital,O
of,O
northern,O
railways,O
at,O
new,O
Delhi,B-geo
(bed,O
"no.8,",O
ward,O
no.15),O
since,O
08-06-2020,O
#NAME?,O
for,O
covid,O
thrice.,O
1st,O
report,O
"+ve,",O
2nd,O
#NAME?,O
&,O
3rd,O
#NAME?,O
Pvt.,O
lab,O
are,O
not,O
giving,O
correct,O
results.Need,O
to,O
think,O
why,O
labs,O
are,O
giving,O
different,O
results.,O
M-,B-org
8527303344,O
https://twitter.com/Ijm1972/status/1272486481538330625,O
…,O
My,O
mother,O
admitted,O
in,O
central,O
hospital,O
of,O
northern,O
railways,O
at,O
new,O
Delhi,B-geo
(bed,O
"no.8,",O
ward,O
no.15),O
since,O
08-06-2020,O
#NAME?,O
for,O
covid,O
thrice.,O
1st,O
report,O
"+ve,",O
2nd,O
#NAME?,O
&,O
3rd,O
#NAME?,O
Pvt.,O
lab,O
are,O
not,O
giving,O
correct,O
results.Need,O
to,O
think,O
why,O
labs,O
are,O
giving,O
different,O
results.,O
M-,B-org
8527303344,O
https://twitter.com/sardesairajdeep/status/1272544067445043201,O
…,O
My,O
mother,O
admitted,O
in,O
central,O
hospital,O
of,O
northern,O
railways,O
at,O
new,O
Delhi,B-geo
(bed,O
"no.8,",O
ward,O
no.15),O
since,O
08-06-2020,O
#NAME?,O
for,O
covid,O
thrice.,O
1st,O
report,O
"+ve,",O
2nd,O
#NAME?,O
&,O
3rd,O
#NAME?,O
Pvt.,O
lab,O
are,O
not,O
giving,O
correct,O
results.Need,O
to,O
think,O
why,O
labs,O
are,O
giving,O
different,O
results.,O
M-,B-org
8527303344,O
https://twitter.com/Ijm1972/status/1272486776884441091,O
…,O
My,O
mother,O
admitted,O
in,O
central,O
hospital,O
of,O
northern,O
railways,O
at,O
new,O
Delhi,B-geo
(bed,O
"no.8,",O
ward,O
no.15),O
since,O
08-06-2020,O
#NAME?,O
for,O
covid,O
thrice.,O
1st,O
report,O
"+ve,",O
2nd,O
#NAME?,O
&,O
3rd,O
#NAME?,O
Pvt.,O
lab,O
are,O
not,O
giving,O
correct,O
results.Need,O
to,O
think,O
why,O
labs,O
are,O
giving,O
different,O
results.,O
M-,B-org
8527303344,O
https://twitter.com/Ijm1972/status/1272486574786150402,O
…,O
Criticism,O
mounts,O
as,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
hospital,O
beds,O
run,O
out,O
amid,O
COVID-19,O
surge,O
https://wealthy-healthylife.com/?p=20741,O
Criticism,O
mounts,O
as,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
hospital,O
beds,O
run,O
out,O
amid,O
COVID-19,O
surge,O
|,O
Reuters,B-org
https://in.reuters.com/article/health-coronavirus-india-delhi-idINKBN23M1WY,O
…,O
Will,O
AAP,O
leaders,O
come,O
out,O
of,O
AC,B-org
rooms,O
to,O
face,O
the,O
music,O
now.,O
My,O
uncle,O
died,O
yesterday.,O
Aunty,O
went,O
to,O
the,O
neighbours,O
asking,O
for,O
"help,",O
they,O
shut,O
their,O
doors,O
in,O
her,O
face.,O
She,O
then,O
called,O
the,O
Covid-19,B-geo
"helpline(1075),",O
they,O
asked,O
her,O
the,O
"symptoms,",O
and,O
sent,O
police,O
at,O
her,O
residence,O
in,O
Nirman,B-org
"Vihar,",I-org
Delhi.,I-org
Uncle,I-org
was,O
dead,O
by,O
the,O
time,O
police,O
arrived.,O
@narendramodi,O
@PMOIndia,O
Hello,B-geo
sir,O
we,O
r,O
proud,O
of,O
that,O
you,O
have,O
taken,O
right,O
decisions,O
against,O
covid-19.,O
In,O
this,O
situation,O
my,O
wife,O
is,O
working,O
in,O
delhi,B-geo
based,O
company,O
named,O
Loanmart,B-org
nirman,O
vihar,O
delhi.,O
My,O
salary,O
is,O
pending,O
from,O
month,O
feb,O
and,O
march.,O
Kindly,O
take,O
the,O
decision.,O
8860082885,O
@myogiadityanath,O
Sir,O
I,O
request,O
you,O
to,O
please,O
open,O
a,O
COVID,B-org
19,O
testing,O
centre,O
in,O
Meerut.,B-geo
Meerut,I-geo
is,O
very,O
close,O
to,O
Delhi,B-geo
and,O
Noida,B-geo
so,O
it,O
is,O
a,O
prone,O
city.,O
Karnataka,B-geo
have,O
more,O
testing,O
facilities,O
than,O
us,O
while,O
we,O
have,O
larger,O
population,O
than,O
Karnataka,B-geo
Zee,O
Media,O
building,O
in,O
Noida,B-geo
Sector-16,I-geo
has,O
been,O
sealed,O
A,O
worker,O
in,O
Zee,B-geo
"Media,",I-geo
who,O
is,O
resident,O
of,O
"Delhi,",B-geo
was,O
tested,O
for,O
COVID-19,B-org
on,O
May,B-tim
15,O
A,O
total,O
51,O
samples,O
were,O
collected,O
and,O
sent,O
for,O
"testing,",O
of,O
these,O
28,O
‘positive’,O
patients,O
were,O
found.,O
#coronaupdatesindia,O
#coronaviruspic.twitter.com/7t2YVK0gkV,O
Respected,O
"sir,",O
Great,O
efforts,O
taken,O
by,O
the,O
Noida,B-org
Police,I-org
to,O
comply,O
the,O
direction,O
to,O
stop,O
Covid,O
19,O
and,O
even,O
the,O
boundary,O
of,O
Noida,B-org
has,O
been,O
sealed.,O
No,O
one,O
permitted,O
to,O
cross,O
Noida,B-org
via,I-org
Delhi,I-org
DND,I-org
&,O
sector,O
15,O
Coming,O
to,O
noida,B-geo
to,O
Delhi,B-geo
via,O
ghaziabad,O
is,O
permitted,O
as,O
people,O
using,O
that.,O
#Delhi,B-per
NCR,I-per
chapter,O
of,O
#HumanityFirst,O
donate,O
essential,O
grocery,O
items,O
in,O
food,O
kits,O
to,O
10,O
families,O
of,O
sector,O
105,O
Noida.,B-org
Kits,I-org
contain,O
items,O
which,O
should,O
suffice,O
a,O
small,O
family,O
of,O
four,O
for,O
at,O
least,O
15,O
days.,O
#Lockdown_MuslimsRelief,O
#Covid_19india,B-geo
#Islam,I-geo
#AhmadiyyaMuslimCommunitypic.twitter.com/x9KF7JtOrN,O
Zee,O
Media,O
building,O
in,O
Noida,B-geo
Sector-16,I-geo
has,O
been,O
sealed,O
after,O
six,O
fresh,O
COVID-19,O
cases,O
were,O
reported,O
on,O
Sunday.,O
The,O
five-story,O
building,O
was,O
sealed,O
between,O
11,O
pm,O
and,O
11:30,O
pm,O
on,O
Sunday.,B-org
A,I-org
worker,O
in,O
Zee,B-geo
"Media,",I-geo
who,O
is,O
resident,O
of,O
"Delhi,",B-geo
was,O
tested,O
for,O
"COVID-19,",B-org
Zee,O
Media,O
building,O
in,O
Noida,B-geo
Sector-16,I-geo
has,O
been,O
sealed,O
after,O
six,O
fresh,O
COVID-19,O
cases,O
were,O
reported,O
on,O
Sunday.,O
The,O
five-story,O
building,O
was,O
sealed,O
between,O
11,O
pm,O
and,O
11:30,O
pm,O
on,O
Sunday.,B-org
A,I-org
worker,O
in,O
Zee,B-geo
"Media,",I-geo
who,O
is,O
resident,O
of,O
"Delhi,",B-geo
was,O
tested,O
for,O
"COVID-19,",B-org
Zee,O
Media,O
building,O
in,O
Noida,B-geo
Sector-16,I-geo
has,O
been,O
sealed,O
A,O
worker,O
in,O
Zee,B-geo
"Media,",I-geo
who,O
is,O
resident,O
of,O
"Delhi,",B-geo
was,O
tested,O
for,O
COVID-19,B-org
on,O
May,B-tim
15,O
A,O
total,O
51,O
samples,O
were,O
collected,O
and,O
sent,O
for,O
"testing,",O
of,O
these,O
28,O
‘positive’,O
patients,O
were,O
found.,O
#coronaupdatesindia,O
#coronaviruspic.twitter.com/7t2YVK0gkV,O
Oleander,O
-,O
Okhla,B-geo
bird,O
sanctuary,O
#Delhi,B-per
(archives),O
#FlowerReport,O
stay,O
safe,O
#Covid_19indiapic.twitter.com/LQpaGW9D7P,O
Aap,O
ne,O
jo,O
Sab,B-per
Kuch,I-per
open,O
karne,O
ka,O
order,O
liya,O
"he,",O
rethink,O
it.,O
If,O
Delhi,B-per
is,O
in,O
community,O
spread,O
"stage,",O
lockdown,O
is,O
the,O
only,O
way,O
to,O
keep,O
the,O
numbers,O
low.,O
Opening,O
malls,O
and,O
religious,O
activities,O
will,O
make,O
the,O
conditions,O
worst.,O
NSIC,O
okhla,O
has,O
big,O
exhibition,O
area,O
use,O
that,O
for,O
Covid.,O
@AmitShah,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@TheAjitDovalNSA,O
Bhai,B-geo
saheb,O
GHUGHRUESETH,B-org
Kuch,I-org
nahi,I-org
karega,O
sivay,O
CADYANTRA,B-art
KARNE,I-art
Ke,I-art
ANAND,I-art
VIHAR,I-art
MARKAR,I-art
GAJIPUR,I-art
MANDI,I-art
AUR,I-art
OKHLA,I-art
MANDI,I-art
ke,O
cadyantra,O
hai,O
DELHI,O
ME,O
COVID,O
ke,O
failav,O
Krapya,B-geo
yahi,O
niyam,O
avrodh,O
paida,O
kare,O
to,O
bhi,O
ap,O
@LtGovDelhi,O
ajit,O
davol,O
Saheb,O
kohttps://twitter.com/AmitShah/status/1272067562537451521,O
…,O
#coronavirusindia,O
Faridabad,B-geo
recorded,O
it’s,O
fifth,O
Covid-19,O
death,O
on,O
Thursday,B-tim
after,O
a,O
17-year-old,O
girl,O
succumbed,O
to,O
the,O
infection.,O
#CoronaVirus,O
#Covid19,O
#pandemic,O
#InfectiousDisease,O
#CoronaVirusUpdate,O
#faridabad,O
#haryana,B-geo
#Delhi,I-geo
@DC_Faridabad,O
Due,O
to,O
health,O
conditon,O
of,O
my,O
old,O
age,O
senior,O
citizen,O
"parents,",O
plz,O
allow,O
my,O
family,O
to,O
came,O
back,O
home,O
from,O
Delhi,B-geo
to,O
take,O
care,O
of,O
them.,O
They,O
are,O
stuck,O
due,O
to,O
lockdown,O
since,B-tim
21,I-tim
march,O
2020,O
They,O
are,O
not,O
suffering,O
from,O
any,O
covid,O
symptoms.,O
Plz,O
help.,O
@LtGovDelhi,O
"Sir,",O
I,O
am,O
living,O
at:-,O
PLOT,O
NO.,O
"48-49,",O
RAJU,B-art
"EXT.,",I-art
OLD,I-art
PALAM,I-art
"ROAD,",I-art
OPP.,I-art
MBD,I-art
"SCHOOL,",I-art
"KAKROLA,",I-art
NEW,I-art
DELHI-78.,I-art
One,I-art
of,O
the,O
person,O
in,O
our,O
GALI,O
found,O
COVID-19+,O
yesterday.,O
BUT,O
no,O
any,O
SANITIZATION,O
or,O
Action,B-org
Taken,I-org
till,O
now,O
for,O
safety,O
of,O
others!,O
@SatyendarJain,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
"Sir,",O
I,O
am,O
living,O
at:-,O
PLOT,O
NO.,O
"48-49,",O
RAJU,B-art
"EXT.,",I-art
OLD,I-art
PALAM,I-art
"ROAD,",I-art
OPP.,I-art
MBD,I-art
"SCHOOL,",I-art
"KAKROLA,",I-art
NEW,I-art
DELHI-78.,I-art
One,I-art
of,O
the,O
person,O
in,O
our,O
GALI,O
found,O
COVID-19+,O
yesterday.,O
BUT,O
no,O
any,O
SANITIZATION,O
or,O
Action,B-org
Taken,I-org
till,O
now,O
for,O
safety,O
of,O
others!,O
@dtptraffic,O
@CPDelhi,O
@DCPSouthDelhi,O
"Sir,",O
I,O
am,O
living,O
at:-,O
PLOT,O
NO.,O
"48-49,",O
RAJU,B-art
"EXT.,",I-art
OLD,I-art
PALAM,I-art
"ROAD,",I-art
OPP.,I-art
MBD,I-art
"SCHOOL,",I-art
"KAKROLA,",I-art
NEW,I-art
DELHI-78.,I-art
One,I-art
of,O
the,O
person,O
in,O
our,O
GALI,O
found,O
COVID-19+,O
yesterday.,O
BUT,O
no,O
any,O
SANITIZATION,O
or,O
Action,B-org
Taken,I-org
till,O
now,O
for,O
safety,O
of,O
others!,O
@himachalpolice,O
"Sir,",O
I,O
wanted,O
to,O
enquire,O
about,O
the,O
passenger,O
limit,O
on,O
Inter-state,O
"travel,",O
We,O
are,O
a,O
family,O
of,O
"4,",O
with,O
a,O
personal,O
"car,",O
staying,O
in,O
South,B-geo
West,I-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
Palam,I-geo
Village,I-geo
(out,O
of,O
any,O
containment,O
zone).,O
I,O
haven't,O
applied,O
for,O
Covid,B-org
E-pass.,O
(1/2),O
Maybe,O
it,O
was,O
"impractical,",O
due,O
to,O
COVID,B-org
positive,O
case,O
in,O
Janakpuri,B-geo
in,O
the,O
beginning,O
of,O
Lockdown,O
"3,",O
the,O
entire,O
district,O
of,O
SW,B-org
Delhi,I-org
was,O
put,O
in,O
red,O
"zone,",O
which,O
include,O
Palam,B-geo
which,O
is,O
~6.5,O
KM,O
far,O
from,O
Janakpuri.,B-geo
Heat,O
Wave,O
condition,O
intensifies,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
-,O
maximum,O
temperature,O
recorded,O
is,O
47.6,O
degree,O
Celsius,O
in,O
Palam,B-geo
today.,O
Time,O
to,O
save,O
ourselves,O
from,O
heatwave,O
and,O
Covid-19,B-geo
both.,O
#Staysafe,O
#heatwave,O
#Delhiweather,O
#DelhiFightsCoronapic.twitter.com/K7sWoVfevE,O
Utter,O
confusion,O
with,O
regard,O
to,O
partial,O
relief,O
on,O
lockdown,O
in,O
Delhi.,O
I,O
own,O
one,O
warehouse,O
cum,O
small,O
assembly,O
unit,O
of,O
home,O
entertainment,O
products,O
falling,O
in,O
Palam,B-geo
village,O
of,O
south-west,O
Delhi.,O
Can,O
I,O
operate,O
the,O
unit,O
by,O
following,O
COVID-19,O
norms,O
?,O
Do,O
I,O
need,O
separate,O
permission,O
for,O
it,O
?,O
Jindal,B-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
situated,O
at,O
"Dashrathpuri,",B-org
Dwarka,I-org
-,I-org
Palam,I-org
"Road,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
Parents,I-org
Teacher's,I-org
Meeting,I-org
(Month,I-org
of,I-org
April),I-org
#COVID__19.,I-org
#lockdownindia,O
#Lockdown2.pic.twitter.com/DU8YcLZ8ba,O
Jindal,B-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
situated,O
at,O
"Dashrathpuri,",B-org
Dwarka,I-org
-,I-org
Palam,I-org
"Road,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
Started,I-org
online,O
classes,O
to,O
bridge,O
the,O
education,O
gap,O
created,O
due,O
to,O
the,O
#COVID__19.,B-org
#lockdownindia,I-org
#Lockdown2,I-org
.pic.twitter.com/mucvLVT2q0,O
Jindal,B-org
Public,I-org
School,I-org
situated,O
at,O
"Dashrathpuri,",B-org
Dwarka,I-org
-,I-org
Palam,I-org
"Road,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi.,I-org
Started,I-org
online,O
classes,O
to,O
bridge,O
the,O
education,O
gap,O
created,O
due,O
to,O
the,O
#COVID__19.,B-org
#lockdownindia,O
#Lockdown2pic.twitter.com/lnq26xvVn3,O
The,O
purpose,O
of,O
drawing,O
your,O
attention,O
Mr,O
@AmitKhatriIAS,O
is,O
to,O
solicit,O
your,O
help,O
for,O
grant,O
of,O
SPECIAL,O
EXEMPTION,O
for,O
me,O
to,O
travel,O
from,O
Palam,B-org
Vihar,I-org
Ggn,I-org
to,O
Escorts,B-org
Hospital,I-org
Delhi,I-org
daily.,O
My,O
concern,O
being,O
that,O
I,O
am,O
only,O
Physician,B-gpe
&,O
key,O
member,O
of,O
the,O
Covid,B-org
Task,I-org
Force,I-org
in,O
Hospital.,B-geo
As,O
part,O
of,O
the,O
Don,B-org
Bosco,I-org
Solidarity,I-org
COVID-19,I-org
relief,O
"work,",O
the,O
Don,B-org
Bosco,I-org
Network,I-org
team,O
distributed,O
a,O
second,O
round,O
of,O
grocery,O
kits,O
to,O
the,O
migrant,O
families,O
living,O
under,O
the,O
Palam,B-org
flyover,O
in,O
Delhi.,B-geo
#Covid19,I-geo
#CoronaVirus,O
#India,B-geo
#WeAreDonBoscopic.twitter.com/AItxENJp0L,O
As,O
"predicted,",O
#Palam,B-org
#Delhi,I-org
recorded,O
39.7,O
"degree,",O
almost,O
touched,O
40,O
degree,O
mark.This,O
is,O
the,O
highest,O
#maximum,O
of,O
the,O
season.,O
#Safdarjung,O
recorded,O
38.1,O
degree.,O
#DelhiSummer,O
#DelhiHeat,O
#DelhiRains,O
#COVID,O
@SkymetWeather,O
Up,O
in,O
the,O
Sky....,B-org
Clicked,I-org
by,O
captain.xubhu_,O
#imps31,O
#parikshitsoni,O
#singer,O
#delhi,O
#terracesinger,O
#covid,O
#lockdownsessions,O
@,O
Palam,B-org
https://www.instagram.com/p/B-6hOX0Jjid/?igshid=12pbl26ka7pa,O
…,O
Highest,O
#maximum,O
of,O
the,O
season,O
recorded,O
by,O
#Delhi,B-per
today.,I-per
#Safdarjung,I-per
is,O
36.9,O
and,O
#Palam,B-org
recorded,O
39.1,O
degree.,O
We,O
"think,",O
40,O
degree,O
is,O
not,O
far,O
away,O
now.,O
#DelhiRains,O
#DelhiSummer,O
#COVID__19,O
@SkymetWeather,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@aajtak,O
@ABPNews,O
@BBCHindi,O
@ndtv,O
@ZeeNewsHindi,O
@DelhiPolice,O
Do,O
you,O
really,O
Think,O
that,O
still,O
we,O
can,O
Win,O
That,O
fight,O
which,O
we,O
have,O
started,O
against,O
COVID-19.,O
After,O
this,O
type,O
of,O
mass,O
gathering,O
Delhi,B-org
Pictures,I-org
From,I-org
Palam,I-org
Colony,I-org
Raj,I-org
nagar,I-org
Part-2,I-org
Front,I-org
Of,I-org
DDA,I-org
Park.,I-org
pic.twitter.com/p9hryfxt3T,O
Koi,O
ye,O
batao...,O
abhi,O
jo,O
chilaane,O
se,O
gale,O
me,O
kharash,O
huyi...,O
#Covid_19,O
symptom,O
toh,O
nahi,O
maana,O
jaaega,O
n,O
??,O
Palam,B-org
Delhi,I-org
me,O
aadhe,O
ghante,O
tak,O
"shankh,",O
"ghanti,",O
taaliyon,O
aur,O
thaalio,O
se,O
aakash,O
gunj,O
gaya.,O
#5minute5baje,O
#5baje5minute,O
#ThaliBajao,O
#TaaliBajao,O
#clapforourcarers,O
Two,O
branches,O
of,O
pvt,O
school,O
#sealed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
over,O
violation,O
of,O
fee,O
norms,O
during,O
COVID-19,O
lockdown,O
Following,O
the,O
"directive,",O
two,O
branches,O
of,O
Apeejay,B-geo
School,I-geo
--,O
in,O
Sheikh,B-geo
Sarai's,O
Panchsheel,B-per
Park,I-per
and,O
Saket,O
--,O
were,O
sealed,O
on,O
Monday.,B-geo
Covid-19,O
update:,O
Sleepy,B-per
Panchsheel,I-per
Park,I-per
even,O
more,O
quiet,O
than,O
it,O
was,O
before,O
-,O
Nice,O
to,O
see,O
that,O
social,O
responsibility,O
of,O
our,O
colony,O
being,O
widely,O
recognised.,O
Specially,O
opening,O
up,O
of,O
Club,B-geo
Kitchen,I-geo
for,O
feeding,O
the,O
needy,O
in,O
association,O
with,O
the,O
Delhi,B-org
Police,I-org
https://www.hindustantimes.com/cities/affluent-panchsheel-park-still-as-cloistered-withdrawn-as-it-was-before-the-lockdown/story-y50q1Uv6r0OyBl8ht22F5L.html,O
…,O
Practising,O
social,O
distancing,O
&,O
personal,O
hygiene,O
are,O
the,O
only,O
vaccines,O
against,O
Covid-19.,B-org
Complimenting,I-org
the,O
Delhi,B-org
Govt,I-org
efforts;,I-org
BSES,I-org
has,O
distributed,O
soaps,O
to,O
~,O
3000,O
(&,O
counting),O
residents,O
of,O
JJ,B-org
clusters,O
in,O
Shakur,B-org
"Basti,",I-org
Meera,I-org
Bagh,I-org
&,I-org
Paschim,I-org
Vihar,I-org
in,O
West,B-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
@ArvindKejriwalpic.twitter.com/mwD4nOESNF,O
Respected,O
"PMO,",O
I,O
am,O
a,O
resident,O
of,O
north,O
west,O
"delhi,",O
Paschim,B-per
Vihar,I-per
area,O
BG-7,O
"block,",O
residing,O
in,O
"BG-7/28,",B-org
ground,O
floor.,O
I,O
am,O
regretful,O
to,O
say,O
this,O
as,O
we,O
are,O
going,O
through,O
a,O
very,O
tough,O
time,O
because,O
of,O
"COVID-19,",B-org
and,O
in,O
this,O
deadly,O
situation,O
there,O
has,O
been,O
no,O
proper,O
sanitisation.,O
Thanks,O
to,O
Delhi,B-geo
Govt.,I-geo
for,O
taking,O
strong,O
step,O
of,O
lockdown,O
to,O
control,O
spread,O
of,O
COVID-19.,B-org
"However,",I-org
despite,O
of,O
lockdown,O
i,O
can,O
see,O
lots,O
people,O
on,O
roads.,O
"Also,",O
construction,O
activity,O
going,O
around.,O
AREA-,B-org
Paschim,I-org
Vihar,I-org
BG-5,I-org
/,I-org
BG-6,I-org
Block,I-org
West,I-org
Delhi,I-org
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@PMOIndia,O
@DelhiPolice,O
a,O
fresh,O
case,O
of,O
Sector,O
21,O
COVID,O
positve,O
A,O
25,B-tim
year,O
old,O
male,O
living,O
and,O
working,O
in,O
Patel,B-org
"Nagar,",I-org
Delhi,I-org
and,I-org
R/o,I-org
Uttrakhand,I-org
has,O
been,O
reported,O
to,O
be,O
positive,O
for,O
nCoV,O
on,O
his,O
visit,O
to,O
Chandigarh.,O
He,O
returned,O
from,O
Delhi,B-geo
on,O
May,B-tim
22,I-tim
to,O
visit,O
his,O
mother,O
working,O
in,O
a,O
house,O
in,O
sector-21.,O
COVID,O
STATUS,O
UPDATE,O
A,O
25,B-tim
year,O
old,O
male,O
living,O
and,O
working,O
in,O
Patel,B-org
"Nagar,",I-org
Delhi,I-org
and,I-org
R/o,I-org
Uttrakhand,I-org
has,O
been,O
reported,O
to,O
be,O
positive,O
for,O
nCoV,O
on,O
his,O
visit,O
to,O
Chandigarh.,O
He,O
returned,O
from,O
Delhi,B-geo
on,O
22nd,B-tim
"May,",I-tim
2020,I-tim
to,O
visit,O
his,O
mother,O
working,O
a,O
house,O
in,O
sector-21.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@DelhiJalBoard,O
We,O
citizen,O
of,O
21,O
"block,West",O
Patel,B-per
"Nagar,",I-per
Delhi-08,I-per
are,O
facing,O
major,O
problem,O
of,B-org
Delhi,I-org
Jal,I-org
board,O
Water,O
Supply,O
in,O
our,O
area.,O
We,O
approach,O
many,O
people,O
regarding,O
this,O
issue.,O
I,O
request,O
you,O
to,O
plz,O
look,O
into,O
the,O
matter,O
in,O
this,O
difficult,B-tim
time,I-tim
of,I-tim
Covid,I-tim
19,I-tim
ASAP.,I-tim
@DelhiJalBoard,O
NAME:,B-org
Omang,I-org
Gaba,I-org
ADDRESS:,I-org
"21/37,",I-org
West,I-org
Patel,I-org
"Nagar,",I-org
New,I-org
Delhi,I-org
-,I-org
110008,B-tim
CONTACT,I-tim
NO.:,I-tim
8800418237,I-tim
ISSUE:,I-tim
I,O
have,O
been,O
facing,O
shortage,O
of,O
freshwater,O
supply,O
for,O
last,O
7,B-tim
days,O
at,O
times,O
of,O
Covid-19,B-geo
and,O
the,O
issue,O
has,O
not,O
been,O
resolved,O
even,O
