@CMODelhi,O
sir,O
4,O
covid+,O
patients,O
are,O
at,O
E-21,B-org
1st,O
flr,O
shivaji,B-geo
road,I-geo
adarsh,I-geo
nagar,I-geo
ext.,O
Delhi-110033,O
in,O
North,B-geo
distt.,O
Contact,O
detail,O
ashok,O
singhal,O
mob.09899804043.i,O
have,O
informed,O
@PawanSharma_AAP@SatyendarJain,O
many,O
times,O
but,O
no,O
response,O
recd,O
yet.,O
Sir,O
pls,O
do,O
smting.,O
PPHF,B-org
and,I-org
Wipro,I-org
Foundation,I-org
partnered,O
with,O
Honourable,B-org
MLA,I-org
Pawan,I-org
Kumar,I-org
"Sharma,",I-org
Adarsh,B-geo
nagar,I-geo
"Constituency,",I-org
N.C.T,B-geo
of,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
to,O
fight,O
COVID,O
19,O
by,O
installing,O
10-foot,O
operated,O
hand,O
washing,O
stations,O
in,O
his,O
constituency.,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@PIB_India,O
@PMOIndia,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
#COVID2019indiapic.twitter.com/pxAFpBkGN1,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
pls,O
help,O
person,O
with,O
covid,O
symptoms,O
but,O
nobody,O
coming,O
for,O
help.,O
Health,O
deteriorating,O
day,O
by,O
day.,O
Pls,O
help,O
Patient,O
Name,B-per
Kiran,I-per
Verma,I-per
52,O
yrs,O
Address-c,O
80,O
gali,O
no6,O
majlis,O
park,O
adarsh,B-geo
nagar,I-geo
delhi,O
33,B-tim
Mobile-9818665158,I-tim
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Hon.,B-org
"CM,",I-org
Delhi,B-geo
I'm,O
a,O
resident,O
of,O
Adarsh,B-geo
"Nagar,",I-geo
NW,I-geo
"District,",I-org
Delhi.,I-geo
Currently,O
there,O
are,O
46,O
COVID-19,O
+,O
cases,O
here,O
with,O
multiple,O
deaths,O
as,O
per,O
Aarogya,B-per
Setu,I-per
app,O
on,O
30/04/2020.,O
Still,O
my,O
area,O
hasn't,O
been,O
sealed,O
yet,O
&,O
no,O
testing,O
is,O
taking,O
place,O
Kindly,O
look,O
into,O
this,O
pic.twitter.com/pHqainDeGc,O
A,O
month,O
into,O
"lockdown,",O
two,O
more,O
zones,O
were,O
added,O
to,O
the,O
list,O
-,O
areas,O
from,O
Kotla,B-geo
Mubarakpur,I-geo
and,O
two,O
streets,O
from,O
Majlis,B-geo
Park,I-geo
in,O
Adarsh,B-geo
Nagar.,I-geo
Delhi’s,O
Covid-19,O
containment,O
zones,O
near,O
100-mark.,O
Complete,O
list,O
of,O
97,O
zones,O
here,O
https://www.hindustantimes.com/india-news/delhi-s-covid-19-containment-zones-near-100-mark-complete-list-of-97-zones-here/story-v0RPKaYGH5abrkUOUj23oO.html,O
…,O
@PawanSharma_AAP,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@drharshvardhan,O
This,O
is,O
to,O
bring,O
in,O
your,O
urgent,O
attention,O
that,O
6,O
days,O
before,O
a,O
covid,O
-19,O
#NAME?,O
case,O
was,O
traced,O
from,O
A-30,B-org
Panchwati,I-org
Adarsh,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
-110033,O
",Today",B-tim
1,I-tim
more,I-tim
#NAME?,O
case,O
from,O
the,O
same,O
household.,O
Kindly,O
seal,O
the,O
premises,O
to,O
stop,O
the,O
spread,O
Operation,O
of,O
freight,O
trains,O
is,O
continuing,O
while,O
passenger,O
train,O
services,O
are,O
suspended,O
in,O
wake,O
of,O
COVID-19.,O
Operating,O
staff,O
on,O
"duty,",O
are,O
wearing,O
mask,O
and,O
maintaining,O
social,O
"distancing,",O
at,O
Adarsh,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
railway,I-geo
station,I-geo
of,B-org
Delhi,I-geo
Division.,I-org
@RailMinIndia,O
@RailwayNorthernpic.twitter.com/IU1IZJCZra,O
Operation,O
of,O
freight,O
trains,O
is,O
continuing,O
while,O
passenger,O
train,O
services,O
are,O
suspended,O
in,O
wake,O
of,O
COVID-19.,O
Operating,O
staff,O
on,O
"duty,",O
are,O
wearing,O
mask,O
and,O
maintaining,O
social,O
"distancing,",O
at,O
Adarsh,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
railway,I-geo
station,I-geo
of,B-org
Delhi,I-geo
Division.,I-org
@RailMinIndia,O
@RailwayNorthernpic.twitter.com/xiqhclAHOb,O
Operation,O
of,O
freight,O
trains,O
is,O
continuing,O
while,O
passenger,O
train,O
services,O
are,O
suspended,O
in,O
wake,O
of,O
COVID-19.,O
Operating,O
staff,O
on,O
"duty,",O
are,O
wearing,O
mask,O
and,O
maintaining,O
social,O
"distancing,",O
at,O
Adarsh,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
station,I-geo
of,B-org
Delhi,B-org
Division.,I-org
@RailMinIndia,O
@RailwayNorthernpic.twitter.com/fGExurLSmm,O
Operation,O
of,O
freight,O
trains,O
is,O
continuing,O
while,O
passenger,O
train,O
services,O
are,O
suspended,O
in,O
wake,O
of,O
COVID-19.,O
Operating,O
staff,O
on,O
"duty,",O
are,O
wearing,O
mask,O
and,O
maintaining,O
social,O
"distancing,",O
at,O
Adarsh,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
station,O
of,B-org
Delhi,I-geo
Division.,I-org
@RailMinIndia,O
@RailwayNorthernpic.twitter.com/8FkVUGMx8A,O
Operation,O
of,O
freight,O
trains,O
is,O
continuing,O
while,O
passenger,O
train,O
services,O
are,O
suspended,O
in,O
wake,O
of,O
COVID-19.,B-org
Station,I-geo
Master,I-org
on,O
duty,O
at,O
Adarsh,B-geo
Nagar,I-geo
railway,O
station,O
of,B-org
Delhi,I-geo
Division,I-org
wearing,O
mask,O
and,O
maintaining,O
social,O
distancing.,O
pic.twitter.com/ejaR1jL709,O
#AMIT,O
SHAH,O
Nein,I-org
LNJP,B-geo
Hospital,I-geo
Ka,I-org
Daura,I-org
Kiya.,I-org
Achha,I-org
Hota,I-org
Ki,I-org
AMIT,I-org
SHAH,I-org
MCD,I-org
HOSPITALs-,O
AIIMS-,B-art
RML,I-art
Etc.,I-art
KA,I-art
Dora,I-art
Bhi,I-art
Karte.,I-art
DELHI,I-art
Mein,I-art
Hi,I-art
NEHIN,I-art
SAMASAT,I-art
BHARAT,I-art
Mein,I-art
#Covid_19,I-art
India,B-geo
Cases,I-art
Ki,I-art
Buri,I-art
Haalat,I-art
Hai.,I-art
Jiska,I-art
Jimma,I-art
Rajyon,I-art
Ke,I-art
Saath,I-art
KENDAR,I-art
SARKAR,I-art
Ka,I-art
Bhi,I-art
"Hai,",I-art
Jismein,I-art
SARKAR,I-art
Nakam,I-art
Rehi,I-art
New,B-geo
Delhi:,I-geo
AIIMS,I-geo
sets,O
up,O
24x7,O
COVID-19,O
helpline,O
number,O
https://www.dnaindia.com/india/report-new-delhi-aiims-sets-up-24x7-covid-19-helpline-number-2828036,O
…,O
You're,O
saying,O
Delhi's,O
healthcare,O
is,O
worse,O
than,O
other,O
states?,O
Is,O
that,O
why,O
all,O
MPs,O
and,O
big,O
politicians,O
come,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-geo
for,O
treatment?,O
Even,O
before,O
covid,O
there,O
were,O
long,O
lines,O
outside,O
OPD,B-org
of,I-org
Aiims,I-geo
of,O
people,O
from,O
all,O
over,O
the,O
"country,",O
especially,O
"UP,",O
"BIHAR,",B-geo
HARYANA,B-geo
AND,I-org
RAJASTHAN.,I-geo
Delhi,B-per
Govt,I-per
must,O
take,O
over,O
gangaram,O
hospital,O
mgmt,O
&,O
convert,O
it,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-geo
2,I-org
@LtGovDelhi,I-org
Sack,I-org
all,O
criminal,O
billing,O
section,O
fr,O
fleecing,O
Patients.,O
11,O
lacks,O
from,O
covid,O
PATIENT,O
&,O
killed,O
the,O
person,O
@drharshvardhan,O
@AmitShah,B-org
@BJP4Delhi,I-org
@ABVPDelhi,I-org
Fix,I-org
PVT,I-org
billing,O
charges,O
Amit,B-per
Shah,I-per
is,O
visiting,O
Delhi,B-geo
Govt,I-org
Hospital,I-geo
to,O
review,O
preparedness,O
to,O
handle,O
Covid,O
care.....Good.....Hope,O
he,O
will,O
also,O
visit,O
"AIIMS,",B-geo
Safdarjung,I-geo
&,I-org
RML,I-geo
",",O
other,O
central,O
govt,O
run,O
hospitals,O
&,B-org
MCD,I-org
hospitals,O
too,O
......,O
#DelhiFightsCorona,O
Delhi:,B-per
Dial,I-per
to,O
get,O
three,O
choices!,O
AIIMS,O
sets,O
up,O
24×7,O
COVID-19,O
helpline,O
number;,O
details,O
https://newseverything.in/lifestyle/delhi-dial-to-get-three-decisions-aiims-units-up-24x7-covid-19-helpline-quantity-particulars/,O
…,O
NEW,O
:,O
20,O
healthcare,O
workers,O
of,O
"AIIMS,",B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
test,O
positive,O
for,O
Corona,O
Virus,O
in,O
24,O
hours.,O
Total,O
624,O
healthcare,O
workers,O
of,O
AIIMS,B-geo
have,O
been,O
tested,O
positive,O
so,O
far.,O
131,O
of,O
them,O
are,O
under,O
treatment,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-geo
Jhajjar,I-org
Campus.,I-org
#COVID19,I-org
#Covid_19https://twitter.com/drasmalhi/status/1272446073022251008,O
…,O
NEW,O
:,O
20,O
healthcare,O
workers,O
of,O
"AIIMS,",B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
test,O
positive,O
for,O
Corona,B-geo
Virus,I-geo
in,O
24,O
hours.,O
Total,O
624,O
healthcare,O
workers,O
of,O
AIIMS,B-geo
have,O
been,O
tested,O
positive,O
so,O
far.,O
131,O
of,O
them,O
are,O
under,O
treatment,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-geo
Jhajjar,I-org
Campus.,I-org
#COVID19,I-org
#Covid_19,I-org
NEW,O
:,O
20,O
healthcare,O
workers,O
of,O
"AIIMS,",B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
test,O
positive,O
for,O
Corona,B-geo
Virus,I-geo
in,O
24,O
hours.,O
Total,O
624,O
healthcare,O
workers,O
of,O
AIIMS,B-geo
have,O
been,O
tested,O
positive,O
so,O
far.,O
131,O
of,O
them,O
are,O
under,O
treatment,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-geo
Jhajjar,I-geo
Campus.,I-geo
#COVID19,I-org
#Covid_19,I-org
AIIMS,B-geo
Sets,O
Up,O
24×7,O
#COVID__19,B-org
Helpline,I-org
Number,I-org
To,I-org
Guide,I-org
Medicos,I-org
At,I-org
Delhi,B-geo
Hospitals,I-geo
Sourced,I-org
from:,O
@ETHealthWorld,O
#COVID19Helpline,O
#AIIMS,O
pic.twitter.com/RRoFj7XkbS,O
New,B-geo
Delhi:,I-geo
AIIMS,I-geo
sets,O
up,O
24x7,O
COVID-19,O
helpline,O
number,O
https://ift.tt/2zBASLY,O
#delhi,O
#newdelhi,O
[,O
Best,O
#Maths,O
#Tutor,O
for,O
Home,B-org
#Tuition,I-org
in,O
#Delhi.,B-geo
Call,I-org
Now,O
9582317419,O
],O
Joint,O
health,O
team,O
to,O
visit,O
Delhi,B-per
Covid,I-per
hosps,O
https://ift.tt/2ACGSnY,O
A,O
joint,O
team,O
of,O
doctors,O
from,O
Central,O
health,O
"department,",O
Delhi,B-geo
"government,",O
All,O
Indian,B-gpe
Institute,B-geo
of,I-org
Medical,I-geo
Sciences,I-org
(AIIMS),I-geo
and,O
three,O
muni…,O
pic.twitter.com/LNM5Vq7CdH,O
In,O
an,O
endeavour,O
to,O
provide,O
experts’,O
advice,O
to,O
medicos,O
involved,O
in,O
tacking,O
#COVID19,O
patients,O
at,O
minor,O
hospitals,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
and,O
small,O
cities,O
across,O
the,O
"country,",O
the,O
All,O
India,B-geo
Institute,I-org
of,I-org
Medical,I-org
Sciences,I-org
(#AIIMS),I-geo
has,O
set,O
up,O
a,O
24X7,B-org
COVID-19,I-org
helpline,O
number.,O
https://bit.ly/2zwxnpV,O
pic.twitter.com/UDXULo5yPb,O
COVID-19,O
tests,O
to,O
be,O
tripled,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
in,O
next,O
six,O
"days,",O
says,O
Amit,B-per
Shah,I-per
https://nationnext.in/covid-19-tests-to-be-tripled-in-delhi-in-next-six-days-says-amit-shah/?fbclid=IwAR0JVInGakTUHbe8p0Wo_zv89uBEK3RLMQN7_No3GdE9iGlj8fa7PvDUzyo,O
…,O
#Covid19,O
#NationNext,O
#India,B-geo
#CoronavirusInIndia,O
#IndiaNextMedia,O
#Lockdown,O
#AmitShah,O
#NewDelhi,O
#CMKejriwal,O
#CoronavirusTesting,O
#AIIMS,O
#AmitShah,O
after,O
3.5,B-tim
months,O
have,O
called,O
a,O
meeting,O
to,O
discuss,O
how,O
to,O
curb,O
the,O
COVID-19.,B-org
This,O
is,O
after,O
all,O
the,O
"lockdowns,",O
virtual,O
"rallies,",O
poaching,O
MLAs.,O
Finally,O
he,O
has,O
given,O
a,O
thought,O
on,O
"""discussing"".",O
No,O
one,O
will,O
forget,O
that,O
AIIMS,O
only,O
admitted,O
VIPs.,O
#ArvindKejriwal,O
#Delhi,B-per
#COVID,I-per
https://twitter.com/dna/status/1272370270716731392,O
…,O
AIIMS,O
validated,O
an,O
antigen,O
based,O
COVID,O
-,O
19,O
kit.,O
Sensitivity,O
84,O
Specificity,O
100,O
Result,O
in,O
15,O
min.,O
Now,O
approved,O
by,O
ICMR,B-geo
and,O
DGHS,B-org
Sample,I-org
:,O
swab,O
Cost,O
per,O
test,O
<,O
500,O
rs.,O
Covid,O
19,O
rapid,O
antigen,O
kit,O
has,O
been,O
launched,O
in,O
the,O
country.,O
Delhi,B-geo
to,O
start,O
testing,O
SOON,O
@ANI,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
Covid-19,B-org
News:,I-org
Does,I-org
India,B-geo
Need,I-org
Another,I-org
Lockdown?,I-org
What,I-org
Delhi,B-geo
AIIMS,I-geo
Director,I-org
Say(Source:,I-org
NDTV),I-org
click,O
here,O
-->,O
http://tinyurl.com/yczmxdr4,O
Thank,O
you,O
@ICCR_Delhi,B-eve
Dean,I-eve
"Amarjeeva,",I-eve
@VMBJP,I-eve
"sir,",O
"@aiims_newdelhi,",O
"@PMOIndia,",O
@Delhiuniversit,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@DusuForeign,O
always,O
there,O
to,O
help,O
you.,O
#coronavirus,O
#COVID__19,O
#ThankYou,O
#help,O
#safety,O
#StayHomehttps://twitter.com/DusuForeign/status/1272219165349249024,O
…,O
AIIMS,O
sets,O
up,O
24×7,O
COVID-19,O
helpline,O
amid,O
rise,O
in,O
coronavirus,O
infections,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
|,O
India,B-org
News,I-org
http://dinowap.in/aiims-sets-up-24x7-covid-19-helpline-amid-rise-in-coronavirus-infections-in-delhi-india-news/,O
…,O
As,O
per,O
HM,O
Amit,O
Shah’s,O
"directions,",O
Union,O
health,O
ministry,O
sets,O
up,O
3,O
teams,O
of,O
4,O
doctors,O
each,O
from,O
AIIMS,B-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
"DGHS,",I-org
Union,I-org
health,I-org
ministry,I-org
&,I-org
Delhi,I-geo
govt.,O
Assisted,O
by,O
officers;,O
teams,O
to,O
inspect,O
major,O
dedicated,O
CoVid-19,O
facilities,O
proposed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
&,O
make,O
recommendations,O
4,O
improvement,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@ZeeNews,O
@RajatSharmaLive,O
@AajtkL,O
@indiatvnews,O
@LtGovDelhi,O
@DSGMCDelhi,O
@VHPDigital,O
@BJP4Delhi,O
@PMOIndia,O
@drharshvardhan,O
@SCofIndia,O
@highcourtdelhi,O
#,O
WHY,O
we,O
are,O
not,O
using,O
temple,O
empty,O
space,O
for,O
COVID-19.,B-org
Chhatrapur,B-geo
"Mandir,",I-geo
"Akshardham,",B-geo
"Shanidham,",B-geo
big,O
place,O
in,O
delhi,O
Fly,O
past,O
over,O
Akshardham,B-geo
and,O
Mayur,B-geo
Vihar,I-geo
areas,O
of,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
by,O
C130,B-org
to,O
express,O
gratitude,O
to,O
#COVID,O
warriors,O
#Delhi,B-per
pic.twitter.com/JfuHrkswpc,O
These,O
days,O
we,O
bankers,O
are,O
geting,O
several,O
e,O
challans,O
for,O
over,O
speeding,O
specially,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-geo
Mandir,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
location.,O
Sir,I-org
in,O
this,O
covid,O
situation,O
we,O
try,O
to,O
spend,O
less,O
time,O
on,O
roads,O
and,O
hurry,O
to,O
reach,O
the,O
bank,O
"branch,",O
we,O
are,O
at,O
90,O
kmph,O
@nitin_gadkari,O
During,O
the,O
current,O
national,O
lockdown,O
to,O
limit,O
the,O
spread,O
of,O
the,O
coronavirus,O
(COVID-19),O
"pandemic,",O
Swaminarayan,B-per
Akshardham,I-per
in,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
is,O
providing,O
free,O
packaged,O
hot,O
meals,O
daily,O
to,O
the,O
needy,O
as,O
specified,O
by,O
the,O
local,O
government.,O
#Akshardham,B-per
@BAPSpic.twitter.com/qAUwFlwBjw,O
@BabitaPhogat,O
ji,O
don't,O
forget,O
that,O
no,O
Covid,O
19,O
test,O
was,O
done,O
of,O
labourers,O
who,O
gathered,O
in,O
Anand,B-geo
Vihar,I-geo
ISBT,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
?,O
Why,O
so,O
?,O
उनके,O
टेस्ट,O
से,O
राजनीतिक,O
लाभ,O
नहीं,O
मिलना,O
था,O
क्या,O
इसलिए,O
उनके,O
टेस्ट,O
नहीं,O
किए,O
गए?,O
Absolutely,O
TRUE,O
@iamDivyaKhosla,O
Also,O
as,O
Delhi,B-geo
CM,I-geo
where,O
were,O
you,O
Mr,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
when,O
1000s,B-org
Migrants,I-org
gathered,O
at,O
Anand,B-geo
Vihar,I-geo
ISBT.Why,O
you,O
didn't,O
go,O
to,O
them,O
&,O
convinced,O
them,O
to,O
stay.,O
Many,O
"lives,",O
ended,O
while,O
migrating,O
could,O
be,O
saved,O
by,O
you.,O
#COVID,O
#21daylockdown,O
#ChineseVirushttps://twitter.com/iamDivyaKhosla/status/1244563275041222657,O
…,O
Last,O
evening,O
saw,O
anand,B-geo
vihar,I-gep
ISBT,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
pics,O
where,O
lakhs,O
of,O
workers,O
were,O
stranded,O
violating,O
"lockdown,",O
ignoring,O
criticality,O
of,O
"COVID,",B-org
few,O
"says,",O
"""virus",O
se,O
to,O
bach,O
jayengy,O
but,O
bhukh,O
se,O
pehle,O
mar,O
"jayengy"",",O
govt,O
says,O
dnt,O
"panic,",O
but,O
instant,O
21day,O
lockdown,O
is,O
also,O
a,O
panic,O
mind,O
decision,O
Huge,O
crowd,O
at,O
anand,O
vihar,O
isbt,O
Full,B-org
Video,I-org
Watch,I-org
here,O
https://youtu.be/dhq1JAQfvx8,O
#PMReliefFund,O
#PMOfIndia,O
#pmcares,O
#AkshayKumar,O
#Covid_19,O
#COVID2019italia,O
#covid2019india,O
#shameonbcci,O
#Delhi,B-per
hi,I-per
#anandvihar,O
This,O
is,O
so,O
heartbreaking!,O
Nothing,O
less,O
than,O
a,O
catastrophe,O
in,O
waiting,O
at,O
Anand,B-geo
Vihar,I-geo
ISBT,I-geo
in,O
#Delhi.,O
The,O
govt,O
needs,O
to,O
address,O
this,O
issue,O
of,O
migrant,O
workers,O
instead,O
of,O
urging,O
all,O
to,O
watch,O
Ramayana,B-org
&,I-org
Mahabharata,I-org
at,O
home.,O
#गरीब_की_पुकार_सुनो_सरकार,O
#Covid_19indiapic.twitter.com/OcuuE3vLor,O
Sir,O
please,O
watch,O
out,O
",",O
current,O
condition,O
of,O
Anand,B-geo
vihar,O
ISBT,O
",",O
Delhi,B-geo
.,O
This,O
much,O
crowd,O
",",O
if,O
in,O
worst,O
worst,O
case,O
single,O
person,O
is,O
infected,O
with,O
COVID_19,B-org
",",O
then,O
Sir,B-per
",",O
results,O
will,O
ruin,O
many,O
things.,O
Huge,O
crowd,O
at,O
anand,O
vihar,O
isbt,O
Watch,O
here,O
https://youtu.be/dhq1JAQfvx8,O
#PMReliefFund,O
#PMOfIndia,O
#pmcares,O
#AkshayKumar,O
#Covid_19,O
#COVID2019italia,O
#covid2019india,O
#shameonbcci,O
#Delhi,B-per
#anandvihar,I-per
#COVID2019india,O
This,O
picture,O
is,O
from,O
Anand,B-geo
Vihar,I-geo
ISBT,I-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi..,I-geo
Is,I-org
this,O
a,O
Social,O
distancing..?,O
This,O
is,O
called,O
complete,O
lockdown..,O
#Dailywagers,O
suffer,O
more,O
in,O
that,O
@PMOIndia,O
and,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Please,O
Do,O
something,O
sir,O
and,O
stop,O
this,O
crowd,O
to,O
stop,O
covid,O
community,O
spread,O
pic.twitter.com/V51teofbYI,O
If,O
you,O
"can,",O
read,O
the,O
Book,B-art
Life,I-art
after,O
Death,O
by,O
Swami,B-per
"Abhedananda,",I-per
it's,O
about,O
"Planchette,",O
you,O
will,O
get,O
it,O
in,O
any,O
Ramkrishna,B-geo
Ashram,I-geo
book,I-org
"store,",I-org
Delhi,I-geo
it's,O
near,O
Ramkrishna,B-geo
Ashram,I-geo
Metro,I-geo
station,O
near,O
Karol,B-geo
Bagh.,I-geo
Very,I-org
in-depth,O
analysis,O
Do,O
kaudi,O
ke,O
kavi....tum,O
CM,O
hote,O
to,O
kya,O
karte....Covid,O
patients,O
ko,O
Banglore,O
se,O
Delhi,B-geo
lake,O
treatment,O
dete???,O
Tum,O
woh,O
Oont,O
ho,O
pahad,O
dekhke,O
hin,O
heenana,O
jante,O
ho....,O
Waise,O
bhi,O
tumko,O
Anna,B-geo
ke,O
saath,O
nagpur,O
ashram,O
mein,O
hona,O
chahiye.,O
Khulle,B-geo
mein,O
mat,O
ghoomo...,O
@RailMinIndia,O
Train,O
number,O
2915,O
Ashram,O
covid,O
special,O
Ahemdabad,B-geo
to,O
delhi,B-geo
Coach,I-geo
number,O
D2,B-org
SEAT,O
NUMBER,O
29,O
_PNR-8731529859,B-org
Sir,I-org
mera,O
headphone,O
me,O
coach,O
d2,O
Seat,O
number,O
29,O
k,O
uper,O
wali,O
seat,O
par,O
bhool,O
gya,O
"hu,",O
JBL,O
black,O
colour,O
headphone,O
Please,O
help,O
me,O
mobile,O
number,O
9782150302,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
ek,O
bande,O
ko,O
Corona,B-geo
hua,O
usko,O
blood,O
vomiting,O
ho,O
rhi,O
hai.,O
Uski,B-geo
family,O
also,O
covid,O
positive.,O
Hospital,O
mai,O
jagah,O
nhi,O
hai.,O
6,O
crpf,O
log,O
bhi,O
uss,O
ashram,O
mai,O
positive,O
hai.,O
Ram,B-art
babu,O
ko,O
hua,O
corona,O
Sawan,O
ashram,O
",",O
Shakti,B-geo
nagar,I-geo
delhi-,O
7,O
If,O
u,O
can,O
help,O
.,O
Vision,O
2026,O
team,O
distributed,O
1150,O
ration,O
kits,O
at,O
"Jasola,",B-geo
"Ashram,",I-geo
Trilokpuri,I-geo
"R,",I-org
Turkman,O
"Gate,",O
Jama,B-geo
Masjid,I-geo
If,O
"introduced,",O
"Mehrauli,",B-geo
Kalu,B-geo
Sarai,I-geo
and,I-org
"Okhla,",B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
to,O
the,O
needy.,O
#MondayMotivaton,O
#MondayVibes,O
#lockdown4guidelines,O
#COVID,O
#Ramadanpic.twitter.com/M1cE93QMPt,O
Subject:,O
A,O
Special,O
Diet,O
is,O
Panacea,B-geo
for,O
COVID-19,B-org
which,O
works,O
as,O
a,O
vaccination,O
for,O
patients.,O
https://www.facebook.com/groups/628680207976051/permalink/651525865691485/,O
…,O
Astro,B-org
Sunil,I-org
Garg,I-org
(Nail,I-org
&,I-org
Teeth),I-org
7982311549,B-tim
9911020152,I-tim
9811332914,I-tim
https://youtu.be/fn5ft2tmq_Q,O
"1/1,Panchkuian",B-geo
"Road,",I-geo
RK,B-geo
Ashram,I-geo
Marg,I-geo
metro,O
"station,",O
New,B-geo
Delhi-110001,I-geo
COVID-19:,B-org
Radha,I-geo
Soami,I-geo
Satsang,I-geo
Beas,I-geo
Ashram,I-geo
provides,O
relief,O
to,O
migrant,O
workers,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
https://www.devdiscourse.com/article/headlines/1020780-covid-19-radha-soami-satsang-beas-ashram-provides-relief-to-migrant-workers-in-delhi,O
…,O
Delhi,B-per
ke,O
Ashram,O
(,O
sunlight,O
colony,O
2,O
),O
main,O
paya,O
gya,O
ek,O
Covid-19,O
ka,O
marij,O
pic.twitter.com/t8CiQRHrwQ,O
–,O
at,O
Sunlight,O
colony,O
-,O
II,B-eve
Kishan,B-per
Reddy,I-per
ji,I-per
has,O
been,O
really,O
spending,O
more,O
time,O
on,O
ground,O
to,O
really,O
manage,O
law,O
and,O
order,O
especially,O
during,O
covid,O
crises.,O
His,O
recent,O
visit,O
to,O
Azadpur,B-geo
Mandi,I-geo
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
surprised,O
and,O
motivated,O
me,O
to,O
support,O
farmers,O
24*7.,O
Praying,O
God,O
to,O
shower,O
our,O
best,O
wishes,O
and,O
blessings,O
on,O
him,O
Delhi,B-per
is,O
much,O
wealthier,O
than,O
Gurgaon/,B-per
Noida,I-per
but,O
the,O
health,O
infra,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
has,O
crippled.,O
Govt,O
failed,O
to,O
spread,O
the,O
COVID.,O
All,O
cases,O
of,O
Gurgaon,B-geo
has,O
Origin,B-org
of,I-org
Azadpur,B-geo
anaz,O
mandi,O
and,O
TBJ,B-org
@abcjain28,O
@aajtak,O
@AmitShah,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Today,B-tim
news,O
doing,O
round,O
about,O
Labour,O
paying,O
2500+,O
to,O
truck,O
man,O
@Azadpur,B-geo
mandi,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
to,O
go,O
to,O
their,O
native,O
places.,O
If,O
they,O
have,O
money,O
then,O
why,O
they,O
have,O
to,O
travel,O
inspite,O
of,O
getting,O
facilities,O
by,O
the,O
government.,O
Is,O
it,O
to,O
increase,O
COVID,B-org
COVID-19:,O
दिल्ली,O
के,O
आजादपुर,O
से,O
आए,O
मरीजों,O
ने,O
पूर्णिया,O
को,O
बनाया,O
कोरोना,O
हॉट,O
स्पॉट,O
COVID-19,B-org
Patients,I-org
from,O
Azadpur,B-geo
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
made,O
Purnia,B-geo
a,O
Corona,B-geo
hot,O
spot,O
brskp,O
BRVJ,O
|,O
purnia,O
–,O
News,O
in,O
Hindi,B-geo
https://newsattend.com/covid-19-%e0%a4%a6%e0%a4%bf%e0%a4%b2%e0%a5%8d%e0%a4%b2%e0%a5%80-%e0%a4%95%e0%a5%87-%e0%a4%86%e0%a4%9c%e0%a4%be%e0%a4%a6%e0%a4%aa%e0%a5%81%e0%a4%b0-%e0%a4%b8%e0%a5%87-%e0%a4%86%e0%a4%8f-%e0%a4%ae/,O
…,O
Migrant,O
labour,O
is,O
not,O
spreading,O
",",O
it's,O
Dharavi,B-per
in,O
Mumbai,B-geo
",",O
azadpur,O
in,O
delhi,B-geo
.,O
Local,O
people,O
are,O
responsible,O
for,O
spread,O
of,O
covid.,O
pic.twitter.com/dvyCzgUzCa,O
Don't,O
know,O
if,O
we,O
have,O
"noticed,",O
the,O
fruits,O
and,O
vegetables,O
markets,O
are,O
becoming,O
new,O
hotspots.Azadpur,O
"Mandi-Delhi,",B-per
Khandsa,I-per
"mandi-Gurgaon,",O
Koyambedu-Chennai,B-geo
are,O
just,O
to,O
name,O
a,O
few.,O
Govts,O
and,O
healthcare,O
authorities,O
please,O
take,O
a,O
note,O
@cmohry,O
@CMODelhi,O
.,O
"Together,we",O
can,O
beat,O
covid,O
Hmmm,B-per
got,O
confirmed,O
in,O
a,O
news,O
channel,O
about,O
it.,O
22,O
members,O
of,O
hos,O
near,O
&,O
dears,O
are,O
quarantined.,O
He,O
got,O
infected,O
from,O
Delhi,B-geo
Azadpur,I-geo
Sabji,I-geo
Mandi.,I-geo
He,O
is,O
a,O
driver,O
from,O
Chawadi,B-geo
village,O
in,O
Rewari,B-geo
district.,O
#COVIDー19,O
#Covid_19https://twitter.com/mrana9920/status/1257643860785688577,O
…,O
With,O
at,O
least,O
15,O
Covid,O
cases,O
in,O
Azadpur,B-geo
"Mandi,",I-geo
Asia's,O
largest,O
wholesale,O
market,O
may,O
become,O
Delhi's,O
next,O
hotspot.,O
Traders,O
fear,O
losing,O
their,O
lives,O
&,O
livelihood,O
as,O
shops,O
are,O
sealed,O
&,O
only,O
limited,O
trucks,O
are,O
allowed,O
in.,O
https://youtu.be/AjOffPTT4_s,O
With,O
at,O
least,O
15,O
Covid,O
cases,O
in,O
Azadpur,B-geo
"Mandi,",I-geo
Asia's,O
largest,O
wholesale,O
market,O
may,O
become,O
Delhi's,O
next,O
hotspot.,O
Traders,O
fear,O
losing,O
their,O
lives,O
&,O
livelihood,O
as,O
shops,O
are,O
sealed,O
&,O
only,O
limited,O
trucks,O
are,O
allowed,O
in.,O
@AshokGoelBJP,O
@RameshJonwal01,O
@devender1962pic.twitter.com/sZtdrrERcK,O
With,O
at,O
least,O
15,O
Covid,O
cases,O
in,O
Azadpur,B-geo
"Mandi,",I-geo
Asia's,O
largest,O
wholesale,O
market,O
may,O
become,O
Delhi's,O
next,O
hotspot.,O
Traders,O
fear,O
losing,O
their,O
lives,O
&,O
livelihood,O
as,O
shops,O
are,O
sealed,O
&,O
only,O
limited,O
trucks,O
are,O
allowed,O
in.,O
#COVID__19,O
@srivatsayb,O
@aayeff1https://youtu.be/AjOffPTT4_s,O
Two,O
medical,O
teams,O
deployed,O
at,O
Delhi&#39;s,O
Azadpur,B-geo
Mandi,I-geo
to,O
conduct,O
COVID-19,O
check-up,O
https://in.news.yahoo.com/two-medical-teams-deployed-delhis-azadpur-mandi-conduct-190304949.html,O
…,O
:Auto,B-geo
pickup,O
by,O
wikyou,O
With,O
at,O
least,O
15,O
Covid-19,O
cases,O
in,O
Azadpur,B-geo
"Mandi,",I-geo
Asia's,O
largest,O
wholesale,O
market,O
may,O
become,O
Delhi's,O
next,O
hotspot.,O
Traders,O
fear,O
losing,O
their,O
lives,O
&,O
livelihood।।।,O
ThePrint's,O
@sravastidasgupt2,O
reports,O
from,O
the,O
spot..,O
https://youtu.be/AjOffPTT4_s,O
With,O
at,O
least,O
15,O
Covid-19,O
cases,O
in,O
Azadpur,B-geo
"Mandi,",I-geo
Asia's,O
largest,O
wholesale,O
market,O
may,O
become,O
Delhi's,O
next,O
hotspot.,O
Traders,O
fear,O
losing,O
their,O
lives,O
&,O
livelihood,O
as,O
shops,O
are,O
sealed,O
&,O
only,O
limited,O
trucks,O
are,O
allowed,O
in.,O
ThePrint's,O
@sravastidasgupt2,O
reports,O
https://youtu.be/AjOffPTT4_s,O
&#039;What,B-org
Will,I-org
People,I-org
Eat?&#039;:,I-org
With,I-org
Increasing,I-org
Covid-19,I-org
"Cases,",I-org
Traders,I-org
at,O
Delhi&#039;s,O
Azadpur,B-per
Man...,I-per
https://csybuzz.live/india-trending-news/what-will-people-eat-with-increasing-covid-19-cases-traders-at-delhis-azadpur-mandi-battle-fears/?feed_id=88&_unique_id=5eacd47b4c39c,O
…,O
2,O
Doctors,O
Teams,B-org
Conduct,I-org
COVID-19,I-org
Testing,I-org
In,I-org
Delhi’s,I-geo
Azadpur,I-geo
Mandi,I-geo
https://pakkikhabar.in/2-doctors-teams-conduct-covid-19-testing-in-delhis-azadpur-mandi/,O
…,O
Vegetable,O
prices,O
could,O
rise,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
as,O
supply,O
to,O
Azadpur,B-geo
Mandi,I-geo
falls,O
amid,O
Covid,O
cases,O
ThePrint's,O
Samyak,B-per
Pandey,I-per
@Samyak_01,I-per
reportshttps://bit.ly/3d9pB3D,O
2,O
Doctors,O
Teams,B-org
Conduct,I-org
COVID-19,I-org
Testing,I-org
In,O
Delhi’s,O
Azadpur,B-per
Mandi:,I-per
आजादपुर,O
सब्जी,O
मंडी,O
से…,O
https://goo.gl/fb/As1xPc,O
Delhi:,B-per
Vehicles,I-per
queue,O
up,O
at,O
Badarpur-Faridabad,B-geo
border,O
as,O
Police,O
personnel,O
check,O
passes,O
and,O
IDs,O
of,O
"people,",O
commuting,O
through,O
the,O
route.,O
Haryana,B-geo
govt,O
has,O
sealed,O
borders,O
with,O
the,O
national,O
capital,O
in,O
wake,O
of,O
increasing,O
number,O
of,O
#COVID19,B-org
cases,O
#Covid_19pic.twitter.com/1WFjdHOoGd,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
"sir,",O
I,O
lost,O
my,O
Job,O
due,O
to,O
Covid,O
19,O
and,O
my,O
final,O
interview,O
is,O
schedule,O
in,O
another,O
company,O
on,O
7,O
jun,O
at,O
barakhambha,O
"road,",O
Delhi.,O
Currently,O
I,O
m,O
in,O
gurgaon,O
so,O
how,O
can,O
manage,O
if,O
border,O
are,O
sealed.,O
I,O
try,O
to,O
conveyance,O
them,O
for,O
video,O
calling,O
but,O
they,O
r,O
not,O
agree.,O
Pls,O
help,O
We,O
can,O
beat,O
COVID-19,B-org
Together,I-org
http://www.shikshamitraonline.co.in,I-org
Abroad,I-org
Education,I-org
Counselist,I-org
call,O
us,O
.,O
Call,B-org
Us:,I-org
-7290008713,I-org
Visit,I-org
Us:,I-org
"B-35,",I-org
Ansal,I-org
Chamber,I-org
"2,",I-org
Bhikaji,B-geo
Cama,I-geo
"Place,",I-geo
RK,B-geo
"Puram,",I-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
.,O
#ShikshaMitra,O
#MbbsInRussia,O
#MBBSAbroad,O
#MBBSCourse,O
#LifeInRussia,O
#StudyMBBSpic.twitter.com/j8ZuuaubhK,O
@dtptraffic,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@narendramodi,O
@nitin_gadkari,O
Receiving,O
this,O
from,O
Delhi,B-geo
traffic,O
police,O
At,O
the,O
time,O
of,O
"COVID-19,",B-org
Vehicle,I-org
No.,I-org
DL...,I-org
-32371354,O
found,O
VIOLATING,O
STOP,O
LINE,O
at,O
Bhikaji,B-geo
CAMA,B-org
"PLACE,",O
I,O
request,O
plz,O
don't,O
send,O
these,O
at,O
this,O
time,B-tim
later,I-tim
on,O
you,O
will,O
recover,O
it,O
Will,O
the,O
lockdown,O
be,O
enforced?....pics,O
of,O
Mohammadpur,B-geo
village,O
behind,O
bhikaji,B-geo
cama,I-geo
place,I-geo
new,I-geo
delhi,I-geo
110066,O
...its,O
like,O
a,O
party,O
going,O
on....filthy,O
resturants,O
operating,O
half,O
shuttered....,O
people,O
enjoying,O
on,O
streets....locals,O
sitting,O
on,O
parked,O
bikes,O
and,O
imparting,O
expertise,O
on,O
covid,O
https://twitter.com/DelhiPolice/status/1242352031928438785,O
…pic.twitter.com/ocrTZM8MNM,O
All,O
major,O
hospitals/clinics/nursing,O
homes,O
in,O
#Delhi,B-geo
to,O
display,O
availability,O
of,O
#COVID19,B-org
and,O
non,O
Covid,O
beds,O
on,O
large,O
LED,O
boards,O
at,O
entrance,O
along,O
with,O
charges,O
and,O
details,O
of,O
contact,O
persons,O
pic.twitter.com/WhZ7KyW5BO,O
#JustIn,O
A,O
#Covid_19,O
positive,O
patient,O
from,O
Central,B-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
who,O
was,O
neither,O
an,O
employee,O
of,O
the,O
President's,O
Secretariat,O
nor,O
a,O
resident,O
of,O
the,O
President's,B-geo
Estate,I-geo
expired,O
on,O
13.04.2020,O
with,O
co-morbidities,O
at,O
B,B-org
L,I-org
Kapoor,I-org
"Hospital,",I-org
New,B-geo
Delhi:,I-geo
ANI,I-org
quoting,O
Rashtrapati,B-geo
Bhavan,I-geo
sources,O
Live,O
Updates,O
|,O
A,O
COVID19,O
positive,O
patient,O
from,O
Central,B-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
who,O
was,O
neither,O
an,O
employee,O
of,O
the,O
President's,O
Secretariat,O
nor,O
a,O
resident,O
of,O
the,O
President's,B-geo
Estate,I-geo
expired...,O
Catch,O
all,O
the,O
live,O
updates,O
here:,O
https://bit.ly/2XSao2g,O
#Covid_19,O
#CoronavirusPandemic,O
Fatehpuri,B-geo
Masjid,I-geo
in,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
to,O
remain,O
closed,O
till,O
July,B-tim
4,I-tim
amid,O
COVID-19,O
"pandemic,",O
Shahi,B-per
Imam,I-per
Mufti,I-per
Mukarram,I-per
Ahmed,I-per
asks,O
devotees,O
to,O
pray,O
at,O
home.,O
#FatehpuriMasjid,O
#MuftiMukarramAhmed,O
#COVID19Pandemic,O
#ShahiImam,O
#MuslimDevotees,O
#ChandniChowk,O
https://www.latestly.com/india/news/fatehpuri-masjid-in-new-delhi-to-remain-closed-till-july-4-amid-covid-19-pandemic-shahi-imam-mufti-mukarram-ahmed-asks-devotees-to-pray-at-home-1818708.html,O
…,O
In,O
hotel,O
"industry,these",O
r,O
basics,O
&,O
are,O
followed,O
as,O
hygiene,O
from,O
decades.,O
Now,O
with,O
"covid,",O
I,O
am,O
sure,O
hotels,O
will,O
follow,O
sanitization,O
to,O
the,O
“T”.,B-org
U,I-org
would,O
agree,O
with,O
me,O
that,O
eating,O
in,O
a,O
restaurant,O
is,O
much,O
safer,O
than,O
eating,O
road,O
side,O
or,O
roaming,O
in,O
Chandni,B-geo
"Chowk,if",I-geo
atall,O
you,O
know,O
Delhi,B-geo
@ArvindKejriwal,O
",",O
sir,O
ye,O
adress,O
hai,O
(4760,O
jaipuria,O
building,O
jogi,O
wara,O
nai,O
sarak,O
chandni,B-geo
chowk,I-geo
delhi-,I-geo
6),O
yaha,O
covid,O
postive,O
patient,O
"hai,sir",O
helpline,O
pe,O
bhi,O
call,O
kiya,O
hai,O
but,O
abhi,O
koi,O
aaya,O
nhi,O
"hai,",O
is,O
building,O
me,O
bahut,O
families,O
rehti,O
hai.,O
Sir,B-org
DM,I-org
OFFICE,I-org
ke,O
report,O
bhi,O
isme,O
attach,O
hai,O
pic.twitter.com/a8umGt4fNY,O
@CPDelhi,O
@drharshvardhan,O
sir,O
ye,O
adress,O
hai,O
(4760,O
jaipuria,O
building,O
jogi,O
wara,O
nai,O
sarak,O
chandni,B-geo
chowk,I-geo
delhi,I-geo
-,I-tim
6,I-tim
),O
yaha,O
covid,O
postive,O
"hai,sir",O
helpline,O
pe,O
bhi,O
call,O
kiya,O
hai,O
but,O
abhi,O
koi,O
aaya,O
nhi,O
hai,O
is,O
building,O
me,O
bahut,O
families,O
rehti,O
hai.,O
Sir,B-org
DM,I-org
OFFICE,I-org
ke,O
report,O
bhi,O
isme,O
attach,O
hai,O
pic.twitter.com/4ti6GhZSHR,O
@MoHFW_INDIA.,O
sir,O
ye,O
adress,O
hai,O
(4760,O
jaipuria,O
building,O
jogi,O
wara,O
nai,O
sarak,O
chandni,B-geo
chowk,I-geo
delhi,I-geo
-,I-tim
6,I-tim
),O
yaha,O
covid,O
postive,O
patient,O
"hai,sir",O
helpline,O
pe,O
bhi,O
call,O
kiya,O
hai,O
but,O
abhi,O
koi,O
aaya,O
nhi,O
"hai,",O
is,O
building,O
me,O
bahut,O
families,O
rehti,O
hai.,O
Sir,B-org
DM,I-org
OFFICE,I-org
ke,O
report,O
bhi,O
isme,O
attach,O
hai,O
pic.twitter.com/KHItE33gT2,O
@drharshvardhan,O
sir,O
ye,O
adress,O
hai,O
(4760,O
jaipuria,O
building,O
jogi,O
wara,O
nai,O
sarak,O
chandni,B-geo
chowk,I-geo
delhi,I-geo
-,I-tim
6,I-tim
),O
yaha,O
covid,O
postive,O
patient,O
"hai,sir",O
helpline,O
pe,O
bhi,O
call,O
kiya,O
hai,O
but,O
abhi,O
koi,O
aaya,O
nhi,O
"hai,",O
is,O
building,O
me,O
bahut,O
families,O
rehti,O
hai.,O
Sir,B-org
DM,I-org
OFFICE,I-org
ke,O
report,O
bhi,O
isme,O
attach,O
hai,O
pic.twitter.com/8WrYVp71I7,O
Sir,O
pls.dont,O
open,O
commercial,O
markets,O
in,O
delhi(very,O
crowded,O
markets,O
in,O
walled,O
city,O
of,O
old,O
delhi)to,O
avoid,O
covid,O
19,O
spread.the,O
sanitary,O
and,O
garbage,O
conditions,O
of,O
area,O
is,O
bad.the,O
corporation,O
inspectors,O
is,O
very,O
careless,O
and,O
also,O
D.m,O
of,O
area,O
of,O
chandni,B-geo
chowk,I-geo
is,O
careless,O
about,O
his,O
job,O
pic.twitter.com/yyh1pDCtJS,O
Severely,O
COVID-19,O
affected,O
Delhi’s,O
Chandni,B-geo
Chowk,I-geo
to,O
remain,O
closed,O
till,O
31st,B-tim
May,I-tim
https://ift.tt/3by9Zp6,I-tim
#Delhi99,I-tim
@LtGovDelhi,O
Sir,O
",sir",O
"greetings,",O
I,O
have,O
my,O
work,O
office,O
in,O
Chandni,B-geo
"Chowk,",I-geo
in,O
view,O
of,O
the,O
way,O
covid,O
19,O
cases,O
are,O
increasing,O
in,O
"Delhi,",B-geo
increase,O
the,O
lockdown,O
to,O
30,O
"may,",O
if,O
alive,O
we,O
will,O
do,O
more.,O
Even,O
today,B-tim
there,O
are,O
472,O
cases,O
in,O
one,O
day.,O
Please,O
extend,O
the,O
lockdown,O
to,O
30,O
may.,O
Thanks।,O
SO,O
as,O
per,O
govt.,O
Data,O
1,O
km,O
from,O
my,O
area,O
there,O
are,O
5,O
cases,O
and,O
in,O
2,O
km,O
20+,O
cases,O
still,O
kejriwal,O
wants,O
delhi,B-geo
in,O
green,O
zone.,O
By,O
the,O
way,O
25,O
BSF,O
soldiers,O
posted,O
at,O
chandni,B-geo
chowk,I-geo
area,I-geo
are,O
now,O
COVID-19,O
+,O
and,O
No,O
1,O
knows,O
from,O
where,O
they,O
got,O
infected.,O
#KejriwalShowsTheWay,O
A,O
#deserted,O
view,O
of,O
a,O
closed,O
lord,O
Shani,B-geo
Dev,I-geo
Temple,I-geo
during,O
a,O
government-imposed,O
lockdown,O
as,O
a,O
preventive,O
measure,O
against,O
the,O
coronavirus,O
in,O
Chandni,B-geo
"Chowk,",I-geo
Old,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
on,O
Saturday,B-tim
ANI,B-per
Photo/Rahul,I-per
Singh,I-per
#COVID19Lockdown,O
#COVID,B-org
#Lockdown2,I-org
#lockdownindia,O
#PhotoOfTheDay,O
#photojournalismpic.twitter.com/ez2TiQ5wrb,O
Seriously,O
Iftaar,B-eve
shoppers,O
at,O
Chandni,B-geo
Chowk,I-geo
Delhi......and,O
here,O
we,O
are,O
working,O
hard,O
staying,O
Home,O
trying,O
to,O
break,O
the,O
#COVID,B-org
chain..Religion,O
is,O
the,O
bane,O
of,O
existence,O
pic.twitter.com/P5t28uKM3T,O
Delhi,B-geo
के,I-per
Chandni,I-geo
Chowk,I-geo
की,O
ये,O
तस्वीर,O
Lockdown,O
को,O
दिखा,O
रही,O
है,O
"ठेंगा,",O
आप,O
भी,O
देखिए,O
#Covid,B-org
#Lockdown,I-org
#Delhi,B-geo
#ChandniChowk,I-geo
#LockdownKoDikhayaThenga,O
#HilaDegiChandniChowkKiTasveer,O
#LockdownKiUdiDhajiya,O
http://youtube.com/watch?v=0ajRck_jS78&t=6s,O
…pic.twitter.com/fPfKZAMaHY,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@republic,O
if,O
COVID,B-org
cases,O
in,O
delhi,B-geo
rise,O
after,O
what,O
we,O
witnessed,O
in,O
chandni,B-geo
"chowk,",I-geo
an,O
FIR,B-org
must,O
be,O
filed,O
against,O
the,O
CM,B-org
of,O
Delhi.He,O
doesnt,O
have,O
the,O
guts,O
to,O
ask,O
ppl,O
of,O
a,O
particular,O
community,O
to,O
refrain.,O
Shame,O
on,O
AAP,B-org
&,O
its,O
govt.,B-org
#CantLetDownGuard,O
#District_Administration,O
inspecting,O
#Chandni_Chowk,B-geo
area.,O
#dmcentral,O
#Covid_19india,O
#StayAtHome,O
@HMOIndia,O
@PMOIndia,O
@GovtOfIndia_,O
@govt_delhi,O
@nidhi2959pic.twitter.com/c1gHAoNDq7,O
In,O
a,O
late-night,O
"operation,",O
#Delhi's,B-geo
district,O
administration,O
shifted,O
hundreds,O
of,O
homeless,O
daily,O
"wagers,",O
staying,O
on,O
the,O
streets,O
of,O
Chandni,B-geo
Chowk,I-geo
since,O
India's,O
"lockdown,",O
to,O
various,O
quarantine,O
facilities.,O
The,O
area,O
may,O
also,O
be,O
marked,O
as,O
a,O
#Covid_19,O
hotspot.https://www.newindianexpress.com/cities/delhi/2020/apr/17/daily-wagers-evicted-from-chandni-chowk-2131292.html,O
…,O
@PMOIndia,O
my,O
mama,O
lives,O
in,O
delhi,B-geo
vishnunath,O
bhargava,O
in,O
chawri,B-geo
bazar,I-geo
is,O
covid,O
19,O
positive,O
on,O
10,O
may,O
2020,O
There,O
are,O
3,O
other,O
family,O
members,O
who,O
are,O
not,O
well,O
and,O
has,O
high,O
fever.,O
There,O
is,O
no,O
test,O
conducted,O
of,O
other,O
family,O
member,O
Delhi’s,B-geo
10k-bed,O
facility,O
to,O
be,O
ready,O
by,O
"June-end,",O
Health,B-org
"News,",I-org
ET,I-org
"HealthWorld,",I-org
New,B-geo
Delhi:,I-geo
A,I-org
"10,000-bed",O
makeshift,O
facility,O
coming,O
up,O
at,O
Chhatarpur,B-geo
in,O
South,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
to,O
tackle,O
the,O
capital’s,O
surging,O
Covid-19,O
cases,O
will,O
...,O
",http://medicalnewser.com/delhis-10k-bed-facility-to-be-ready-by-june-end-health-news-et-healthworld.html",O
…pic.twitter.com/yyTOVa83o2,O
Delhi:,B-geo
Chhatarpur,I-geo
to,O
have,O
"10,000-bed",O
Covid-19,O
facility,O
https://www.indiatoday.in/mail-today/story/delhi-chhatarpur-to-have-10000-bed-covid19-facility-1689083-2020-06-15,O
…,O
#MailToday,O
A,O
"10,000-bed",O
makeshift,O
facility,O
coming,O
up,O
at,O
Chhatarpur,B-geo
in,O
South,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
to,O
tackle,O
the,O
capital’s,O
surging,O
Covid-19,O
cases,O
will,O
be,O
fully,O
operational,O
by,O
the,O
month-end.,O
https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/politics-and-nation/delhis-10k-bed-facility-to-be-ready-by-june-end/articleshow/76376185.cms?utm_source=contentofinterest&utm_medium=text&utm_campaign=cppst,O
…,O
Delhi:,B-geo
Chhatarpur,I-geo
to,O
have,O
"10,000-bed",O
Covid-19,O
facility,O
https://newsroof.website/2020/06/15/delhi-chhatarpur-to-have-10000-bed-covid-19-facility/,O
…,O
Will,O
power,O
is,O
mightier,O
than,O
COVID-19:,B-org
Tune,I-org
in,O
to,O
hear,O
Shri,B-org
Rohit,I-org
Rajbir,I-org
"Singh,",I-org
Addl.,I-org
"DCP,",I-org
"Najafgarh,",I-geo
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
narrate,O
his,O
personal,O
experience,O
of,O
getting,O
infected,O
and,O
coming,O
back,O
stronger,O
to,O
serve,O
the,O
nation,O
-,O
https://www.mygov.in/podcast/mygov-positive-stories-episode-103/,O
…,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
namaskar,O
our,O
dear,O
honorable,O
"CM,",O
I,O
want,O
to,O
give,O
a,O
suggestion,O
for,O
delhi,B-geo
covid,O
patient,O
the,O
government,O
have,O
to,O
take,O
over,O
the,O
radha,B-geo
sawmi,I-geo
satsang,I-geo
bhawan,I-geo
at,O
chhatarpur,B-geo
and,O
convert,O
it,O
into,O
covid,O
hospital,O
it,O
has,O
a,O
huge,O
area,O
so,O
all,O
the,O
covid,O
suffering,O
patients,O
can,O
stay.,O
Why,O
in,O
chhatarpur,B-geo
testing,O
of,O
covid-19,O
is,O
very,O
less,O
"?,",O
in,O
fact,O
minimum,O
in,O
sagar,O
"division,",O
even,O
till,O
now,O
5,O
shramic,O
trains,O
at,O
reached,O
chhatarpur,B-geo
",Today",B-tim
1,I-tim
#NAME?,O
case,O
comes,O
(whose,O
testing,O
is,O
done,O
in,O
delhi),O
",",O
why,O
district,O
officers,O
are,O
so,O
irresponsible,O
@collchhatarpur,O
@CMMadhyaPradesh,O
Sir,B-per
Iam,I-per
stuck,O
in,O
delhi,B-geo
with,O
my,O
children's,O
in,O
one,O
room,O
due,O
to,O
fear,O
of,O
covid,O
cant,O
go,O
out,O
being,O
more,O
than,O
month,O
no,O
job,O
and,O
loosing,O
money,O
I,O
want,O
to,O
go,O
back,O
to,O
my,O
home,O
in,O
Chhatarpur,B-geo
@PMOIndia,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
vulnerable,O
little,O
children,O
",",O
mass,O
exodus,O
migrant,O
workers,O
fear,O
Covid,B-per
",",O
terror,O
hunger,O
walking,O
cycling,O
Delhi,B-geo
to,O
Chhatarpur,B-geo
600,O
km,O
-,O
this,O
could,O
have,O
been,O
done,O
better,O
!,O
@save,O
@pragyavats,O
@SavetheChildren,O
Speak,O
up,O
!pic.twitter.com/QFierUKfxF,O
One,O
day,O
trip,O
to,O
Maldives,B-geo
is,O
more,O
cheaper,O
than,O
spending,O
a,O
day,O
in,O
Delhi,B-org
Max,I-org
Life,I-org
Hospital,I-org
for,I-org
COVID-19,I-org
patients.,O
Trust,O
"me,",O
medical,O
sector,O
is,O
becoming,O
a,O
business,O
in,O
our,O
country!!!,O
pic.twitter.com/J6An3ydS7F,O
Looking,O
at,O
"Covid-19,",B-geo
universities,O
like,O
Delhi,B-geo
and,O
chhattisgarh,B-geo
took,O
a,O
good,O
decision,O
by,O
promoting,O
1st,O
and,O
2nd,B-tim
year,O
students.,O
Gujarat,B-org
Universities,I-org
also,O
needs,O
to,O
learn,O
from,O
them.@nsui,O
@NSUIGujarat,O
#Save_Gujarat_Students,O
Glad,O
to,O
see,O
@Radhika_Khera,B-geo
give,O
back,O
to,O
the,O
news,O
anchors,O
in,O
the,O
same,O
currency,O
that,O
they,O
"deserve,",O
countering,O
their,O
RHETORICAL,O
WHATABOUTERY,O
with,O
FACTS,O
on,O
how,O
Maharashtra,B-geo
govt,O
is,O
handling,O
#COVID__19,O
with,O
INNOVATIVE,O
RESPONSIBILITY,O
&,O
not,O
running,O
away,O
from,O
the,O
situation,O
like,O
Delhi,B-geo
govt,O
@sardesairajdeep,O
@republic,O
to,O
all,O
dying,O
to,O
give,O
awards,O
for,O
best,O
performance,O
during,O
Covid,O
19,O
The,O
worst,O
affected,O
cities,O
are,O
"Mumbai,",B-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
"Thane,",I-geo
Ahmedabad,I-geo
and,O
Chennai,B-geo
which,O
alone,O
covers,O
50%,O
of,O
national,O
cases.,O
This,O
sums,O
up,O
all.,O
We,O
know,O
who,O
rules,O
which,O
state.,O
Just,O
like,O
Delhi,B-geo
did.,O
Don't,O
comorbities,O
deaths,O
into,O
the,O
covid,O
count.,O
Are,O
you,O
sure,O
it,O
is,O
avbl?,O
Give,O
clear,O
info,O
after,O
verifuing,O
pls.,O
Patient's,O
son,O
is,O
also,O
Covid-19,O
positive,O
and,O
cant,O
roam,O
all,O
over,O
the,O
city...,O
he,O
is,O
located,O
at,O
masjid,I-geo
moth,O
(Near,B-per
Chirag,I-per
Delhi),I-per
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
@AamAadmiParty,O
"""Open",B-org
Delhi,I-org
"Hotels""",I-org
and,O
make,O
them,O
ready,O
to,O
occupy,O
500000,O
#COVID19Pandemic,O
victims,O
in,O
#Covid_19india,B-geo
#Delhi,I-geo
Early,O
to,O
Act,O
is,O
better,O
than,O
late.,O
#aamaadmiparty,O
#ArvindKejriwal,O
#CoronavirusIndia,O
Hospitals,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
charging,O
a,O
bomb,O
for,O
Covid-19,B-geo
treatment,O
(Minimum,B-per
Cost,I-per
of,O
treatment,O
to,O
be,O
around,O
$4000).,O
How,O
will,O
someone,O
that,O
is,O
poor,O
and,O
not,O
insured,O
afford,O
this?,O
What,O
is,O
our,O
government,O
doing,O
about,O
it?,O
#coronaviruspic.twitter.com/vlHpF8tmdF,O
We,O
want,O
to,O
know,O
the,O
exactly,O
numbers,O
in,O
Chirag,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
and,O
Sheikh,B-geo
Sarai,I-geo
phase,O
2,O
Please,O
provide,O
us,O
some,O
mechanism,O
to,O
know,O
the,O
area,O
wish,O
cases.,O
As,O
people,O
are,O
not,O
coming,O
forward,O
and,O
disclosing,O
the,O
Covid,O
results,O
even,O
with,O
the,O
RWAs.,O
We,O
heard,O
different,O
numbers.,O
Please,O
clearify,O
this,O
Is,O
he,O
a,O
Delhi,B-geo
resident?,O
Fits,O
into,O
the,O
criteria,O
for,O
testing?,O
Are,O
there,O
enough,O
beds,O
for,O
the,O
CM?,B-org
Will,O
private,O
and,O
public,O
hospitals,O
turn,O
him,O
away?,O
Does,O
he,O
have,O
a,O
valid,O
ID,O
card?,O
Is,O
he,O
any,O
less,O
or,O
more,O
human,O
that,O
other,O
Covid-19,O
patients?,O
https://twitter.com/timesofindia/status/1269891613301657600,O
…,O
Delhi,B-geo
CM,I-per
Arvind,I-per
Kejriwal,I-per
"unwell,",O
to,O
be,O
tested,O
for,O
COVID-19,B-org
on,O
June,B-tim
9,I-tim
@moneycontrolcomhttps://www.moneycontrol.com/news/india/delhi-cm-arvind-kejriwal-to-be-tested-for-covid-19-on-june-9-5374111.html,O
…,O
@Saurabh_MLAgk,O
@DelhiPolice,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@DCPSouthDelhi,O
Found,O
4,O
persons,O
positive,O
in,O
826,B-tim
Chirag,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
&,O
the,O
house,O
owner,O
remove,O
the,O
COVID-19,B-org
Sticker,I-org
to,O
run,O
his,O
shop.,O
Kindly,O
look,O
into,O
it.,O
#COVIDUpdates,O
#HelpNotDeathpic.twitter.com/HpAi0Hp6ta,O
"""",O
Chirag,B-org
Tale,I-org
"Andhera""",I-org
Delhi,I-org
being,O
capital,O
of,O
India,B-geo
has,O
highest,O
number,O
of,O
containment,O
zones,O
where,O
the,O
relaxations,O
announced,O
by,O
Central,B-org
Government,I-org
will,O
not,O
apply.,O
Kejriwal,O
says,O
we,O
have,O
to,O
learn,O
to,O
live,O
with,O
COVID-19.Since,O
he,O
is,O
not,O
able,O
to,O
bring,O
down,O
spread,O
",this",O
statement.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@narendramodi,O
@DCPSouthDelhi,O
@DelhiPolice,O
Though,O
chirag,B-geo
delhi,I-geo
has,O
been,O
marked,O
as,O
red,O
zone,O
for,O
COVID-19,B-org
.I,I-org
am,O
living,O
in,O
chirag,B-geo
delhi,I-geo
and,O
movement,O
of,O
people,O
inside,O
the,O
village,O
premises,O
is,O
very,O
often.sir,O
please,O
depute,O
some,O
police,O
personnel,O
to,O
control,O
this,O
at,O
earliest,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@narendramodi,O
@DelhiPolice,O
.We,O
are,O
almost,O
in,O
the,O
third,O
stage,O
of,O
COVID-19,B-org
.but,O
people,O
are,O
not,O
taking,O
the,O
necessary,O
precautions,O
at,O
my,O
place(Chirag,O
delhi),O
falls,O
under,O
malviya,B-geo
nagar,I-geo
PS.People,O
are,O
roaming,O
on,O
without,O
any,O
fear,O
of,O
lockdown/COVID-19.,O
Please,O
do,O
needful,O
1-Feb,O
Sir,O
think,O
about,O
MIDDLE,O
CLASS,O
also.,O
In,O
"Delhi,",B-org
R4U,I-org
FASHION,I-org
AND,I-org
CLOTHING,I-org
company,O
(,O
Address,O
--,O
Regd,B-org
"Office,",I-org
"758,",I-org
Chirag,B-geo
"Dilli,",I-geo
New,I-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
110017),O
is,O
not,O
giving,O
salary,O
from,B-tim
2,I-tim
months,O
before,O
to,O
any,O
employee.,O
We,O
are,O
facing,O
hard,O
time,O
in,O
COVID-19,B-org
crisis.,O
Please,B-art
Help,I-art
Well,O
done.In,O
"Munirka,chirag",B-geo
delhi,I-geo
of,O
south,B-geo
delhi,I-geo
ppl,O
from,O
all,O
the,O
north-east,O
are,O
struggling,O
with,O
this,O
crisis.Come,O
on,O
one,O
step,O
for,O
them.,O
@AnilSharma4BJP,O
@rameshbidhuri,O
#RSSinAction,O
#RSSfightsCorona,O
#IndiaFightsCorona,O
#Covid_19https://twitter.com/friendsofrss/status/1246330010274869249,O
…,O
@cmohry,O
A,O
man,O
named,O
Sh.,B-per
Chirag,I-per
urf,O
Chilli,B-per
was,O
come,O
in,O
our,O
village,O
Pathera,B-org
District,I-org
"Mahindergarh,",I-org
from,O
Delhi,B-geo
on,O
1/4/2020,O
and,O
he,O
is,O
may,O
be,O
Corona,B-org
Positive.,I-org
Police,I-org
&,I-org
Doctors,I-org
was,O
also,O
come,O
for,O
checkup,O
him,O
but,O
he,O
was,O
not,O
agree,O
for,O
Covid,B-org
test,O
kindly,O
take,O
strict,O
action,O
in,O
this,O
matter.,O
Hon'ble,O
Chirag,O
sir,O
Maximum,O
number,O
of,O
Bihari,B-geo
Live,I-geo
at,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Narela,I-geo
and,I-org
Surat,B-geo
in,O
Covid,B-tim
-,I-tim
19,I-tim
pandemic.,O
I,O
informed,O
that,O
They,O
have,O
mentaly,O
disturbed,O
and,O
no,O
arrangement,O
of,O
food,O
in,O
this,O
Disaster.,B-per
So,I-per
Do,I-per
arrangements,O
for,O
coming,O
home,O
any,O
how,O
by,O
any,O
traveling,O
transport.,O
Thanks,B-per
Jamuiteam,I-per
1075,O
is,O
not,O
being,O
Connected.,O
Now,O
"she,",O
Sushila,B-per
"Devi,",I-per
age,O
77,O
yrs.,O
is,O
admit,O
in,O
Tirathram,B-org
Shah,I-org
Charitable,I-org
"Hospital,",I-org
Civil,B-geo
Lines,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
at,O
bed,O
no.144C.,O
Doctors,O
at,O
Tirathram,B-geo
says,O
that,O
Delhi,B-org
Govt.,I-org
has,O
directed,O
us,O
not,O
to,O
get,O
any,O
Covid,B-org
Tests.,I-org
Can,I-org
you,O
help,O
to,O
get,O
her,O
tested,O
Covid-19,O
?,O
1075,O
is,O
not,O
being,O
Connected.,O
Now,O
"she,",O
Sushila,B-per
"Devi,",I-per
age,O
77,O
yrs.,O
is,O
admit,O
in,O
Tirathram,B-org
Shah,I-org
Charitable,I-org
"Hospital,",I-org
Civil,B-geo
Lines,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
at,O
bed,O
no.144C.,O
Doctors,O
at,O
Tirathram,B-geo
says,O
that,O
Delhi,B-org
Govt.,I-org
has,O
directed,O
us,O
not,O
to,O
get,O
any,O
Covid,B-org
Tests.,I-org
Can,I-org
you,O
help,O
to,O
get,O
her,O
tested,O
Covid-19,O
?,O
1075,O
is,O
not,O
being,O
Connected.,O
Now,O
"she,",O
Sushila,B-per
"Devi,",I-per
age,O
77,O
yrs.,O
is,O
admit,O
in,O
Tirathram,B-org
Shah,I-org
Charitable,I-org
"Hospital,",I-org
Civil,B-geo
Lines,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
at,O
bed,O
no.144C.Doctors,O
at,O
Tirathram,B-geo
says,O
that,O
Delhi,B-per
Govt.,I-per
has,O
directed,O
us,O
not,O
to,O
get,O
any,O
Covid,B-per
Tests.Can,I-per
you,O
help,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Covid,O
19,O
Strikes,O
at,O
heart,O
of,O
Delhi,B-geo
with,O
7,O
positive,O
cases,O
of,O
Corona,B-geo
..,O
Oberoi,B-org
"Apartments,",I-org
civil,B-geo
Lines,I-geo
delhi,I-geo
sealed,O
..,O
just,O
200,O
meters,O
4m,O
LG,B-org
house,O
n,O
500,O
Meters,O
from,O
CM,O
residence.,O
Covid,O
19,O
Strikes,O
at,O
heart,O
of,O
Delhi,B-geo
with,O
7,O
positive,O
cases,O
of,O
Corona,B-org
..,O
Oberoi,B-org
"Apartments,",I-org
civil,B-geo
Lines,I-geo
delhi,I-geo
sealed,O
..,O
just,O
200,O
meters,O
4m,O
LG,B-org
house,O
n,O
500,O
Meters,O
from,O
CM,B-geo
residence,I-geo
..,O
pic.twitter.com/TJGcwHDO7P,O
Six,O
people,O
have,O
been,O
diagnosed,O
with,O
COVID-19,B-org
in,O
Dashrath,B-geo
Puri(South,I-geo
West,I-geo
"Delhi),as",O
per,O
Aarogya,B-per
Setu,I-per
but,O
still,O
people,O
are,O
roaming,O
like,O
nothing,O
has,O
happened.,O
Area,O
should,O
be,O
declared,O
hotspot.,O
Respect,O
sir,O
I,O
am,O
the,O
resident,O
of,O
dashrath,B-geo
puri,I-geo
new,I-geo
delhi,I-geo
and,O
I,O
am,O
stuck,O
in,O
my,O
village,O
since,B-tim
22,I-tim
March.(edalghardi,I-tim
village),I-tim
.,O
My,O
dadi,O
who,O
is,O
living(delhi),O
recently,O
with,O
my,O
aunty.Some,O
how,O
please,O
grant,O
us,O
(4person),O
the,O
e-pass,O
from,O
edalghardi,B-geo
(u.p),O
to,O
delhi.(covid,O
19,O
negative),O
Sir...,B-org
Company,I-org
in,O
#Aerocity,B-geo
with,O
name,O
Rattanindia,B-org
forcing,O
all,O
employees,O
to,O
come,O
to,O
office,O
or,O
apply,O
for,O
leave.,O
This,O
is,O
how,O
we,O
will,O
win,O
battle,O
of,O
Covid-19.,B-org
How,I-org
can,O
one,O
reach,O
office,O
from,O
outside,O
Delhi,B-geo
border?,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@HMOIndia,O
@msisodia,O
@narendramodi,O
@CMODelhi,O
Sir...,B-org
Company,I-org
in,O
#Aerocity,B-geo
with,O
name,O
Rattanindia,B-org
forcing,O
all,O
employees,O
to,O
come,O
to,O
office,O
or,O
apply,O
for,O
leave.,O
This,O
is,O
how,O
we,O
will,O
win,O
battle,O
of,O
Covid-19.,B-org
How,I-org
can,O
one,O
reach,O
office,O
from,O
outside,O
Delhi,B-geo
border?,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@HMOIndia,O
@manishaisodia,O
@narendramodi,O
@CMODelhi,O
Please,O
take,O
a,O
minute,O
to,O
listen,O
to,O
the,O
inspiring,O
experience,O
shared,O
by,O
first,O
COVID,B-org
positive,O
case,O
in,O
Aerocity,B-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
taking,O
us,O
through,O
his,O
successful,O
journey,O
from,O
quarantine,O
to,O
recovery.,O
@CMODelhi,O
&,B-org
Delhi,I-org
govt's,O
amazing,O
healthcare,O
team,O
&,O
staff,O
ensured,O
he,O
felt,O
safe,O
and,O
spirited.,O
https://twitter.com/DMNewDelhi/status/1254097148112584704,O
…,O
Paid,O
quarantine,O
centres,O
in,O
Aerocity,B-geo
near,O
the,O
Indira,B-geo
Gandhi,I-geo
International,I-geo
(IGI),I-geo
Airport,I-geo
were,O
shut,O
by,O
the,O
Delhi,B-geo
government,O
on,O
Friday,B-tim
as,O
people,O
move,O
out.,O
From,O
"now,",O
all,O
Covid-19,O
suspected,O
patients,O
will,O
be,O
taken,O
directly,O
to,O
government,O
quarantine,O
centres,O
set,O
up,O
in,O
various,O
parts,O
Paid,O
quarantine,O
centres,O
in,O
Aerocity,B-geo
near,O
the,O
Indira,B-geo
Gandhi,I-geo
International,I-geo
(IGI),I-geo
Airport,I-geo
were,O
shut,O
by,O
the,O
Delhi,B-geo
government,O
on,O
Friday,B-tim
as,O
people,O
move,O
out.,O
From,O
"now,",O
all,O
Covid-19,O
suspected,O
patients,O
will,O
be,O
taken,O
directly,O
to,O
government,O
quarantine,O
centres,O
set,O
up,O
in,O
various,O
parts,O
Paid,O
quarantine,O
centres,O
in,O
Aerocity,B-geo
near,O
the,O
Indira,B-geo
Gandhi,I-geo
International,I-geo
(IGI),I-geo
Airport,I-geo
were,O
shut,O
by,O
the,O
Delhi,B-geo
government,O
on,O
Friday,B-tim
as,O
people,O
move,O
out.,O
From,O
"now,",O
all,O
Covid-19,O
suspected,O
patients,O
will,O
be,O
taken,O
directly,O
to,O
government,O
quarantine,O
centres,O
set,O
up,O
in,O
various,O
parts,O
NEW,B-geo
DELHI,I-geo
DISTRICT,I-geo
ADMINISTRATION,O
had,O
set,O
up,O
the,O
first,O
of,O
its,O
kind,O
paid,O
quarantine,O
in,O
hotels,O
at,O
AEROCITY,B-geo
to,O
accommodate,O
the,O
international,O
passengers,O
who,O
travelled,O
back,O
from,O
the,O
nations,O
with,O
high,O
incidence,O
of,O
COVID-19.,B-org
@LtGovDelhi,I-org
@CMODelhi,I-org
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Please,O
do,O
something,O
for,O
those,O
people,O
who,O
work,O
in,O
hotel,O
industry,O
especially,O
who,O
work,O
in,O
"aerocity,",O
Delhi.,O
#Covid_19india,O
#StaySafe,O
2,O
innovations,O
in,O
utilizing,O
social/captive,O
infrastructure,O
in,O
private,O
and,O
public,O
sector,O
by,O
Delhi,B-org
Govt,I-org
for,O
#COVID.,O
1,O
Housing,O
constructed,O
by,O
DUSIB/DJB/DSIIDC,B-org
converted,O
into,O
100,O
bed,O
hospital.,O
100,O
more,O
coming.,O
2,O
"Redfox,",B-per
Ibis,I-per
+,O
LemonTree,O
hotel,O
in,O
Aerocity,O
used,O
for,O
quarantine.,O
https://twitter.com/AAPDelhi/status/1240554027714113536,O
…,O
Following,O
the,O
directive,O
on,O
public,O
gathering,O
due,O
to,O
"#COVID,",B-org
venue,O
of,O
today’s,O
strategic,O
meeting,O
has,O
been,O
changed,O
from,O
@BigBoyToyz,O
to,O
"@JWMarriott,",O
"Aerocity,",B-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
The,O
meetings,O
will,O
happen,O
throughout,O
the,O
day,O
in,O
#ICB,B-org
Executive,O
suit.,O
Ask,O
for,O
me,O
at,O
reception.,O
See,O
you,O
allhttps://twitter.com/ind_cryptobulls/status/1238939478619607040,O
…,O
@LtGovDelhi,O
All,O
MCD,B-org
&,I-org
NDMC,I-org
hospitals,O
must,O
take,O
Covid,O
patients.The,O
number,O
is,O
increasing,O
&,O
we,O
must,O
instruct,O
to,O
concerned,O
municipalities,O
&,B-org
Delhi,B-geo
Cantonment,I-geo
Board,I-geo
also.,O
@Ch_AnilKumarINC,O
@ChatrathM,O
@JaiKish21958000,O
@mudit_aggarwal,O
@alimehdi_inc,O
@PMOIndia,O
@rajnathsingh,O
@moayush,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@sharmarekha,O
plz,O
look,O
into,O
this.,O
My,O
mother,O
has,O
to,O
go,O
door,O
to,O
door,O
and,O
work,O
for,O
electrol,O
work,O
by,O
the,O
order,O
of,O
Delhi,B-geo
cantonment,I-geo
board,I-geo
in,O
this,O
Covid,B-per
19,O
situation,O
by,O
putting,O
their,O
life,O
on,O
risk.,O
Plz,O
help.,O
https://twitter.com/vinzkaushik/status/1266018271062396928,O
…,O
The,O
Army’s,O
Base,B-org
Hospital,I-org
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
Cantonment,I-geo
has,O
extended,O
its,O
medical,O
facilities,O
to,O
Delhi,B-org
"Police,",I-org
after,O
the,O
latter,O
made,O
a,O
request,O
for,O
admitting,O
Covid-19,O
positive,O
cases,O
in,O
the,O
force.,O
https://bit.ly/2WWMWis,O
Armed,B-org
Forces,I-org
Personnel,I-org
Among,I-org
24,I-org
Covid-19,I-org
Positive,I-org
Patients,I-org
at,O
Army's,O
RR,B-org
Hospital,I-org
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
All,O
of,O
them,O
have,O
been,O
shifted,O
to,O
the,O
Army's,O
Base,O
hospital,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
Cantonment,I-geo
pic.twitter.com/qMHs1qdDha,O
Covid,O
outbreak,O
in,O
Army's,O
apex,O
hospital,O
in,O
Delhi:,B-geo
24,O
cancer,O
"patients,",O
including,O
serving,O
and,O
retired,O
military,O
personnel,O
and,O
"dependents,",O
admitted,O
in,O
Army,B-org
Hospital,I-org
(R&R),I-org
test,O
positive,O
for,O
"Corons,",O
shifted,O
to,O
Base,B-org
"Hospital,",I-org
Delhi,I-org
Cantonment.,I-org
One,O
Indian,B-gpe
Army,B-org
doctor,O
and,O
a,O
private,O
person,O
were,O
tested,O
COVID,B-org
positive,O
at,O
Manekshaw,B-org
Enclave,I-org
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
Cantonment,I-geo
area,O
https://www.wefornews.com/indian-army-doctor-infected-with-coronavirus/,O
…,O
#COVID2019,B-org
Reaches,I-org
Delhi,I-org
Cantonment,I-org
area,O
(Indian,B-org
Army),I-org
A,I-org
total,O
of,O
2,O
cases,O
positive,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
Cantt.,I-geo
1,O
army,O
doctor,O
and,O
1,O
jawan,O
(,O
Army,O
doctor,O
involved,O
in,O
anti-COVID,O
operation,O
in,O
civilian,O
area,O
),O
pic.twitter.com/Y9gBHcyES8,O
The,O
body,O
of,O
corona,O
virus,O
(COVID-19),O
victim,O
kept,O
in,O
a,O
coffin,O
before,O
the,O
burial,O
in,O
#NewDelhi,O
graveyard.,O
Delhi,B-org
Gate,I-org
Cemetery,I-org
Is,I-org
running,O
out,O
of,O
space,O
as,O
COVID-19,B-org
Death,I-org
Count,I-org
Rises,I-org
and,O
may,O
have,O
no,O
space,O
left,O
for,O
burials,O
by,O
the,O
end,O
of,O
June.,B-org
#Coronaindia,I-org
#india,I-org
Photo,I-org
by,O
Vijay,O
Pandeypic.twitter.com/FwVaMSdQMN,O
Cemetery,O
at,O
Delhi,B-geo
gate,O
fast,O
running,O
out,O
of,O
space.,O
Hygienically,O
COVID,O
patients,O
shd,O
be,O
"cremated,",O
coz,O
of,O
virus.,O
It's,O
a,O
blunder.these,O
r,O
not,O
normal,O
times,O
n,O
normal,O
virus.,O
Surprised,O
at,O
KEJRIWAL's,O
ignorance.,O
He,O
is,O
suppose,O
to,O
be,O
educated.,O
With,O
rising,O
Covid-19,O
death,O
"toll,",O
Delhi,B-per
Gate,I-per
cemetery,O
running,O
out,O
of,O
burial,O
space,O
(via:,O
https://www.hindustantimes.com/delhi-news/with-rising-covid-19-death-toll-delhi-gate-cemetery-running-out-of-burial-space/story-fDhhzvWUsG9bhytWkKlmNJ.html,O
…)https://newsaroundme.com/story/64AD8A022329FD30,O
…,O
Delhi,B-org
Gate,I-org
Cemetery,I-org
Running,I-org
Out,I-org
Of,I-org
Space,I-org
As,I-org
COVID-19,I-org
Death,I-org
Count,I-org
Rises,I-org
https://wordbeyond.com/2020/06/12/delhi-gate-cemetery-operating-out-of-house-as-covid-19-loss-of-life-depend-rises/,O
…,O
Delhi,B-per
Gate,I-per
cemetery,O
may,O
soon,O
run,O
out,O
of,O
burial,O
space,O
as,O
Covid,O
death,O
toll,O
continues,O
to,O
rise,O
in,O
the,O
national,O
capital:,O
Reports,O
|,O
Indiablooms,B-org
-,I-org
First,I-org
Portal,I-org
on,I-org
Digital,I-org
News,I-org
Management,I-org
https://www.indiablooms.com/news-details/N/62278/delhi-gate-cemetery-may-soon-run-out-of-burial-space-as-covid-death-toll-continues-to-rise-in-the-national-capital-reports.html,O
…,O
#Muslim,B-per
"Cemetery,",I-per
#Novel,I-per
"Coronavirus,",I-per
"#Coronavirus,",I-per
#Covid,I-per
19,O
With,O
rising,O
Covid-19,O
death,O
"toll,",O
Delhi,B-per
Gate,I-per
cemetery,O
running,O
out,O
of,O
burial,O
space,O
..,O
https://www.hindustantimes.com/delhi-news/with-rising-covid-19-death-toll-delhi-gate-cemetery-running-out-of-burial-space/story-fDhhzvWUsG9bhytWkKlmNJ.html,O
…,O
Delhi,B-per
Gate,I-per
cemetery,O
runs,O
out,O
of,O
‘do,O
gaz,O
zameen’,O
for,O
Covid-19,O
victims,O
as,O
death,O
toll,O
overwhelms,O
national,O
capital,O
https://is.gd/enOBQW,O
R,B-org
people,O
frm,O
a,O
particular,O
religion,O
dying,O
in,O
larger,O
numbers?,O
At,O
least,O
Hindus,O
dont,O
take,O
up,O
any,O
space,O
after,O
they,O
pass,O
on,O
so,O
no,O
added,O
stress,O
there,O
#COVID19,O
:,O
With,O
a,O
rapid,O
incline,O
in,O
the,O
number,O
of,O
deaths,O
due,O
to,O
"COVID-19,",O
the,O
New,B-org
Cemetery,I-org
for,I-org
Mohammedans,I-org
at,O
Delhi,B-geo
Gate,I-geo
is,O
under,O
stress,O
and,O
may,O
have,O
no,O
space,O
left,O
for,O
burials.,O
#DelhiGate,B-geo
#Mohammedans,B-gpe
#COVID_19,B-org
#Coronavirushttps://bit.ly/3hijKMl,O
With,O
rising,O
Covid-19,O
death,O
"toll,",O
Delhi,B-geo
Gate,I-geo
cemetery,O
running,O
out,O
of,O
burial,O
space,O
http://www.hindustantimes.com/delhi-news/with-rising-covid-19-death-toll-delhi-gate-cemetery-running-out-of-burial-space/story-fDhhzvWUsG9bhytWkKlmNJ.html,O
…,O
With,O
rising,O
Covid-19,O
death,O
"toll,",O
Delhi,B-geo
Gate,I-geo
cemetery,O
running,O
out,O
of,O
burial,O
space,O
http://toi.in/eDK3ea,O
Download,O
the,O
TOI,B-org
app,O
now:https://timesofindia.onelink.me/efRt/installtoi,O
With,O
rising,O
Covid-19,O
death,O
"toll,",O
Delhi,B-geo
Gate,I-geo
cemetery,O
running,O
out,O
of,O
burial,O
space,O
http://toi.in/HBp8wa,O
With,O
rising,O
Covid-19,O
death,O
"toll,",O
Delhi,B-geo
Gate,I-geo
cemetery,O
running,O
out,O
of,O
burial,O
space,O
http://toi.in/bBo0_Z,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
failing,O
as,O
"CM,",O
a,O
friend’s,O
father,O
lost,O
his,O
life,O
to,O
covid,O
now,O
another,O
friend’s,O
father,O
struggling,O
at,O
LNJP,B-org
"hospital,Delhi",O
gate,B-geo
.,O
How,O
can,O
you,O
shut,O
all,O
the,O
covid,O
test,O
centres,O
",",O
reports,O
are,O
awaited,O
.,O
No,O
oxygen,O
supply,O
at,O
hospital,O
.,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@msisodia,O
@AamAadmiParty,O
More,O
than,O
4,O
mn,O
Covid-19,O
detection,O
tests,O
in,O
India,B-geo
so,O
far:,O
Health,O
ministry,O
https://www.business-standard.com/article/current-affairs/covid-19-detection-tests-cross-4-mn-mark-as-cases-rise-health-ministry-120060301457_1.html,O
…,O
via,O
NaMo,O
Apppic.twitter.com/Zer4clFYEi,O
Cheetau,B-geo
spotted,O
in,O
Jungle.,B-org
Users,I-org
claim,O
the,O
video,O
is,O
taken,O
from,O
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
delhi,I-geo
cantt.,O
Real,O
or,O
fake?,O
Go,O
check,O
out,O
on,O
youthube,O
channel,O
https://youtu.be/6Wj3QZYaZaQ,O
Do,O
Not,O
forget,O
to,O
"like,",O
share,O
and,O
subscribe.,O
#YouTube,O
#tiktokexposed,O
#carryminatiroast,O
#Covid_19india,O
Covid,B-org
Poster,I-org
Challenge,I-org
Category,I-org
1:00,O
Class,O
1-5;,O
Theme:,B-org
Stay,I-org
Safe,I-org
Student,I-org
Name:,I-org
Amy,I-org
Laishram,I-org
Parent's,I-org
Name:,I-org
Dr,I-org
Shanta,I-org
Laishram,I-org
and,I-org
Dr,I-org
Kabita,I-org
Laishram,I-org
Class:,I-org
4,I-org
School:,I-org
Springdales,I-org
"School,",I-org
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
@crpfindiapic.twitter.com/IAWJvh0s9M,O
#crpfindia,O
",#BalsenaFightsCorona",O
Theme:Life,O
during,O
COVID,B-org
Student,I-org
name:,I-org
Anshika,I-org
Mohanty,I-org
Class:,I-org
6,I-org
School:,I-org
Springdales,I-org
"School,",I-org
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Father,I-org
name:,I-org
Ashok,I-org
Mohanty,I-org
Mobile:,I-org
9911519307,I-org
Email:,I-org
ashoksmohanty@gmail.com,I-org
pic.twitter.com/7yhwDxM4DE,O
KASHVI,O
GUPTA,O
CLASS,O
-,O
2,O
B,B-org
SPRINGDALES,I-org
SCHOOL,O
DHAULA,B-geo
"KUAN,",I-geo
NEW,I-geo
DELHI,I-geo
PARENTS:-,I-art
DINESH,I-art
GUPTA,I-art
PREETI,I-art
GUPTA,I-art
COVID,I-art
POSTER,I-art
CHALLENGE,I-art
@crpfindiapic.twitter.com/G1BZDzhbkJ,O
#UnlockYourCreativity,O
@crpfindia,O
COVID,B-org
POSTER,I-org
CHALLENGE,I-org
Aaveer,I-org
Dhawan,I-org
Category,I-org
1:00,O
1st,O
B,B-org
Theme:,I-org
Stay,I-org
Safe,I-org
School,I-org
-,I-org
Springdales,I-org
School,I-org
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Mob:,I-org
9873224191,O
pic.twitter.com/PauN6o4k18,O
#CRPFPosterChallenge,O
@crpfindia,O
COVID,B-org
POSTER,I-org
CHALLENGE,I-org
Aaveer,I-org
Dhawan,I-org
Category,I-org
1:00,O
1st,O
B,B-org
Theme:,I-org
Stay,I-org
Safe,I-org
School,I-org
-,I-org
Springdales,I-org
School,I-org
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Mob:,I-org
9873224191,O
pic.twitter.com/CuS0NRJfQc,O
@crpfindia,O
COVID,B-org
POSTER,I-org
CHALLENGE,I-org
Aaveer,I-org
Dhawan,I-org
Category,I-org
1:00,O
1st,O
B,B-org
Theme:,I-org
Stay,I-org
Safe,I-org
School,I-org
-,I-org
Springdales,I-org
School,I-org
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Mob:,I-org
9873224191,O
pic.twitter.com/Wf8mPQ1UHd,O
@crpfindia,O
COVID,B-org
POSTER,I-org
CHALLENGE,I-org
Aaveer,I-org
Dhawan,I-org
Category,I-org
1:00,O
1st,O
B,B-org
Theme:,I-org
Stay,I-org
Safe,I-org
School,I-org
-,I-org
Springdales,I-org
School,I-org
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Mob:,I-org
9873224191,O
pic.twitter.com/yMHa3JaS4I,O
@crpfindia,O
Covid,B-org
Poster,I-org
Challenge,I-org
Student,I-org
name-,O
AYUSHMAAN,O
KHER,O
Parents,O
name-,O
TARUN,B-art
AND,I-art
ARADHNA,I-art
KHER,I-art
Class-,I-art
II,I-art
School-,I-art
SPRINGDALES,I-art
"SCHOOL,",I-art
DHAULA,B-geo
"KUAN,",I-geo
NEW,I-geo
DELHI,I-geo
pic.twitter.com/qpzLywQcvn,O
@crpfindia,O
Covid,B-org
Poster,I-org
Challenge,I-org
Student,I-org
name-,O
TARINI,O
KHER,O
Parent,O
name-,O
TARUN,B-org
&,I-org
ARADHNA,I-org
KHER,I-org
Class-,I-org
V,I-org
School-,I-org
SPRINGDALES,I-org
"SCHOOL,",O
DHAULA,B-geo
"KUAN,",I-geo
NEW,I-geo
DELHI,I-geo
pic.twitter.com/clXTIB52HR,O
@crpfindia,O
COVID,B-org
POSTER,I-org
CHALLENGE,I-org
Aaveer,I-org
Dhawan,I-org
Category,I-org
1:00,O
1st,O
B,B-org
Theme:,I-org
Stay,I-org
Safe,I-org
School,I-org
-,I-org
Springdales,I-org
School,I-org
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Mob:,I-org
9873224191,O
pic.twitter.com/YhJJxYxcGU,O
Covid,B-org
Poster,I-org
Challenge,I-org
-,I-org
poster,O
made,O
by,O
Ayaan,B-org
Malhotra,I-org
s/o,I-org
Pooja,I-org
"Malhotra,",I-org
class,O
"1,",O
Springdales,B-org
"School,",I-org
Dhaula,B-geo
"Kuan,",I-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
@crpfindiapic.twitter.com/36oZlzvfrH,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
My,O
society,O
Delhi,B-geo
P-Pocket,B-geo
Dilshad,I-geo
Garden,I-geo
has,O
found,O
a,O
case,O
that,O
is,O
positive,O
but,O
i,O
am,O
unable,O
to,O
find,O
that,O
on,O
Covid,B-per
App,I-per
as,O
well,O
as,O
No,O
Indication,O
around,O
100M,B-org
of,O
any,O
case,O
by,O
amy,O
physical,O
sticker,O
or,O
something,O
Update,O
47,O
:,O
6:30,O
pm,O
-,O
Guru,B-org
Teg,I-org
Bahadur,I-org
Hospital,I-org
"(GTB),",I-org
Tahirpur,B-geo
"Rd,",I-geo
GTB,I-geo
"Enclave,",I-geo
Dilshad,I-geo
"Garden,",I-geo
New,I-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
has,O
hundreds,O
of,O
beds,O
still,O
vacant,O
and,O
are,O
taking,O
even,O
suspected,O
COVID,O
cases.,O
Go,O
there,O
in,O
case,O
you,O
stay,O
nearby.,O
They,O
don’t,O
pick,O
up,O
the,O
phone,O
easily.,O
Contact,O
:,O
11,B-tim
2258,I-tim
6262,I-tim
@hospitalyashoda,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
@ndtv,O
Delhi,B-geo
resident,O
COVID-19,O
positive,O
patient,O
at,O
Yashoda,B-org
Hospital,I-org
Koshambi,I-org
Sahibabad,I-org
allowed,O
to,O
travel,O
to,O
"Home,",B-org
Dilshad,B-geo
Garden,I-geo
by,O
private,O
car,O
driven,O
by,O
own,O
"children,I",O
don’t,O
know,O
what,O
to,O
"say,",O
this,O
is,O
criminal.,O
No,O
reporting,O
no,O
updates!,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
"Sir,",O
In,O
Dilshad,B-geo
Garden,I-geo
",",O
Why,B-per
Covid,I-per
patients,O
are,O
home,O
quarantine.,O
Earlier,O
you,O
said,O
Delhi,B-org
government,I-org
has,O
good,O
plan,O
and,O
medical,O
facility.,O
GTB,O
hospital,O
is,O
nearby,O
but,O
still,O
home,O
quarantine.,O
Please,O
share,O
your,O
views,O
on,O
this.,O
Some1,B-per
told,O
me,O
that,O
Dilshad,B-geo
Garden,I-geo
in,O
"Delhi,hotspot",O
of,O
COVID19,B-org
had,O
mad,O
rush,O
of,O
people,O
buying,O
Coolers/ACs,O
due,O
to,O
hot,O
weather.,O
How,O
to,O
believe,O
Covid,B-per
can,O
restrict,O
#Indians,O
from,O
shopping?,O
@narendramodi,B-per
Govt,I-per
needs,O
to,O
be,O
smart,O
to,O
make,O
India,B-geo
Great,I-org
Again.,I-org
#stocks,O
#equities,O
#investing,O
#Delhifightagainstcorona,B-geo
Delhi,B-org
govt,I-org
has,O
Been,O
decided,O
#GTBHospital,O
Dilshad,B-geo
Garden,I-geo
to,O
be,O
become,O
a,O
#COVID,B-org
hospital,O
in,O
next,O
2-Mar,O
days,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@SatyendarJain,O
@Priyajeph11,O
@DrSunilArora4,O
@GtbhRda,O
@MamcRda,O
@rdalhmc,O
@drpankajsolanki,O
@the_orthopod,O
#CoronaPandemic,O
#StayHomeStaySafe,O
#Delhifightagainstcorona,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
govt,O
has,O
Been,O
decided,O
#GTBHospital-,O
Dilshad,B-geo
Garden,I-geo
to,O
be,O
become,O
a,O
#COVID,B-org
hospital,O
in,O
next,O
2-Mar,O
days.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@SatyendarJain,O
#CoronaPandemic,O
#StayHomeStaySafehttps://twitter.com/ArvindKejriwal/status/1264806239835283459,O
…,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
@DelhiPolice,O
@AmitShahOffice,O
@PMOIndia,O
@narendramodi,B-org
Delhi,B-geo
opened,O
but,O
moving,O
to,O
worst,O
condition,O
at,O
residence,O
risk.,O
No,O
compliance,O
of,O
rules,O
and,O
regulations.,O
Totally,O
scrapped,O
lockdown,O
1,O
and,O
2,O
which,O
helped,O
to,O
fight,O
against,O
Covid.,B-org
From,I-org
dilshad,O
garden.,O
Sharing,O
acknowledgment,O
of,O
#PPEKits,O
donated,O
by,O
me,O
in,O
collaboration,O
with,O
Aarohan,B-per
Helping,I-per
Hands,I-per
to,O
"#SwamiDayanandHospital,",O
Dilshad,B-geo
"Garden,",I-geo
#Delhi,I-geo
#Covid_19,I-org
@GautamGambhir,I-org
@M_Lekhi,I-org
@thakkar_sameet,O
@bhav2406,O
@indiantweeter,O
@iSinghApurva,O
@iSinghVikash,O
@narendramodi,O
@JPNadda,O
@RSSorgpic.twitter.com/A13ymDUcOw,O
@CMODelhi,B-per
"Sir,",I-per
as,O
per,O
the,O
recent,O
news,O
",",O
first,O
two,O
hotspots,O
of,O
"delhi,",B-geo
dilshad,I-geo
garden,I-geo
and,O
"seemapuri,",B-geo
were,O
covid,O
free,O
long,O
back,O
by,O
the,O
virtue,O
of,O
operation,O
SHEILD,O
and,O
were,O
about,O
to,O
de,O
contain,O
them,O
as,O
there,O
weren't,O
any,O
case,O
from,O
past,B-tim
30,I-tim
days,O
or,O
even,O
more.,O
Sir,O
when,O
would,O
it,O
occur?,O
"Sir,",O
as,O
per,O
the,O
recent,O
news,O
",",O
first,O
two,O
hotspots,O
of,O
"delhi,",B-geo
dilshad,I-geo
garden,I-geo
and,O
"seemapuri,",B-geo
were,O
covid,O
free,O
long,O
back,O
by,O
the,O
virtue,O
of,O
operation,O
SHEILD,O
and,O
were,O
about,O
to,O
de,O
contain,O
them,O
as,O
there,O
weren't,O
any,O
case,O
from,O
past,B-tim
30,I-tim
days,O
or,O
even,O
more.,O
Sir,O
when,O
would,O
it,O
occur?,O
@AamAadmiParty,O
My,O
Father,O
is,O
suffering,O
from,O
cancer,O
disease,O
and,O
due,O
to,O
COVID,B-org
cases,O
found,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
caner,I-geo
"Institute,Dilshad",I-geo
garden,I-geo
his,O
treatment,O
is,O
stopped.,O
Now,O
we,O
dont,O
know,O
where,O
we,O
can,O
continue,O
his,O
treatment,O
and,O
we,O
can't,O
afford,O
pvt,O
hospital,O
Please,O
help,O
sir!!!,O
helpsir!!!,O
My,O
Father,O
is,O
suffering,O
from,O
cancer,O
disease,O
and,O
due,O
to,O
COVID,B-org
cases,O
found,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
caner,I-geo
"Institute,Dilshad",I-geo
garden,I-geo
his,O
treatment,O
is,O
stopped.,O
Now,O
we,O
dont,O
know,O
where,O
we,O
can,O
continue,O
his,O
treatment,O
and,O
we,O
can't,O
afford,O
pvt,O
hospital,O
Please,O
help,O
sir!!!,O
helpsir!!!!@ArvindKejriwal,O
@msisodia,O
No,O
case,O
has,O
been,O
reported,O
in,O
last,O
15,B-tim
days,O
from,B-tim
3,I-tim
locations,O
in,O
the,O
national,O
"capital,",O
including,O
Dilshad,B-geo
"Garden,",I-geo
60,O
containment,O
zones,O
identified,O
till,O
now:,O
Delhi,B-org
Health,I-org
Min,I-org
Satyendar,I-org
Jain,I-org
Latest,I-org
updates,O
https://www.mapsofindia.com/my-india/health/just-facts-coronavirus-in-india,O
…,O
#coronavirusinindia,O
#COVID,O
No,O
case,O
has,O
been,O
reported,O
in,O
last,O
15,B-tim
days,O
from,B-tim
3,I-tim
locations,O
in,O
the,O
national,O
"capital,",O
including,O
Dilshad,B-geo
"Garden,",I-geo
60,O
containment,O
zones,O
identified,O
till,O
now:,O
Delhi,B-org
Health,I-org
Min,I-org
Satyendar,I-org
Jain,I-org
Latest,I-org
updates,O
https://www.mapsofindia.com/my-india/health/just-facts-coronavirus-in-india,O
…,O
#CoronaUpdatesInIndia,O
#Covid_19,O
Operation,O
SHIELD,O
successful,O
in,O
containing,O
COVID-19,O
spread,O
in,O
Dilshad,B-geo
Garden:,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
health,O
minister,O
http://bachatkar.com/operation-shield-successful-in-containing-covid-19-spread-in-dilshad-garden-delhi-health-minister/,O
…pic.twitter.com/3Ypvqh1edG,O
Delhi,B-org
Govt's,I-org
Operation,I-org
SHIELD,I-org
successful,O
in,O
Vasundhara,B-geo
Enclave,I-geo
and,I-org
Khichripur,I-geo
as,O
well,O
Both,O
places,O
were,O
sealed,O
on,O
31,O
March.,O
No,O
new,O
cases,O
of,O
Covid-19,B-geo
in,O
the,O
last,O
15,B-tim
days,O
Earlier,B-tim
Dilshad,B-geo
Garden,I-geo
also,O
was,O
Corona,O
free,O
because,O
of,O
Operation,O
SHIELD,O
Good,O
going,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Covid,B-per
tested,O
on,O
8th,B-tim
"June,",I-tim
paid,O
INR,O
4500,O
at,O
Medeor,B-org
Hospital,I-org
Dwarka,I-org
"Delhi,",I-org
Day,B-tim
6,I-tim
still,O
waiting,O
for,O
report.,O
Hospital,O
is,O
not,O
taking,O
seriousely.,O
Making,O
fool,O
to,O
"us,",O
blaming,O
ICMR,O
delaying,O
in,O
"report,",O
is,O
that,O
true.,O
Humble,O
Request,O
to,O
donate,O
for,O
Shri,B-org
Shiv,I-org
Shankar,I-org
sharma(79/M),O
struggling,O
with,O
Covid-19,B-geo
in,O
Prakash,B-org
Hospital,I-org
",Dwarka(",I-org
Delhi,I-org
),O
He,O
has,O
niether,O
a,O
family,O
nor,O
relative,O
support.,O
We,O
have,O
achieved,O
to,O
collect,O
"125,000",O
inr,O
out,O
of,O
5,O
Lacs.,B-per
Kindly,I-per
retweet,O
this,O
message.,O
pic.twitter.com/ns32iZsq4L,O
#Covid19plasmarequirement,O
My,O
"father,",O
diagnosed,O
with,O
"Covid-19,",B-org
is,O
undergoing,O
treatment,O
at,O
a,O
hospital,O
in,O
"Dwarka,",B-geo
"Delhi,",I-geo
on,O
ventilator,O
support.,O
Please,O
suggest,O
the,O
centres,O
of,O
plasma,O
therapy,O
in,O
NCR,B-geo
and,O
the,O
procedure,O
to,O
be,O
followed,O
for,O
same,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@raghav_chadha,O
@AtishiAAP,O
@lalpathlabs,O
wheather,O
covid,O
19,O
test,O
is,O
available,O
for,O
CGHS,B-org
card,O
holder,O
in,O
your,O
lab,O
at,O
Dwarka,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
10,O
cases,O
in,O
Classic,B-geo
apartment,O
#dwarka,B-geo
Delhi.,O
All,O
these,O
people,O
have,O
been,O
going,O
out,O
to,O
nearby,O
parks,O
for,O
jogging,O
or,O
markets,O
for,O
buying,O
stuffs.,O
There,O
is,O
no,O
clue,O
how,O
they,O
got,O
infected....,O
#CoronavirusIndia,O
#Covid_19indiapic.twitter.com/XL4cL839op,O
@ShaleenMitra,O
@SatyendarJain,O
This,O
injection,O
is,O
required,O
urgently,O
for,O
a,O
50+,O
yrs,O
covid,O
patient,O
admitted,O
in,O
dwarka,B-geo
delhi,I-geo
and,O
in,O
ICU,B-geo
for,O
past,B-tim
2,I-tim
days.,O
Her,O
life,O
is,O
totally,O
dependent,O
on,O
availability,O
of,O
this.,O
Please,O
guide,O
where,O
to,O
get,O
it.,O
Doctors,O
prescription,O
attached,O
too,O
pic.twitter.com/TkOOj6XdmQ,O
"Dwarka,",B-geo
Delhi:,I-geo
Our,I-org
sister,O
from,O
Manipur,B-geo
got,O
help.,O
My,O
heartfelt,O
gratitude,O
to,O
@DelhiPolice,O
&,O
@DCPDwarka,O
for,O
reaching,O
out,O
to,O
help,O
them.,O
Salute,O
to,O
our,O
#CoronaWarriors,O
who,O
despite,O
their,O
busy,O
schedules,O
had,O
done,O
humanitarian,O
services,O
in,O
between!,O
@NBirenSingh,O
#IndiaFightsCorona,O
@COVID,O
pic.twitter.com/2Dn142AqTs,O
Any,B-per
Covid19,I-per
dedicated,O
hospital,O
in,O
"dwarka,",B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
?,O
My,O
friend's,O
mother,O
struggling,O
to,O
get,O
admitted,O
with,O
symptoms,O
of,O
Covid,B-geo
since,O
morning!,O
Any,O
private,O
hospital,O
where,O
bed,O
available?,O
@CovidIndiaSeva,O
there,O
is,O
a,O
covid,O
19,O
patient,O
in,O
Sahara,B-geo
Society,I-geo
Sector,I-geo
6,I-geo
Dwarka,I-geo
",",O
Delhi.,I-geo
He,O
bought,O
milk,O
from,O
same,O
mather,O
dairy,O
booth,O
and,O
many,O
other,O
did,O
too.,O
If,O
we,O
show,O
symptoms,O
like,O
"cough,",O
fever,O
and,O
"dyspnea,",O
Should,O
we,O
visit,O
flu,O
clinic???,O
Body,O
Transformation,O
going,O
on,O
.,O
#stressbuster,O
#bodybuilding,O
#fitness,O
#selflove,O
#parapowerlifting,O
#Dream,O
#motivated,O
#diet,O
#lockdown,O
#covid,O
#stayhome,O
#staysafe,O
#India,B-geo
@,O
"Dwarka,",B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
https://www.instagram.com/p/CAFdDe_HSE1/?igshid=1t8rd69rn8x5q,O
…,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
"Sir,",B-per
Venkateshwar,I-per
hospital,O
in,O
"Dwarka,",B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
is,O
not,O
allowing,O
even,O
day-care,O
admission,O
to,O
cancer,O
patients,O
for,O
regular,O
chemo,O
without,O
Covid,O
#NAME?,O
certificate,O
issued,O
in,O
last,O
72,B-tim
hrs.,O
Is,O
it,O
as,O
per,O
govt.,O
guidelines,O
?,O
If,O
"yes,",O
kindly,O
review,O
"it,",O
as,O
it,O
is,O
not,O
feasible,O
always.,O
Menu,O
of,O
dinner,O
full,O
of,O
"nutrition,",O
"fruits,",O
dairy,O
"products,",O
green,O
vegetables,O
at,O
Covid,B-org
Care,I-org
"Center,",I-org
PTS,I-org
Dwarka.,I-org
Delhi,I-org
"Gov,",I-org
best,O
care,O
and,O
cure,O
all,O
patients.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@SatyendarJain,O
@ipathak25,O
#CoronaWarriorspic.twitter.com/PaCXxkVXVJ,O
@drharshvardhan,O
Sir,O
I,O
have,O
a,O
suggestion,O
of,O
keeping,O
Dwarka,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
insulated,O
from,O
Covid,B-geo
afflicted,O
/,O
symptomatic,O
cases.,O
There,O
r,O
only,O
3-Apr,O
major,O
entry,O
points,O
to,O
Dwarka,B-geo
if,O
thermal,O
screening,O
is,O
done,O
of,O
entrants,O
to,O
Dwarka,B-geo
at,O
these,O
points,O
u,O
will,O
b,O
able,O
to,O
isolate,O
the,O
sub,O
city,O
from,O
COVID,B-org
A,O
small,O
mesage,O
on,O
covid,O
19,O
by,O
Pravisha,B-per
Sharma,I-per
@,O
"Dwarka,",B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
https://www.instagram.com/p/B_hrqhnH3Ap/?igshid=7ufmaos5cvdk,O
…,O
@msisodia,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
Today,B-tim
I,O
received,O
notice,O
from,O
OPG,O
school,O
Dwarka,B-geo
(Delhi),I-geo
asking,O
Tuition,O
"fees,",O
but,O
with,O
a,O
note,O
saying,O
“as,O
per,O
govt,O
"directions,",O
pay,O
only,O
tuition,O
fees,O
now,O
and,O
school,O
shall,O
collect,O
all,O
other,O
fees,O
after,O
the,O
school,O
reopens,O
after,O
Covid-19”,O
@DelhiparentsDPA,O
#Okhla_Jamia_Nagar,B-geo
based,O
group,O
is,O
distributing,O
#Rashan_Kits,O
in,O
#Dwarka_Delhi.,B-geo
#ServingTheNation,O
#Covid_19india,O
#Cronahttps://twitter.com/SyedZainulHaid2/status/1254136560607531008,O
…,O
Covid,B-per
Poster,I-per
Challenge.,I-per
Poster,I-per
by,O
Arav,B-per
Bisht,I-per
class,O
4th,O
student,O
Venkateswar,B-org
International,I-org
School,I-org
Sector,O
10,O
Dwarka,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
@crpfindiapic.twitter.com/VSvQrlsmN7,O
@crpfindia,O
Covid,O
poster,O
"challenge,",O
Name,B-org
Nidhish,I-org
"Kumar,",I-org
class,I-org
7th,I-org
A,I-org
",School",I-org
N.K.Bagrodia,I-org
Global,I-org
"School,Dwarka",I-org
",Delhi",I-org
pic.twitter.com/xMa2VDkI1K,O
Humble,O
Request,O
to,O
donate,O
for,O
Shri,B-org
Shiv,I-org
Shankar,I-org
sharma(79/M),O
struggling,O
with,O
Covid-19,O
in,O
Prakash,B-org
Hospital,I-org
",Dwarka(",I-org
Delhi,I-org
),O
He,O
has,O
niether,O
a,O
family,O
nor,O
relative,O
support.,O
We,O
have,O
achieved,O
to,O
collect,O
"125,000",O
inr,O
out,O
of,O
5,O
Lacs.,B-per
Kindly,I-per
retweet,O
this,O
message.,O
pic.twitter.com/ns32iZsq4L,O
COVID-19:,B-org
Delhi,B-geo
के,I-geo
Dwarka,I-geo
mor,O
पर,O
Corona,B-per
"Positive,परिवार",I-per
के,O
6,O
लोग,O
quaran...,O
https://youtu.be/jCIRcoa1RQ8,O
via,O
@YouTube,O
The,O
champ,O
who,O
is,O
"Akshita,",O
"@DaggerWords,",O
brings,O
out,O
the,O
#JanataCurfew,O
updates,O
from,O
Delhi's,B-geo
Dwarka,B-geo
Mor.,I-geo
The,O
roads,I-geo
are,O
eerily,O
"silent,",O
and,O
people,O
appear,O
to,O
be,O
following,O
the,O
instructions,O
to,O
defeat,O
Covid-19.,O
#IndiaFightCoronahttps://twitter.com/jankibaat1/status/1241636663748481025,O
…,O
#CRPFPosterChallenge,O
Category,O
2,O
Covid,B-per
Poster,I-per
Challenge,I-per
Made,I-per
by,O
Madhvi,B-org
Singh,B-per
Parent,B-org
name,O
-,O
Vinita,B-org
Singh,I-org
Class,I-org
-,I-org
8,I-org
School,I-org
-,I-org
Shiksha,B-org
Bharati,I-org
Global,I-org
School,I-org
"Dwarka,",I-geo
sector,O
-,O
"8,",O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
pic.twitter.com/GlmFG9YlmZ,O
@crpfindia,O
COVID,B-art
POSTER,I-art
CHALLENGE,I-art
Name,I-art
-,I-art
AARADHYA,I-art
JHA,I-art
CATEGORY,I-art
1(CLASS,I-art
2),I-art
THEME-,I-art
STAY,I-art
SAFE,I-art
PARENT,I-art
NAME,I-art
-,I-art
DR,I-art
AMRITA,I-art
JHA,I-art
SCHOOL-,I-art
VENKATESHWAR,B-org
INTERNATIONAL,I-org
SCHOOL,I-org
SECTOR,I-art
10,I-tim
DWARKA,B-geo
NEW,I-geo
DELHI,I-geo
110075,I-geo
pic.twitter.com/kpWjX3CnID,O
#CRPFPosterChallenge,O
@crpfindia,O
Name:,B-org
Arindita,I-org
Biswas,I-org
Class:,I-org
9,I-org
School:,I-org
Venkateshwar,I-org
International,I-org
"School,",I-org
"sector-10,",I-org
"Dwarka,",B-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Father's,I-org
Name:,I-org
Anjan,I-org
Biswas,I-org
Mother's,I-org
Name:,I-org
Ruma,I-org
Biswas,I-org
Topic:,I-org
Life,I-org
during,O
COVID,O
pic.twitter.com/ME4zy3lKU6,O
#CRPFPosterChallenge,O
@crpfindia,O
Student:,B-org
Prasiddhi,I-org
Rastogi,I-org
Parent:,I-org
Neeru,I-org
Rastogi,I-org
Class:,I-org
VII,I-org
(Category,I-org
II),I-org
Theme:,I-org
Life,I-org
During,I-org
Covid,I-org
School:,I-org
Venkateshwara,I-org
International,I-org
"School,",I-org
Dwarka,B-geo
"Sector-10,",O
New,B-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
pic.twitter.com/5ga44jJBFD,O
Covid,B-per
Poster,I-per
Challenge.,I-per
Poster,I-per
by,O
Arav,B-per
Bisht,I-per
class,O
4th,O
student,O
Venkateswar,B-org
International,I-org
School,I-org
Sector,O
10,O
Dwarka,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
@crpfindiapic.twitter.com/VSvQrlsmN7,O
Tentative,O
list,O
of,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hotspots,O
to,O
be,O
sealed,O
1,O
Entire,O
affected,O
street,O
near,O
Gandhi,B-geo
"Park,",I-geo
Malviya,B-geo
"Nagar,",I-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
2,O
Entire,O
affected,O
street,O
of,O
Gali,B-geo
No,I-geo
"6,",O
L1,B-org
Sangam,B-geo
"Vihar,",I-geo
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
3,I-org
Shahajahanabad,I-org
"society,",O
Plot,B-geo
No,I-geo
"1,",O
Sector,O
"11,",O
Dwarka,B-geo
4,O
Dinpur,B-geo
Village,I-geo
Dwarka,I-geo
sector,O
-11,O
situated,O
Shahjahanabad,B-geo
Apartments,I-geo
have,O
been,O
declared,O
as,O
‘containment,O
zone’,O
by,O
the,O
Delhi,B-org
Government.,I-org
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
|,O
Latest,O
updates,O
https://www.mapsofindia.com/my-india/health/just-facts-coronavirus-in-india,O
…,O
#coronaupdatesindia,O
#COVID,O
Dwarka,B-geo
sector,O
-11,O
situated,O
Shahjahanabad,B-geo
Apartments,I-geo
have,O
been,O
declared,O
as,O
‘containment,O
zone’,O
by,O
the,O
Delhi,B-org
Government.,I-org
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
|,O
Latest,O
updates,O
https://www.mapsofindia.com/my-india/health/just-facts-coronavirus-in-india,O
…,O
#coronaupdatesindia,O
#COVID,O
Dwarka,B-geo
sector,O
-11,O
situated,O
Shahjahanabad,B-org
Apartments,I-org
have,O
been,O
declared,O
as,O
‘containment,O
zone’,O
by,O
the,O
Delhi,B-org
Government.,I-org
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
|,O
Latest,O
updates,O
https://www.mapsofindia.com/my-india/health/just-facts-coronavirus-in-india,O
…,O
#coronaupdatesindia,O
#COVID,O
#Shahjahanabad,B-geo
society,O
#Dwarka,B-geo
#Delhi,I-geo
sector,I-geo
11,O
plot1,B-geo
is,O
declared,O
#covid...,O
https://youtu.be/n7tRscic4aI,O
via,O
@YouTube,O
LIST,O
OF,O
20,O
SEALED,O
SPOTS,O
IN,O
#DELHI,B-geo
1.Entire,O
effected,O
street,O
near,O
Gandhi,B-org
"Pqrk,",I-org
Malviya,B-geo
"Nagar,",I-geo
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
2.Entire,I-org
effected,O
street,O
of,O
Gali,B-org
No,O
6,O
",",O
L,B-org
1,I-org
Sangam,I-org
"Vihar,",I-org
New,B-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
3.Shahajahanabad,B-geo
"society,",O
plot,O
no,O
"1,",O
Sector,O
"11,",O
Dwarka.,B-geo
4.Dinpur,I-org
Village,I-org
(1/5),O
20,O
hotspot,O
areas,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
to,O
be,O
sealed,O
#COVID,O
1,O
Entire,O
effected,O
street,O
near,O
Gandhi,B-per
"Park,",I-per
Malviya,B-geo
"Nagar,",I-geo
2,O
Entire,O
effected,O
street,O
of,O
Gali,B-org
No,O
6,O
",",O
L,B-org
1,I-org
Sangam,I-org
"Vihar,",I-org
3,I-org
Shahajahanabad,B-geo
"society,",I-geo
plot,I-geo
no,I-geo
"1,",O
Sector,O
"11,",O
Dwarka.,B-geo
4,O
Dinpur,B-geo
Village,I-geo
5,O
Markaz,B-geo
Masjid,I-geo
and,O
Nizamuddin,B-geo
Basti,I-geo
If,O
hospitals,O
are,O
giving,O
oxygen,O
and,O
paracetamol,O
"only,",O
why,O
hospitals,O
are,O
required.,O
Hospitals,O
don't,O
have,O
beds.,O
Can,O
CM,B-org
Delhi,I-org
take,O
cognizance,O
of,O
Ashirvad,B-geo
hospital,O
",sector",O
12,O
"Dwarka,",B-geo
situated,O
in,O
shopping,O
"complex,",O
converted,O
into,O
Covid,O
19,O
hospital.,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
"Sir,",O
I,O
request,O
you,O
please,O
shift,O
Covid-19,B-geo
hospital,O
from,O
Aayushman,B-org
Hospital,I-org
situated,O
at,O
1to,O
3,O
floors,O
Sector,O
"12,",O
"DWARKA,",B-geo
New,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
where,O
very,O
narrow,O
entry,O
about,O
5,O
feet,O
and,O
medical,O
shop,O
on,O
this,O
entry,O
place.,O
Please,O
take,O
it,O
seriously.,O
Regards,O
"Today,",O
We,O
have,O
Distributed,O
more,O
than,O
300,O
kgs,O
of,O
Raw,B-org
Ration,I-org
to,O
Needy,O
People,O
in,O
Dwarka,B-geo
Sector,I-geo
12,O
Slum,B-org
Areas/Juggis..,I-org
COVID-19.,I-org
#Empoweringhumanity,I-org
#poor,O
#CoronaVirus,O
#Indialockdown,O
#food,O
#ration,O
#delhi,B-geo
pic.twitter.com/ATeJ2X5TIr,O
@crpfindia,O
Hello,B-geo
good,O
evening,O
Sir/Madam,B-per
Kindly,I-per
find,O
attached,O
poster,O
regarding,O
COVID-19,O
poster,O
challenge.,O
This,O
is,O
Nuransh,B-org
Kaushik,I-org
S/o,I-org
Dr.Chandra,I-org
Shekhar,I-org
kaushik,I-org
Class-3rd-Rock,I-org
View,I-org
Venkateshwar,B-org
International,I-org
"School,Dwarka",I-org
Sector-12,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
Thanks,O
pic.twitter.com/qniMurRshI,O
New,O
unoccupied,O
large,O
buildings,O
one,O
of,O
Election,B-org
Commission,I-org
of,I-org
India,B-geo
and,O
another,O
of,O
UP,B-org
State,I-org
Govt.lying,O
unoccupied,O
in,O
Dwarka,B-geo
Sector,I-geo
"13,",O
New,B-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
Can,I-org
be,O
considered,O
for,O
COVID,B-org
facility.,O
@PMOIndia,O
@MoHFW_INDIA,O
@drharshvardhan,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
@DelhiVsCorona,O
@esichq,O
Corona,B-geo
warrior,O
Hari,B-org
"Rajesh,",I-org
Nursing,I-org
"Asstt.,",I-org
ESI,I-org
"Hospital,",I-org
Jhilmil,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
has,O
been,O
left,O
to,O
fend,O
for,O
"himself,",O
didn't,O
get,O
any,O
call,O
from,O
doctor.,O
Pregnant,O
wife,O
&,O
3,O
yr,O
old,O
son,O
of,O
patient,O
is,O
on,O
high,O
risk,O
but,O
no,O
covid,O
test,O
is,O
being,O
done,O
for,O
them.,O
Plz,O
help!!!,O
pic.twitter.com/2K6avBj5zf,O
Aap,O
khud,O
bhi,O
soch,O
sakte,O
hai,O
ki,O
agar,O
Delhi,B-geo
ke,O
almost,O
sabhi,O
hospitals,O
and,O
Covid-19,B-org
patients,O
ki,O
haalat,O
esi,O
hoti,O
to,O
aaj,O
sabse,O
zyada,O
Delhi,B-geo
me,O
ilaaj,O
krwane,O
aaye,O
logo,O
ki,O
deaths,O
hoti,O
jo,O
ki,O
nahi,O
hai.,O
Sir,O
ye,O
thik,O
hai,O
magar,O
noida,B-geo
mai,O
kaun,O
sa,O
covid,O
19,O
hospital,O
banaya,O
hai,O
jankari,O
dege,O
to,O
aapka,O
aabhar,O
hoga,O
noida,B-geo
ke,O
garibo,O
par,O
kiuki,O
esi,O
bhi,O
mana,O
kar,O
deti,O
hai,O
admission,O
ko,O
kailash,O
bhi,O
nahi,O
leta.,O
Delhi,B-geo
mai,I-per
kejariwal,O
ji,O
ne,O
mana,O
kar,O
diya,O
ab,O
bataiye,O
kaha,O
jaye,O
garib.,O
Sir,O
please,O
answer.,O
Emergency,O
calls,O
for,O
emergent,O
measures.,O
In,O
"Delhi,",B-geo
there,O
are,O
well,O
equipped,O
armed,O
&,O
paramilitary,O
forces,O
"hospitals,",O
"Railway,",O
ESI,B-org
&,I-org
Police,I-org
"hosp.,",O
TB,B-org
&,I-org
Cancer,I-org
"Hosp.,",I-org
Dental,I-org
&,I-org
mental,I-org
"disease,",I-org
Ortho,I-org
"hosp.,",O
"Homeo,",B-per
"Ayurved,",I-per
Yoga,I-per
&,O
many,O
others.,O
Why,O
not,O
open,O
these,O
for,O
public,O
for,O
covid,O
admit.,O
doctors,O
and,O
anaesthesia,O
technician,O
from,O
ESI,B-org
"hospital,",O
"Basaidarapur,",B-geo
new,I-geo
delhi,I-geo
were,O
not,O
allowed,O
to,O
enter,O
in,O
their,O
hostel,O
situated,O
in,O
between,O
staff,O
quarters,O
today.,O
Some,O
of,O
them,O
were,O
posted,O
in,O
COVID,O
area,O
#DelhiPolice,B-org
#NDTVExclusive,O
#ZEENews,O
#ArvindKejriwal,O
#esic,O
#esicheadquarter,O
Goa,B-geo
has,O
22,O
#COVID__19,O
COVID19,O
active,O
positive,O
cases,O
reported.,O
All,O
the,O
patients,O
are,O
admitted,O
in,O
ESI,B-geo
"hospital,",I-geo
Margao.,O
More,O
tests,O
of,O
the,O
passengers,O
that,O
arrived,O
today,B-tim
from,O
Delhi,B-geo
train,O
is,O
underway.,O
pic.twitter.com/hTFt0Yeif4,O
@indian_nurses,O
no,O
n95masks,O
and,O
ppe,O
kit,O
being,O
provided,O
to,O
nurses,O
working,O
in,O
esi,O
hospital,O
okhla,B-geo
phase,I-geo
1,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
.,O
One,O
staff,O
nurse,O
became,O
covid,O
positive,O
due,O
to,O
negligence,O
of,O
administration,O
@LabourMinistry,O
sir,O
nurses,O
working,O
in,O
ESI,B-geo
HOSPITAL,I-geo
OKHLA,I-geo
phase,I-geo
2,O
New,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
are,O
not,O
being,O
provided,O
with,O
n95,O
masks,O
&,O
ppe,O
kits.,O
One,O
nurse,O
tested,O
positive,O
for,O
covid,O
but,O
still,O
no,O
measures,O
taken,O
by,O
administration,O
for,O
nurse’s,O
safety,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
sir,O
I,O
request,O
you,O
ki,O
jo,O
hospitals,O
hai,O
delhi,B-geo
ke,O
waha,O
admit,O
ni,O
kar,O
rahe,O
normal,O
case,O
bhi,O
us,O
wajah,O
se,O
log,O
mar,O
rahe,O
hai,O
esi,O
he,O
chalta,O
raha,O
to,O
covid,O
19,O
se,O
kam,O
aur,O
natural,O
death,O
zyada,O
hongi,O
to,O
sir,O
request,O
hai,O
meri,O
apse,O
ki,O
kuchh,O
kariye..,O
@dtptraffic,O
"sir,",O
my,O
father,O
having,O
covid,O
-19,O
duty,O
pass,O
which,O
is,O
issued,O
from,O
south,O
delhi.,O
But,O
we,O
are,O
residing,O
in,O
noida,B-geo
currently,O
can,O
he,O
travel,O
from,O
noida,B-geo
to,O
his,O
office(,O
ESI,B-org
hospital,Iorg
"basaidharapur,",B-geo
new,I-geo
delhi),I-geo
As,O
we,O
are,O
very,O
confused.,O
Please,O
suggest,O
@aajtak,O
@chitraaum,O
delhi,B-geo
govt,O
ne,O
mostly,O
hospitals,O
ko,O
covid,O
9,O
hospital,O
declare,O
kr,O
diya,O
lekin,O
bht,O
si,O
esi,O
emergency,O
hai,O
cardic,O
attack.pregnancy.un,O
patients,O
ko,O
hospital,O
nhi,O
lenge.esa,O
to,O
bht,O
he,O
dukhad,O
hai.plz,O
toda,O
soche,O
kya,O
ye,O
thik,O
h?,O
ishpe,O
kch,O
highlight,O
kre.taki,O
govt,O
solutions,O
nikle.,O
pic.twitter.com/8D3NJQhTVm,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
delhi,O
govt,O
ne,O
mostly,O
hospitals,O
ko,O
covid,O
9,O
hospitals,O
declare,O
kr,O
diya,O
.lekin,O
bht,O
si,O
esi,O
emergency,O
hai,O
cardic,O
attack.pregnancy.etc,O
un,O
patients,O
ko,O
hospital,O
nhi,O
lenge.esa,O
to,O
bht,O
he,O
dukhad,O
hai.plz,O
toda,O
soche,O
kya,O
ye,O
thik,O
h?,O
plz,O
sir,O
kch,O
solutions,O
nikle.,O
@chitraaum,O
delhi,B-geo
govt,O
ne,O
mostly,O
hospitals,O
ko,O
covid,O
9,O
hospitals,O
declare,O
kr,O
diya,O
.lekin,O
bht,O
si,O
esi,O
emergency,O
hai,O
cardic,O
attack.pregnancy.etc,O
un,O
patients,O
ko,O
hospital,O
nhi,O
lenge.esa,O
to,O
bht,O
he,O
dukhad,O
hai.plz,O
toda,O
soche,O
kya,O
ye,O
thik,O
h?,O
ishpe,O
kch,O
highlight,O
kre.taki,O
govt,O
solutions,O
nikle.,O
@LtGovDelhi,O
gm,O
sir,O
delhi,O
govt,O
ne,O
mostly,O
hospitals,O
ko,O
covid,O
9,O
hospitals,O
declare,O
kr,O
diya,O
.lekin,O
bht,O
si,O
esi,O
emergency,O
hai,O
like.cardic,O
attact.pregnancy.etc,O
un,O
patients,O
ko,O
hospital,O
nhi,O
lenge.esa,O
to,O
bht,O
he,O
dukhad,O
hai,O
sir.plz,O
toda,O
soche,O
kya,O
ye,O
thik,O
h?.,O
#COVID,B-org
@DCDK9,I-org
has,O
identified,O
41,O
residents,O
from,O
DK,O
who,O
attended,O
Tablighi,B-per
Jamaat,I-per
in,O
New,B-geo
Delhi.,I-geo
Out,I-geo
of,O
these,O
26,O
have,O
been,O
quarantined,O
on,O
Yenepoya,B-geo
Hospital,I-geo
"premises,",O
and,O
2,O
at,O
ESI,B-geo
hospital.,I-geo
@compolmlr,O
@spdkpolice,O
@mangalurupolice,O
@bharathshetty_y,O
@DgpKarnataka,O
@BSBommai,O
@ANI,O
@CPDelhi,O
Hon'ble,O
Sir,B-geo
Deen,I-geo
Bandhu,I-geo
Public,I-geo
School,I-geo
Ghevra,I-geo
Delhi-81,I-geo
has,O
appointed,O
a,O
fool,O
secretary,O
Bhupender,B-per
Singh,I-per
Ahlawat,I-per
who,O
is,O
compelling,O
teachers,O
of,O
the,O
school,O
to,O
come,O
to,O
school,O
during,O
this,O
pandemic,O
COVID-19,O
inspite,O
of,O
ur,O
orders.,O
Plz,O
remove,O
him,O
from,O
his,O
post,O
as,O
he,O
is,O
misusing,O
his,O
powers.,O
Hon'ble,O
Manish,B-org
Sisodia,I-org
"Sir,",I-org
inspite,O
of,O
ur,O
"orders,",O
Secretary,O
of,O
Deen,B-geo
Bandhu,I-geo
Public,I-geo
School,I-geo
Ghevra,I-geo
Delhi-81,I-geo
is,O
compelling,O
teachers,O
of,O
come,O
to,O
school,O
during,O
this,O
pandemic,O
COVID-19.,B-org
Plz,I-org
remove,O
Him,O
from,O
his,O
post,O
immediately,O
sir..,O
@CPDelhi,O
"Sir,",O
I,O
"am,a",O
"student,living",O
in,O
Ghitorni,B-geo
"delhi-30,I",O
am,O
facing,O
a,O
lot,O
of,O
problem,O
here,O
due,O
to,O
covid,O
"19,I",B-org
want,O
to,O
go,O
my,O
"home(saharsa,bihar).I",O
am,O
keep,O
trying,O
to,O
book,O
ticket,O
from,O
last,O
few,B-tim
days,O
but,O
unfortunately,O
couldn’t.Plz,O
help,O
me,O
to,O
find,O
out,O
solution.,O
Mob.,B-per
No.,I-per
9762681424,O
@narendramodi,O
I,O
was,O
working,O
in,O
IO,B-org
Digital,I-org
from,O
last,O
3,B-tim
years,O
which,O
is,O
based,O
in,O
ghitorni,B-geo
new,I-geo
"delhi,",I-geo
after,O
lockdown,O
i,O
was,O
working,O
from,O
home,O
and,O
given,O
my,O
100%,O
before,B-tim
15,I-tim
days,O
back,O
company,O
fired,O
me,O
due,O
to,O
covid,O
19,O
now,O
I,O
don't,O
have,O
source,O
of,O
income,O
to,O
survive,O
my,O
no.,O
7982745308,O
help,O
@ArvindKejriwal,O
I,O
was,O
working,O
in,O
IO,B-org
Digital,I-org
from,O
last,O
3,B-tim
years,O
which,O
is,O
based,O
in,O
ghitorni,B-geo
new,I-geo
"delhi,",I-geo
after,O
lockdown,O
i,O
was,O
working,O
from,O
home,O
and,O
given,O
my,O
100%,O
before,B-tim
15,I-tim
days,O
back,O
company,O
fired,O
me,O
due,O
to,O
covid,O
19,O
now,O
I,O
don't,O
have,O
source,O
of,O
income,O
to,O
survive,O
my,O
no.,O
7982745308,O
help,O
Covid,O
in,O
@DGSSB:,O
8,O
tests,O
positive,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
for,O
"covid-19,",O
taking,O
the,O
no,O
of,O
personnel,O
infected,O
with,O
coronavirus,O
to,O
13,O
They,O
are,O
from,O
25,O
battalion,O
SSB,O
deployed,O
in,O
Ghitorni.,B-geo
Dear,O
"sir,",O
Please,O
help,O
us.,O
Do,O
mahine,O
ho,O
gaye,O
jhelte,O
jhelte,O
ab,O
kuch,O
kripa,O
kijiye,O
aap,O
log,O
kuch,O
kariye.,O
We,O
need,O
help.,O
I,O
am,O
living,O
alone,O
in,O
ghitorni,B-geo
new,I-geo
Delhi,I-geo
and,O
pls,O
send,O
us,O
back,O
hardoi,B-geo
@dmhardoi,O
@Uppolice#COVID__19,O
#Kejriwal,B-org
Please,I-org
help,O
Hindu,B-org
Rights,I-org
Watch,I-org
Activities,I-org
Report,I-org
in,O
Covid,B-geo
19,O
pandemic,O
crisis,O
:,O
From,B-tim
6,I-tim
June,I-tim
2020,I-tim
to,I-tim
12,I-tim
June,I-tim
2020,I-tim
:,I-tim
27,I-tim
Copies,I-tim
of,O
Shrimadbhagavat,B-org
Gita,I-org
have,O
distributed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-geo
riots,O
affected,O
area,O
of,O
Gokulpuri,B-geo
#DelhiRiots,O
#delhiriots2020pic.twitter.com/W1shx9FSLm,O
Golfing,O
in,O
the,O
times,O
of,O
#COVID__19,B-org
..,O
*PLEASE,O
do,O
not,O
touch,O
the,O
flag*,O
#SocialDistancing,O
Via,B-geo
@VedamJaishankar,O
@kartikmurali,O
please,O
let,O
us,O
know,O
if,O
the,O
Delhi,B-geo
Golf,I-geo
Course,I-geo
has,O
something,O
good,O
like,O
this..,O
https://twitter.com/VedamJaishankar/status/1270354982307414018,O
…,O
New,B-org
‘Covid,I-org
rules’:,I-org
"Jeev,",I-org
"Ajeetesh,",I-org
Sharma,I-org
back,O
of,O
the,O
golf,O
course;,O
maintain,O
social,O
distancing,O
The,O
golfers,O
are,O
back.,O
From,O
Chandigarh,B-geo
to,O
Delhi,B-geo
to,O
"Bengaluru,",B-geo
they,O
are,O
back,O
on,O
the,O
course,O
and,O
swinging,O
away,O
but,O
with,O
a,O
new,O
set,O
of,O
Covid-19,B-geo
rules,O
in,O
the,O
Why,O
delhi,O
Government,O
reduce,O
testing,O
for,O
Covid,B-org
patient,O
at,O
least,O
it,O
should,O
be,O
done,O
for,O
direct,O
contact,O
person,O
for,O
breaking,O
chain,O
of,O
corona,O
it's,O
very,O
serious,O
issue,O
and,O
it's,O
became,O
harauble,O
for,O
GOVIND,B-geo
PURI,I-geo
KALKAJI,I-geo
Area,I-geo
Why,O
delhi,B-org
Government,I-org
reduce,O
testing,O
for,O
Covid,B-org
patient,O
at,O
least,O
it,O
should,O
be,O
done,O
for,O
direct,O
contact,O
person,O
for,O
breaking,O
chain,O
of,O
corona,O
it's,O
very,O
serious,O
issue,O
and,O
it's,O
became,O
harauble,O
for,O
GOVIND,B-geo
PURI,I-geo
KALKAJI,I-geo
Area,I-geo
Why,O
delhi,B-org
Government,I-org
reduce,O
testing,O
for,O
Covid,B-org
patient,O
at,O
least,O
it,O
should,O
be,O
done,O
for,O
direct,O
contact,O
person,O
for,O
breaking,O
chain,O
of,O
corona,O
it's,O
very,O
serious,O
issue,O
and,O
it's,O
became,O
harauble,O
for,O
GOVIND,B-geo
PURI,I-geo
KALKAJI,I-geo
Area,I-geo
Why,O
delhi,B-org
Government,I-org
reduce,O
testing,O
for,O
Covid,B-org
patient,O
at,O
least,O
it,O
should,O
be,O
done,O
for,O
direct,O
contact,O
person,O
for,O
breaking,O
chain,O
of,O
corona,O
it's,O
very,O
serious,O
issue,O
and,O
it's,O
became,O
harauble,O
for,O
GOVIND,B-geo
PURI,I-geo
KALKAJI,I-geo
Area,I-geo
Why,O
delhi,B-org
Government,I-org
reduce,O
testing,O
for,O
Covid,B-org
patient,O
at,O
least,O
it,O
should,O
be,O
done,O
for,O
direct,O
contact,O
person,O
for,O
breaking,O
chain,O
of,O
corona,O
it's,O
very,O
serious,O
issue,O
and,O
it's,O
became,O
harauble,O
for,O
GOVIND,B-geo
PURI,I-geo
KALKAJI,I-geo
Area,I-geo
Dear,B-per
Atishi,I-per
ma'am,O
We,O
are,O
leaving,O
in,O
GOVIND,B-geo
PURI,I-geo
KALKAJI,O
South,B-geo
Delhi,I-geo
this,O
your,O
consideration,O
in,O
our,O
area,O
there,O
in,O
one,O
Covid,B-org
positive,O
patient,O
but,O
adminstration,O
is,O
not,O
taking,O
necessary,O
action,O
even,O
his,O
family,O
members,O
are,O
under,O
denger,O
kindly,O
take,O
the,O
necessary,O
action,O
Regards,B-per
Mukesh,I-per
Dear,B-per
Atishi,I-per
ma'am,O
We,O
are,O
leaving,O
in,O
GOVIND,B-geo
PURI,I-geo
KALKAJI,O
