Sentence #0,
@,O
garimaguptabjp,O
@,O
adeshguptabjp,O
@,O
MCDdelhi,O
@,O
narendramodi,O
@,O
PMOIndia,O
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,B-PER
@,O
SatyendarJain,O
This,O
is,O
the,O
situation,O
of,O
Mahatma,B-LOC
Gandhi,I-LOC
Road,I-LOC
Adarsh,B-LOC
Nagar,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
33,B-MISC
from,O
past,B-TIM
1,I-TIM
month,I-TIM
authority,O
waiting,O
for,O
some,O
accident,O
or,O
for,O
election,O
time,O
to,O
come,O
pic.twitter.com/hk6JaMBeJ0,O
Sentence #1,
@,O
Delhi,B-ORG
police,I-ORG
Adarsh,B-LOC
Nagar,I-LOC
can,O
we,O
do,O
something,O
for,O
youth,O
driving,O
bikes,O
without,O
helmets,O
and,O
unauthorised,O
parking,O
.,O
Accident,O
in,O
waiting,O
Sentence #2,
@,O
Adarsh,B-LOC
Nagar,I-LOC
Delhi,B-ORG
police,I-ORG
.,O
Can,O
we,O
check,O
young,O
children,O
driving,O
bikes,O
without,O
helmets,O
and,O
unauthorised,O
car,O
parking,O
.,O
Accident,O
in,O
waiting,O
.,O
Sentence #3,
Respect,O
.,O
Docs,O
at,O
aiims,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
removed,O
&,O
saved,O
life,O
of,O
a,O
man,O
who,O
was,O
victim,O
of,O
an,O
accident,O
at,O
mathura,O
&,O
had,O
a,O
iron,O
rod,O
lodged,O
in,O
his,O
brain,O
.,O
Sentence #4,
A,O
rare,O
successful,O
surgery,O
performed,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
A,O
30,B-TIM
year,O
old,O
man,O
during,O
his,O
motor,O
bike,O
accident,O
was,O
thrown,O
o,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/bv3It3,O
Sentence #5,
Aiims,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
is,O
clogged,O
due,O
to,O
some,O
accident,O
#,O
delhi,O
#,O
traffic,O
via,O
@,O
meerasapra,O
Sentence #6,
Aiims,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
is,O
clogged,O
due,O
to,O
some,O
accident,O
#,O
delhi,O
#,O
traffic,O
Sentence #7,
RT,O
@,O
aanteladda,O
:,O
Hunting,O
for,O
a,O
good,O
driver,O
.,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
AIIMS,I-LOC
area,I-LOC
.,O
Our,O
driver,O
had,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
his,O
bike,O
broken,O
kneecap,O
.,O
Sentence #8,
Hunting,O
for,O
a,O
good,O
driver,O
.,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
AIIMS,I-LOC
area,I-LOC
.,O
Our,O
driver,O
had,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
his,O
bike,O
broken,O
kneecap,O
.,O
Sentence #9,
Hit,O
&,O
run,O
accident,O
on,O
aiims,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
..,O
drive,O
carefully,O
delhi,O
people,O
..,O
humble,O
request,O
...,O
there,O
are,O
lives,O
at,O
risk,O
..,O
pic.twitter.com/bYAJjdz9bz,O
Sentence #10,
Can,O
somebody,O
tell,O
me,O
why,O
#,O
rape,O
and,O
#,O
accident,O
victims,O
are,O
taken,O
to,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Trauma,I-LOC
Centre,I-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
when,O
there,O
are,O
many,O
hospitals,O
on,O
the,O
way,O
?,O
Sentence #11,
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
-,O
Traffic,O
movement,O
is,O
slow,O
on,O
Ring,B-LOC
Road,I-LOC
AIIMS,B-LOC
twds,O
Hyaat,B-ORG
..,O
accident,O
between,O
few,O
cars,O
at,O
Bhikaji,B-LOC
Cama,I-LOC
Place,I-LOC
...,O
Sentence #12,
Y'day,O
met,O
an,O
accident,O
admitted,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
lets,O
c,O
wat,O
happen,O
?,O
Plz,O
pray,O
.,O
Sentence #13,
Urgent,O
requirement,O
of,O
Blood,O
AB,O
+ve,O
group,O
for,O
an,O
accident,O
victim,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
If,O
willing,O
to,O
donate,O
please,O
contact,O
Biju,O
9716680598,O
Sentence #14,
Bengali,O
film,O
director,O
#,O
SrijitMukherji,B-PER
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Admitted,O
to,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
@,O
FocusNewsIndia,O
Sentence #15,
#,O
Bengali,O
film,O
director,O
#,O
SrijitMukherji,B-PER
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Admitted,O
to,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
pic.twitter.com/TQFMy0VDzm,O
Sentence #16,
Bengali,O
film,O
director,O
Srijit,B-PER
Mukherji,I-PER
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
@,O
htTweets,O
Sentence #17,
#,O
Delhi,B-PER
Need,O
3,O
AB-ve,O
Blood,O
for,O
accident,O
case,O
At,O
AIIMS,B-ORG
Hosp.,I-ORG
Call,O
9891167896,O
via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
cc,O
@,O
WeAreNewDelhi,O
@,O
RTDelhi,O
#,O
iCanSaveLife,O
Sentence #18,
@,O
bhogleharsha,O
@,O
BloodDonorsIn,O
#,O
Delhi,B-PER
Need,O
3,O
units,O
AB-,O
blood,O
At,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
For,O
accident,O
case,O
Call,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//tmi.me/1eWNzw,O
Sentence #19,
#,O
Delhi,B-PER
Need,O
3,O
units,O
AB-,O
blood,O
At,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
For,O
accident,O
case,O
Call,O
9891167896,O
.,O
16Jan,B-TIM
.,O
via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
Sentence #20,
@,O
BloodDonorsIn,O
#,O
Delhi,B-PER
Need,O
3,O
units,O
AB-,O
blood,O
At,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
For,O
accident,O
case,O
Call,O
9891167896,O
.,O
16Jan,B-TIM
.,O
via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
Sentence #21,
#,O
Delhi,B-PER
Need,O
3,O
units,O
AB-,O
blood,O
At,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
For,O
accident,O
case,O
Call,O
9891167896,O
.,O
16Jan,B-TIM
.,O
via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
Sentence #22,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Emergency,O
Need,O
3,O
AB-ve,O
#,O
blood,O
@,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
for,O
accident,O
case,O
.,O
Call,O
9891167896,O
via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
pls,O
RT,O
@,O
tavleen_singh,O
Sentence #23,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Emergency,O
Need,O
3,O
AB-ve,O
#,O
blood,O
@,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
for,O
accident,O
case,O
.,O
Call,O
9891167896,O
#,O
Bloodaid,O
via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
cc,O
@,O
tajinderbagga,O
@,O
upma23,O
Sentence #24,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Emergency,O
Need,O
3,O
AB-ve,O
#,O
blood,O
@,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
for,O
accident,O
case,O
.,O
Call,O
9891167896,O
#,O
Bloodaid,O
via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
cc,O
@,O
Raheelk,O
@,O
tajinderbagg,O
Sentence #25,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
-,O
10,B-MISC
victims,O
of,O
Defence,B-LOC
Colony,I-LOC
accident,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1wMCfep,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1mKbocU,O
Sentence #26,
Hot,O
News,O
:,O
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
The,O
accident,O
occured,O
when,O
a,O
Honda,B-ORG
City,O
car,O
was,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//dlvr.it/1Fc8Fp,O
Sentence #27,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
The,O
accident,O
occured,O
when,O
a,O
Honda,B-LOC
City,O
car,O
was,O
hit,O
from,O
behind,O
by,O
a,O
Swift,B-ORG
D,I-ORG
...,O
Sentence #28,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
The,O
accident,O
occured,O
when,O
a,O
Honda,O
City,O
car,O
was,O
hit,O
fro,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/yTl99b,O
Sentence #29,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
The,O
accident,O
occured,O
when,O
a,O
Honda,B-ORG
City,O
car,O
was,O
hit,O
fro,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/zBl6Zc,O
Sentence #30,
#,O
indianews,O
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
The,O
accident,O
occured,O
when,O
a,O
Honda,B-ORG
Cit,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/wGvM7n,O
#,O
news,O
Sentence #31,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
morning,I-TIM
.,O
According,O
to,O
...,O
Sentence #32,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
m,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/wdVxR2,O
Sentence #33,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
morning,I-TIM
.,O
According,O
to,O
...,O
Sentence #34,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
morning,I-TIM
.,O
According,O
to,O
...,O
Sentence #35,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
m,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//adf.ly/5o63U,O
Sentence #36,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
morning,I-TIM
.,O
According,O
to,O
...,O
Sentence #37,
#,O
News,O
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
t,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/ylTtCS,O
Sentence #38,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
m,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/wWsLFu,O
Sentence #39,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
m,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/A1pOn8,O
Sentence #40,
ndtv,O
:,O
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
t,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/A1pOn8,O
Sentence #41,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
m,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/wWsLFu,O
Sentence #42,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
m,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/wWsLFu,O
Sentence #43,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
m,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/xtXuU7,O
Sentence #44,
Pregnant,O
woman,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
official,O
killed,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
crash,O
:,O
Two,O
people,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
here,O
today,B-TIM
m,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/xtXuU7,O
Sentence #45,
Organs,O
of,O
youth,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
save,O
4,O
lives,O
:,O
NEW,B-LOC
DELHI,I-LOC
:,O
Doctors,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
managed,O
to,O
save,O
lives,O
of,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//donatelifeindia.org/,O
?,O
p=3181,O
Sentence #46,
Manish,B-PER
&,O
Shaily,B-PER
with,O
help,O
from,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
and,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Trauma,I-LOC
center,I-LOC
staff,O
saved,O
the,O
lives,O
of,O
2,O
road,O
accident,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/1czPXH2b2,O
Sentence #47,
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
ji,I-PER
was,O
presently,O
the,O
Union,B-ORG
Rural,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Minister,B-PER
.,O
He,O
passed,O
away,O
due,O
to,O
a,O
heart,O
attack,O
after,O
the,O
accident,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #48,
BJP,B-ORG
leader,O
and,O
Union,B-ORG
Minister,I-ORG
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
dies,O
in,O
an,O
accident,O
.,O
Press,O
release,O
by,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gives,O
out,O
detail,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/4r04KSquD1,O
Sentence #49,
RIP,O
@,O
the_hindu,O
:,O
Indian,B-ORG
Rural,I-ORG
Development,I-ORG
Minister,B-PER
#,O
GopinathMunde,B-PER
passes,O
away,O
at,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
trauma,I-LOC
centre,I-LOC
after,O
a,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
road,I-LOC
accident,O
.,O
Sentence #50,
union,B-ORG
minister,B-PER
gopinadh,B-PER
munde,I-PER
...,O
met,O
an,O
accident,O
near,O
igi,B-LOC
delhi,B-LOC
and,O
expired,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
......,O
Sentence #51,
``,O
@,O
Oneindia,O
:,O
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
passes,O
away,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
after,O
fatal,O
accident,O
.,O
RIP,O
'',O
Sentence #52,
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
injured,O
in,O
road,I-LOC
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
;,O
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//ift.tt/1kDrfXA,O
#,O
india,B-LOC
Sentence #53,
``,O
Rural,O
Development,O
Minister,O
#,O
GopinathMunde,B-PER
passes,O
away,O
at,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
trauma,I-LOC
centre,I-LOC
after,O
suffering,O
severe,O
head,O
injuries,O
in,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
road,O
accident,O
.,O
Sentence #54,
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
meets,O
with,O
accident,O
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
airport,I-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/6EYbxYQQX,O
Sentence #55,
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
meets,O
with,O
accident,O
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
airport,I-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/1uhLmTtd9,O
Sentence #56,
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
meets,O
with,O
accident,O
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
airport,I-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/19W9ImW9K,O
Sentence #57,
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
meets,O
with,O
accident,O
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
airport,I-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//disq.us/8iolgn,O
Sentence #58,
#,O
BreakingNews,O
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
;,O
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1ks4Lxo,O
Sentence #59,
RT-,O
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
;,O
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
:,O
Union,O
rural,O
development,O
ministe,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1mLM1HI,O
#,O
News,O
Sentence #60,
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
meets,O
with,O
accident,O
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
airport,I-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/6xwzUPxs5,O
Sentence #61,
News,O
Flash,O
:,O
Rural,O
Development,O
Minister,O
#,O
GopinathMunde,B-PER
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
trauma,I-LOC
centre,I-LOC
Sentence #62,
Union,B-MISC
minister,O
Gopinath,B-PER
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
Munde,B-PER
's,O
death,O
.,O
Morning,O
car,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Were,O
subsequently,O
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #63,
Check,O
this,O
@,O
SuryaRay,B-PER
Gopinath,I-PER
Munde,I-PER
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
;,O
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
:,O
Union,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//dlvr.it/5sHmyn,O
#,O
SuryaRay,B-PER
#,O
India,B-LOC
Sentence #64,
Gopinath,B-PER
Munde,I-PER
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
;,O
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//dlvr.it/5sHmxp,O
#,O
News,O
Sentence #65,
this,O
accident,O
also,O
reminds,O
us,O
that,O
more,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
like,O
inst,O
.,O
need,O
to,O
be,O
built,O
in,O
every,O
state,O
!,O
!,O
Bhubaneswar,B-LOC
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
is,O
too,O
far,O
!,O
Sentence #66,
#,O
TRLFinalMatch,O
pyare,O
papaji,O
mere,O
dost,O
ka,O
accident,O
ho,O
gya,O
pitaji,O
rahmat,O
karna,O
ji,O
aiims,B-LOC
delhi,B-LOC
troma,B-LOC
center,I-LOC
me,O
admit,O
h,O
ji.plz,O
Sentence #67,
:,O
This,O
is,O
a,O
good,O
idea,O
.,O
ROAD,B-MISC
ACCIDENT,I-MISC
DATA,I-MISC
be,O
shown,O
ON,O
A,O
GIANT,O
SCREEN,O
ON,O
LINE,O
IN,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
X-ING,O
CON,O
.,O
PL.,O
DELHI,B-LOC
GATE,I-LOC
DHOLA,B-LOC
KUAN,I-LOC
ITO,B-LOC
ISBT,B-LOC
Sentence #68,
@,O
narendramodi,B-PER
sir,O
Rajesh,B-LOC
is,O
waiting,O
at,O
Aiims,B-LOC
trauma,I-LOC
centre,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
No.,I-LOC
one,O
listening.he,O
has,O
gone,O
through,O
fatal,O
accident,O
.,O
Sentence #69,
@,O
narendramodi,O
sir,O
Rajesh,B-LOC
jha,I-PER
will,O
die,O
if,O
nt,O
given,O
immediate,O
treatment,O
.,O
he,O
has,O
gone,O
fatal,O
accident,O
.,O
waiting,O
at,O
Aiims,B-LOC
trauma,I-LOC
centre,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #70,
@,O
JPNadda,O
pl,O
say,O
Aiims,B-LOC
trauma,I-LOC
centre,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
to,O
admit,O
vikash,B-PER
jha,I-PER
.,O
he,O
has,O
gone,O
through,O
fatal,O
accident,O
.,O
no,O
one,O
listening,O
there,O
.,O
pl,O
save,O
his,O
life,O
Sentence #71,
@,O
JPNadda,O
sir,O
vikash,B-PER
jha,I-PER
is,O
very,O
serious,O
.,O
fatal,O
accident,O
.,O
but,O
Aiims,B-LOC
trauma,I-LOC
centre,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
nt,O
giving,O
ICU,O
.,O
pl,O
save,O
his,O
life,O
Sentence #72,
Union,B-MISC
minister,B-MISC
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
rushed,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
after,O
he,O
met,O
with,O
accident,O
in,O
south,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
(,O
PTI,O
),O
-,O
via,O
Times,B-ORG
Now,I-ORG
App,O
http,O
:,O
//web.timesnowmobile.com/getapp,O
Sentence #73,
Union,B-MISC
minister,I-MISC
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
rushed,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
after,O
he,O
met,O
with,O
accident,O
in,O
south,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
-,I-LOC
PTI,O
pic.twitter.com/cXePsdbqxx,O
Sentence #74,
Union,O
minister,O
@,O
SuPriyoBabul,O
rushed,O
to,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
after,O
he,O
met,O
with,O
#,O
accident,O
in,O
south,B-LOC
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
-,O
PTI,O
pic.twitter.com/bCVuBt3VXJ,O
Sentence #75,
Union,O
minister,O
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
rushed,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
after,O
he,O
met,O
with,O
accident,O
in,O
south,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
(,O
PTI,O
),O
#,O
BengalPolls,O
Sentence #76,
Bike-borne,O
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
meets,O
with,O
accident,O
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
:,O
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
May,B-TIM
6,I-TIM
:,O
Union,B-ORG
Minister,I-ORG
Babul,B-PER
Supr,I-PER
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1UFunJy,O
Sentence #77,
Minister,B-MISC
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
Admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
Got,O
injured,O
in,O
an,O
accident,O
in,O
hand,O
http,O
:,O
//ibgnews.com/minister-babul-supriyo-admitted-to-aiimsnew-delhi-got-injured-in-an-accident-in-hand-and-chest-while-riding-a-two-wheeler/,O
via,O
@,O
IBG,B-ORG
News,I-ORG
Sentence #78,
Bike-borne,O
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
meets,O
with,O
accident,O
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
:,O
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
May,B-TIM
6,I-TIM
:,O
Union,B-MISC
Minister,I-MISC
Babul,B-PER
Supr,I-PER
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1UFunJy,O
Sentence #79,
Union,B-MISC
Minister,I-MISC
@,O
SuPriyoBabul,B-PER
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
.,O
Get,O
well,O
soon,O
Dada,O
Sentence #80,
Union,O
Minister,O
@,O
SuPriyoBabul,O
(,O
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
),O
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Sentence #81,
Union,O
minister,O
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
rushed,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
after,O
he,O
met,O
with,O
accident,O
in,O
south,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
-,O
PTI,O
Sentence #82,
Union,B-ORG
Minister,I-ORG
Babul,I-ORG
Supriyo,I-ORG
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Trauma,I-LOC
Centre,I-LOC
he,O
's,O
under,O
observation,O
.,O
Sentence #83,
#,O
Flash,O
:,O
Union,B-MISC
Minister,I-MISC
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Trauma,I-LOC
Centre,I-LOC
he,O
's,O
under,O
observation,O
.,O
Sentence #84,
Union,B-MISC
Minister,I-MISC
Babul,B-PER
Supriyo,I-PER
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
admitted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Trauma,I-LOC
Centre,I-LOC
Sentence #85,
Sir,O
@,O
PiyushGoyalOffc,O
yesterday,O
my,O
uncle,O
had,O
an,O
accident,O
and,O
doctors,O
are,O
referred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
and,O
his,O
economical,O
status,O
is,O
not,O
well,O
so,O
he,O
cant,O
afford,O
private,O
ambulance,O
from,O
Darbhanga,B-LOC
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
if,O
railway,B-ORG
will,O
provide,O
a,O
birth,O
than,O
may,O
be,O
he,O
will,O
get,O
well,O
soon,O
.,O
Sentence #86,
Delhi,B-ORG
police,I-ORG
constable,O
Mr,B-PER
Sandeep,I-PER
Sahi,I-PER
paying,O
tribute,O
to,O
three,O
departed,O
souls,O
of,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
doctors,O
in,O
road,B-LOC
accident,O
on,O
expressway,B-LOC
.,O
He,O
had,O
started,O
Road,B-LOC
safety,O
awareness,O
walk,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/77XJ7PfC0L,O
Sentence #87,
3,O
Delhi-,B-LOC
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
docs,O
#,O
#,O
injured,O
in,O
#,O
accident,O
in,O
#,O
UP,B-LOC
@,O
aiims_newdelhi,O
http,O
:,O
//www.drugtodayonline.com/medical-news/nation/6834-3-delhi-aiims-docs-killed-4-injured-in-accident-in-up.html,O
Sentence #88,
My,O
tribute,O
to,O
all,O
3,O
Doctor,O
of,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
who,O
lost,O
their,O
life,O
in,O
a,O
car,O
accident,O
last,O
night,B-TIM
It,O
is,O
a,O
big,O
damage,O
for,O
for,O
nation,O
.,O
#,O
RIP,O
@,O
drmimranqureshi,O
@,O
DrNeelakshiGswm,O
Sentence #89,
@,O
myogiadityanath,O
yogi,O
g,O
please,O
change,O
yamuna,B-LOC
express,I-LOC
way,O
name,O
khuni,O
(,O
blood,O
),O
road,O
of,O
india,B-LOC
becog,O
17.3.2018,O
.,O
4,O
doctors,O
of,O
aiims,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
dead,O
in,O
road,B-LOC
accident,O
.,O
not,O
only,O
doctor,O
many,O
1000,O
people,O
died,O
.,O
either,O
change,O
name,O
ya,O
close,O
the,O
highway,O
.,O
jindgi,O
ek,O
bar,O
milti,O
h,O
yg,O
Sentence #90,
I,O
does,O
condolence,O
for,O
recently,O
Accident,O
on,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Agra,I-LOC
Road,I-LOC
.,O
death,O
Of,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
doctors,O
...,O
We,O
pray,O
to,O
God,O
for,O
peace,O
Their,O
soul,O
...,O
and,O
does,O
Request,O
to,O
all,O
yunger,O
s,O
Caustion,O
for,O
long,O
Drive,O
..,O
Should,O
be,O
safe,O
Drive,O
...,O
Sentence #91,
The,O
seven,O
resident,O
doctors,O
in,O
the,O
Emergency,B-ORG
Medicine,I-ORG
Department,I-ORG
of,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
were,O
travelling,O
to,O
Agra,B-LOC
from,O
Delhi,B-LOC
in,O
a,O
SUV,B-MISC
to,O
celebrate,O
the,O
birthday,O
of,O
Dr,B-PER
Harshad,I-PER
Wankhade,I-PER
who,O
was,O
also,O
killed,O
in,O
the,O
accident,O
.,O
The,O
SUV,O
rammed,O
into,O
a,O
Canter,O
Sentence #92,
While,O
three,O
doctors,O
died,O
on,O
the,O
spot,O
our,O
Sentence #93,
Three,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
doctors,O
killed,O
in,O
an,O
accident,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
#,O
AIIMSDelhi,B-LOC
#,O
Doctors,O
#,O
EmergencyMedicine,O
#,O
Department,O
#,O
AIIMSDoctorsAccident,O
#,O
AIIMSDoctors,O
#,O
Killed,O
#,O
TragicAccident,O
#,O
RoadAccident,O
#,O
YamunaExpressway,B-LOC
#,O
YamunaExpressHighway,B-LOC
#,O
Mathura,B-LOC
#,O
UttarPradesh,B-LOC
https,O
:,O
//goo.gl/MGyikY,O
Sentence #94,
3,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
doctors,O
injured,O
in,O
a,O
accident,O
while,O
on,O
way,O
to,O
Agra,B-LOC
#,O
Agra,B-LOC
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
YamumaExpressway,B-LOC
https,O
:,O
//fb.me/6BwQqxw8c,O
Sentence #95,
Accident,O
on,O
Yamuna,B-LOC
Expressway,I-LOC
claims,O
lives,O
of,O
3,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
others,O
injured,O
Delhi,B-MISC
Video,I-MISC
https,O
:,O
//delhiinformer.com/49220/accident-on-yamuna-expressway-claims-lives-of-3-aiims-delhi-doctors-4-others-injured-delhi-video/,O
pic.twitter.com/kCPFkJwrMF,O
Sentence #96,
:,O
https,O
:,O
//lalluram.com/,O
?,O
p=63232,O
#,O
Doctors,O
#,O
YamunaExpressway,B-LOC
#,O
Accident,O
#,O
delhi,O
#,O
noida,B-LOC
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
@,O
aiims_newdelhi,O
Sentence #97,
3,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
doctors,O
killed,O
in,O
car,O
accident,O
on,O
Yamuna,B-LOC
expressway,I-LOC
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//dilipsoni.in/3-aiims-doctors-killed-in-car-accident-on-yamuna-expressway-near-delhi/,O
Sentence #98,
Extremely,O
sad,O
.,O
3,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
doctors,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
.,O
Why,O
cant,O
our,O
Govts,B-ORG
bring,O
discipline,O
to,O
roads,O
.,O
Driving,O
is,O
a,O
torture,O
even,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
every,O
single,O
day,O
with,O
people,O
breaking,O
traffic,O
rules,O
with,O
impunity,O
.,O
Sentence #99,
https,O
:,O
//timesofindia.indiatimes.com/videos/city/delhi/3-aiims-doctors-killed-in-accident-on-yamuna-expressway/videoshow/63352357.cms,O
Sentence #100,
Sad,O
&,O
Shocking,O
demise,O
of,O
3,O
&,O
serious,O
injuries,O
to,O
4,O
YOUNG,B-MISC
RESIDENT,I-MISC
DRS,O
of,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
New,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
due,O
to,O
*,O
AVOIDABLE,B-MISC
SILLY,I-MISC
ACCIDENT,I-MISC
*,O
is,O
unbearable,O
loss,O
for,O
entire,O
mankind,O
*,O
May,B-TIM
the,O
departed,O
souls,O
RIP,B-ORG
&,O
those,O
having,O
injuries,O
get,O
well,O
soon,O
*,O
Let,O
's,O
Take,O
care,O
&,O
precautions,O
Sentence #101,
#,O
news,O
#,O
newsapp,O
#,O
indianews,O
#,O
socialnews,O
#,O
worldnews,O
#,O
bangalore,B-LOC
#,O
bengaluru,B-LOC
#,O
chennai,B-LOC
#,O
hyderabad,B-LOC
3,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
doctors,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
on,O
Yamuna,B-LOC
Expressway,I-LOC
-,O
The,O
seven,O
doctors,O
were,O
travelling,O
to,O
Agra,B-LOC
from,O
Delhi,B-LOC
in,O
an,O
SUV,O
which,O
rammed,O
into,O
a,O
canter,O
around,O
2.30a,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//ow.ly/WgcN50gTTU3,O
Sentence #102,
3,O
doctors,O
of,O
emergency,O
medicine,O
dept,O
of,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
were,O
killed,O
on,O
Yamuna,B-LOC
Expressway,I-LOC
while,O
4,O
other,O
doctors,O
were,O
gravely,O
injured,O
in,O
the,O
accident,O
.,O
http,O
:,O
//toi.in/nvcDJa/a24gk,O
Sentence #103,
Retweeted,O
ANI,B-ORG
UP,B-LOC
(,O
@,O
ANINewsUP,O
),O
:,O
Sentence #104,
#,O
UPDATE,O
Three,O
doctors,O
from,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
killed,O
three,O
injured,O
in,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
...,O
https,O
:,O
//fb.me/JdV10lN9,O
Sentence #105,
3,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
doctors,O
enroute,O
to,O
Agra,B-LOC
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
on,O
Yamuna,B-LOC
Expressway,I-LOC
http,O
:,O
//ift.tt/2tZDfoh,O
#,O
Politics,B-PER
Seven,I-PER
doctors,O
of,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
were,O
travelling,O
to,O
Agra,B-LOC
from,O
Delhi,B-LOC
in,O
an,O
SUV,O
which,O
rammed,O
into,O
a,O
canter,O
around,O
2.30,B-TIM
AM,I-TIM
police,O
said,O
.,O
Sentence #106,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Need,O
2,O
units,O
O+,O
#,O
blood,O
@,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
for,O
accident,O
case,O
.,O
Call,O
9456858036,O
#,O
BloodAid,O
via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
cc,O
@,O
TajinderBagga,O
@,O
upma23,O
@,O
ArvindGaur,O
Sentence #107,
Note,O
:,O
Drive,O
safely,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Need,O
2,O
units,O
O+VE,O
blood,O
At,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
For,O
accident,O
case,O
Call,O
Via,O
@,O
Pedal_India,B-LOC
cc,O
@,O
TajinderBagga,O
Sentence #108,
6,O
people,O
severely,O
injured,O
in,O
road,B-LOC
accident,O
on,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/YssGuvPn,O
Sentence #109,
Sir,O
my,O
brother,O
is,O
in,O
critical,O
condition,O
after,O
road,O
accident,O
.,O
our,O
family,O
nds,O
Ur,O
help,O
to,O
shift,O
him,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,O
.,O
plz,O
sir,O
we,O
need,O
Ur,O
support,O
.,O
Sentence #110,
@,O
myogiadityanath,O
my,O
brthr,O
condition,O
is,O
critical,O
after,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
.,O
Our,O
family,O
nds,O
Ur,O
help,O
to,O
shift,O
him,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
frm,O
yatharth,B-LOC
noida,I-LOC
Sentence #111,
Delhi,B-LOC
car,O
accident,O
:,O
Another,O
teen,O
succumbs,O
to,O
injuries,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
taking,O
death,O
toll,O
to,O
four,O
http,O
:,O
//www.awesummly.com/news/3757738,O
#,O
top,O
#,O
newspic.twitter.com/00Rw4jcoEo,O
Sentence #112,
Please,O
send,O
your,O
reporters,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
&,O
check,O
signal,O
free,O
U-Turn,O
to,O
avoid,O
an,O
accident,O
at,O
crossing,O
..,O
Sentence #113,
@,O
nitin_gadkari,O
Sir,O
please,O
find,O
time,O
to,O
visit,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
&,O
discover,O
signal,O
free,O
Uturn,O
with,O
no,O
conflict,O
with,O
right,O
turn,O
&,O
eliminate,O
accident,O
Sentence #114,
@,O
manojsinhabjp,O
I,O
was,O
very,O
suspicious,O
n,O
disturbed,O
abt,O
ur,O
accident,O
near,O
Gorakhpur,B-LOC
N,O
dint,O
feel,O
at,O
ease,O
till,O
u,O
reached,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
1,I-LOC
Sentence #115,
The,O
woman,O
was,O
brought,O
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
after,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
July,B-TIM
28,I-TIM
following,O
the,O
Supreme,B-LOC
Courts,I-LOC
orders,O
.,O
#,O
unnaohttps,O
:,O
//www.blush.me/news/landlords-refuse-to-rent-their-home-to-unnao-rape-survivors-kin-delhi-court-asks-dcw-to-help,O
Sentence #116,
Report,O
:,O
The,O
Unnao,O
rape,O
survivor,O
was,O
discharged,O
on,O
Wednesday,B-TIM
from,O
the,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
where,O
she,O
was,O
admitted,O
after,O
she,O
met,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
sources,O
said,O
.,O
Sentence #117,
https,O
:,O
//www.timesnownews.com/india/article/unnao-rape-survivor-discharged-from-aiims/494852,O
Sentence #118,
#,O
UnnaoRapeCase,O
:,O
The,O
Unnao,O
rape,O
survivor,O
was,O
discharged,O
from,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
where,O
she,O
underwent,O
treatment,O
following,O
a,O
car,O
accident,O
sources,O
said,O
on,O
Wednesday,B-TIM
.,O
#,O
UnnaoRapeSurvivor,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
CRPF,B-ORG
@,O
crpfindiahttp,O
:,O
//bit.ly/2lHlJS7,O
Sentence #119,
Unnao,O
rape,O
survivor,O
who,O
was,O
critically,O
injured,O
in,O
a,O
car,O
accident,O
in,O
July,B-TIM
is,O
discharged,O
from,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
https,O
:,O
//www.hindustantimes.com/india-news/unnao-rape-survivor-who-was-critically-injured-in-a-car-accident-in-july-is-discharged-from-aiims-in-delhi/story-9M2p3LVcparIM2fm13wtYO.html,O
#,O
UnnaoCase,O
Sentence #120,
Unnao,O
rape,O
survivor,O
who,O
was,O
critically,O
injured,O
in,O
a,O
car,O
accident,O
in,O
July,B-TIM
is,O
discharged,O
from,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//www.hindustantimes.com/india-news/unnao-rape-survivor-who-was-critically-injured-in-a-car-accident-in-july-is-discharged-from-aiims-in-delhi/story-9M2p3LVcparIM2fm13wtYO.html,O
Sentence #121,
The,O
Unnao,O
rape,O
survivor,O
was,O
discharged,O
on,O
Wednesday,B-TIM
from,O
the,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
where,O
she,O
was,O
admitted,O
after,O
she,O
met,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
https,O
:,O
//economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/politics-and-nation/unnao-rape-survivor-discharged-from-aiims-in-delhi/articleshow/71292583.cms,O
Sentence #122,
#,O
BREAKING,O
:,O
The,O
#,O
Unnao,O
rape,O
survivor,O
was,O
discharged,O
on,O
Wednesday,B-TIM
from,O
the,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
where,O
she,O
was,O
admitted,O
after,O
she,O
met,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/wrpX9aoT8i,O
Sentence #123,
The,O
#,O
UnnaoRape,O
survivor,O
was,O
discharged,O
from,O
the,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
where,O
she,O
was,O
admitted,O
after,O
she,O
met,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
https,O
:,O
//www.outlookindia.com/website/story/india-news-unnao-rape-survivor-discharged-from-aiims-to-stay-in-delhi-for-security-reasons/339385,O
Sentence #124,
The,O
Unnao,O
rape,O
survivor,O
who,O
had,O
sustained,O
grievous,O
injuries,O
in,O
an,O
accident,O
and,O
was,O
undergoing,O
treatment,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
got,O
discharged,O
from,O
the,O
hospital,B-MISC
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #127,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
plz,O
Sentence #128,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #129,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #130,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #131,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #132,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #133,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #134,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #135,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #136,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #137,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #138,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #139,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #140,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #141,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #142,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #143,
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #144,
First,O
the,O
victim,O
father,O
will,O
be,O
tortured,O
and,O
killed,O
then,O
they,O
will,O
arrange,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
to,O
kill,O
her,O
mother,O
and,O
injure,O
the,O
girl,O
.,O
Then,O
she,O
will,O
be,O
put,O
on,O
life,O
support,O
and,O
transferred,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
....,O
#,O
DontProtectRapists,O
Sentence #145,
:,O
http,O
:,O
//www.haribhoomi.com/news/state/delhi/two-died-as-basment-collapses-at-aiims-delhi/38466.html,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Accident,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Sentence #146,
:,O
http,O
:,O
//www.haribhoomi.com/news/state/delhi/two-died-as-basment-collapses-at-aiims-delhi/38466.html,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Accident,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Sentence #147,
Cave,O
in,O
at,O
construction,O
site,O
behind,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
in,O
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
One,O
reported,O
dead,O
https,O
:,O
//www.youtube.com/watch,O
?,O
v=CCN25XmMJMc,O
#,O
Accident,O
Sentence #148,
Accident,O
at,O
construction,O
site,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
reported,O
fatalities,O
@,O
ZeeNews,O
@,O
ibnlive,O
@,O
abpnewstv,O
@,O
ndtv,O
Sentence #149,
@,O
MalikAshutosh,O
Sir,O
colleague,O
and,O
I,O
took,O
accident,O
victim,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
.,O
We,O
were,O
both,O
new,O
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Such,O
was,O
harassment,O
we,O
shall,O
never,O
forget,O
.,O
Sentence #150,
@,O
EchoOfIndia,O
Reminded,O
me,O
of,O
Sunita,B-PER
Narain,I-PER
's,O
road,B-LOC
accident,O
while,O
biking,O
near,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
few,B-TIM
years,O
back,O
.,O
How,O
safe,O
are,O
Delhi,B-LOC
roads,I-LOC
?,O
@,O
Retributions,O
Sentence #151,
@,O
SatyendarJain,O
21year,O
old,O
got,O
brain,O
swelling,O
after,O
accident,O
in,O
coma,O
now,O
patient,O
need,O
to,O
admit,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
called,O
emergency,O
no,O
dnyed,O
Sentence #152,
Donated,O
organs,O
of,O
17-year-old,O
Delhi,B-LOC
accident,O
victim,O
saves,O
three,O
lives,O
@,O
MaxHealthcare,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
READ,O
:,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1MVVBCY,O
Sentence #153,
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1i2wWVt,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
Security,O
guard,O
killed,O
after,O
truck,O
crashes,O
into,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
#,O
accident,O
#,O
truckaccident,O
#,O
roadaccident,O
Sentence #154,
a,O
sadful,O
accident,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
bikaner,B-LOC
's,O
student,O
Khushbo,B-PER
choudhary,I-PER
is,O
sucided,O
at,O
3,O
a.m.,O
hanged,O
at,O
aiims,B-LOC
girls,I-LOC
hostel,I-LOC
in,O
her,O
room,O
Sentence #155,
NHRC,O
issues,O
notices,O
to,O
Union,B-ORG
Health,I-ORG
Secretary,B-PER
Director,B-PER
AIIMS,B-ORG
&,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
Commissioner,O
over,O
denial,O
of,O
treatment,O
to,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
victim,O
Sentence #156,
NHRC,O
issues,O
notices,O
to,O
Union,B-ORG
Health,I-ORG
Secretary,B-PER
Director,B-PER
AIIMS,B-ORG
&,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
Commissioner,O
over,O
denial,O
of,O
treatment,O
to,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
victim,O
.,O
Sentence #157,
NHRC,O
issues,O
notices,O
to,O
Union,B-ORG
Health,I-ORG
Secretary,B-PER
Director,B-PER
AIIMS,B-ORG
&,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
Commissioner,O
over,O
denial,O
of,O
treatment,O
to,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
victim,O
.,O
Sentence #158,
@,O
CPBlr,O
NHRC,O
issues,O
notices,O
to,O
Union,B-ORG
Health,I-ORG
Secretary,O
Director,B-PER
AIIMS,B-ORG
&,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
Commr,I-ORG
over,O
denial,O
of,O
treatment,O
to,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
victim,O
.,O
Sentence #159,
NHRC,O
issues,O
notices,O
to,O
Union,B-ORG
Health,I-ORG
Secretary,O
Director,B-PER
AIIMS,B-ORG
&,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
Commissioner,O
over,O
denial,O
of,O
treatment,O
to,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
victim,O
Sentence #160,
NHRC,O
issues,O
notices,O
to,O
Union,B-ORG
Health,I-ORG
Secretary,O
Director,B-PER
AIIMS,B-ORG
&,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
Commissioner,O
over,O
denial,O
of,O
treatment,O
to,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
victim,O
Sentence #161,
Delhi,B-LOC
cops,O
race,O
to,O
save,O
arm,O
of,O
accident,O
victim,O
:,O
Tanuja,B-PER
lies,O
battling,O
for,O
life,O
at,O
the,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//goo.gl/fb/uxggfK,O
Sentence #162,
Wow,O
accidents,O
cancer,O
injuries,O
&,O
kuch,O
immediate,O
treatments,O
chaalu,O
h,O
aur,O
central,O
govt,B-ORG
k,O
bhi,O
bahot,O
hospitals,O
h,O
wahan,O
jaise,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
RML,B-ORG
etc,O
.,O
wahan,O
jae,O
wo,O
khule,O
h,O
.,O
majdoor,O
agar,O
kuch,O
time,O
delhi,B-LOC
me,O
rha,O
h,O
to,O
uska,O
proof,O
ho,O
to,O
ho,O
jaega,O
but,O
specially,O
koi,O
up,O
hr,O
se,O
free,O
ilaaj,O
krane,O
aae,O
to,O
nahi,O
.,O
Sentence #163,
Have,O
you,O
been,O
following,O
reporting,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
?,O
The,O
hospitals,O
are,O
already,O
not,O
admitting,O
patients,O
.,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
have,O
their,O
beds,O
restocked,O
for,O
VIPs,O
.,O
And,O
thats,O
all,O
besides,O
the,O
point,O
.,O
Imagine,O
you,O
visiting,O
USA,B-LOC
get,O
into,O
an,O
accident,O
&,O
hospitals,O
denying,O
treatment,O
because,O
you,O
are,O
not,O
American,B-MISC
!,O
Sentence #164,
If,O
someone,O
from,O
other,O
states,O
meet,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
then,O
he,O
has,O
to,O
search,O
admission,O
in,O
centeral,B-ORG
government,I-ORG
hospital,O
like,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
or,O
die,O
on,O
road,I-LOC
.,O
Sentence #165,
My,O
parents,O
had,O
met,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
11,B-TIM
years,O
back,O
were,O
admitted,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
Was,O
frequented,O
by,O
the,O
missionary,O
people,O
Sentence #166,
It,O
pissed,O
me,O
off,O
to,O
no,O
limits,O
next,O
morning,O
they,O
were,O
behind,O
bars,O
after,O
that,O
I,O
do,O
n't,O
know,O
Sentence #167,
#,O
Delhi,B-PER
Need,O
#,O
Blood,B-MISC
Type,O
:,O
B-negative,O
At,O
:,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Hospital,I-LOC
.,O
Number,O
of,O
Units,O
:,O
2,O
Primary,O
Number,O
:,O
9958901899,O
Secondary,O
Number,O
:,O
9899790724,O
Patient,O
:,O
A.,B-PER
K,I-PER
Chaturvedi,I-PER
Illness,O
:,O
Accident,O
case,O
Via,O
:,O
@,O
iamsaddammujeeb,O
#,O
BloodMatters,O
Powered,O
by,O
Twitterpic.twitter.com/P10isfl2gA,O
Sentence #168,
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,B-PER
sir,O
please,O
open,O
delhi,B-LOC
borders,O
wid,O
out,O
e,O
pass,O
because,O
we,O
are,O
common,O
people,O
so,O
we,O
have,O
no,O
e,O
pass,O
and,O
any,O
movement,O
pass,O
so,O
how,O
to,O
come,O
in,O
delhi,B-LOC
actually,O
our,O
one,O
fmly,O
member,O
admit,O
in,O
Aiims,B-LOC
during,O
to,O
road,I-LOC
accident,O
now,O
no,O
one,O
there,O
for,O
caring,O
the,O
patient,O
..,O
so,O
please,O
open,O
Sentence #169,
Ashok,B-PER
kumar,I-PER
in,O
bhai,O
ji,O
ka,O
serious,O
accident,O
hua,O
hai,O
.,O
Lnjp,B-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
me,O
inko,O
admit,O
nhi,O
kiya,O
hai,O
.,O
Ab,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
le,O
ja,O
rhe,O
hain,O
.,O
Koi,O
hai,O
jo,O
inko,O
admit,O
karwa,O
sake,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
me,O
..,O
Bahut,O
serious,O
hain,O
.,O
Kripya,O
inki,O
help,O
ki,O
jaye,O
.,O
@,O
jaitushar,O
@,O
DrRebellious,O
Sentence #170,
@,O
drharshvardhan,O
Sir,O
my,O
brother,O
has,O
met,O
with,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
and,O
has,O
serious,O
head,O
injury,O
.,O
Can,O
we,O
get,O
an,O
admission,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
.,O
We,O
shall,O
be,O
highly,O
obliged,O
.,O
He,O
needs,O
immediate,O
surgery,O
.,O
We,O
are,O
not,O
getting,O
any,O
good,O
response,O
from,O
any,O
private,O
hospital,O
Sentence #171,
@,O
IRCTCofficial,O
@,O
PiyushGoyalOffc,O
@,O
PiyushGoyal,O
Dear,O
Sir,O
.,O
Nand,O
got,O
accident,O
in,O
Jan,B-TIM
2020,I-TIM
whose,O
treatment,O
is,O
going,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
for,O
last,O
3-4,B-TIM
months,I-TIM
they,O
are,O
staying,O
at,O
Ghaziabad,B-LOC
he,O
is,O
ok,O
now,O
and,O
want,O
to,O
back,O
to,O
Bihar,B-LOC
but,O
they,O
r,O
unable,O
to,O
book,O
ticket,O
pls,O
arrange,O
3,O
tickets,O
4,O
them,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/QVOekFpEUs,O
Sentence #172,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Need,O
#,O
Blood,B-MISC
Type,O
:,O
Any,O
group,O
At,O
:,O
#,O
AIIMS,B-ORG
Hospital,I-ORG
Number,O
of,O
Units,O
:,O
1,O
Primary,O
Number,O
:,O
9350341300,O
Patient,O
:,O
Sanjeet,B-PER
Illness,I-ORG
:,O
Accident,O
@,O
iCanSaveLife,O
@,O
iamsaddammujeeb,O
@,O
BloodAid,O
@,O
upma23,O
@,O
Suhelseth,B-LOC
Sentence #173,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Need,O
#,O
Blood,B-LOC
Type,B-MISC
:,O
Any,O
group,O
At,O
:,O
AIIMS,B-ORG
Hospital,I-ORG
Number,O
of,O
Units,O
:,O
1,O
Primary,O
Number,O
:,O
9350341300,O
Patient,O
:,O
Sanjeet,B-ORG
Illness,I-ORG
:,O
Accident,O
Via,O
:,O
@,O
iamsaddammujeeb,O
#,O
BloodMatters,O
Powered,O
by,O
Twitterpic.twitter.com/ME9S5VTWFu,O
Sentence #174,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
URGENT,O
Need,O
1,O
Unit,O
Any,O
group,O
#,O
blood,O
@,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Hospital,I-LOC
for,O
Accident,O
case,O
.,O
Call,O
9350341300,O
#,O
BloodAid,O
via,O
@,O
iamsaddammujeeb,O
cc,O
@,O
TajinderBagga,O
@,O
upma23,O
@,O
crowngaurav,O
@,O
ArvindGaur,O
#,O
BloodMatters,O
Sentence #175,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Urgent,O
Need,O
10,O
Units,O
AB+,O
#,O
Blood,O
@,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
for,O
Accident,B-ORG
Case,I-ORG
.,O
Call,O
7210261140,O
#,O
BloodAid,O
via,O
@,O
kavirajpalsingh,O
cc,O
@,O
TajinderBagga,O
@,O
upma23,O
@,O
crowngaurav,O
@,O
ArvindGaur,O
#,O
BloodMatters,O
Sentence #176,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Urgent,O
Need,O
10,O
Units,O
AB+,O
#,O
Blood,O
@,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
for,O
Accident,B-ORG
Case,I-ORG
.,O
Call,O
7210261140,O
#,O
BloodAid,O
via,O
@,O
kavirajpalsingh,O
cc,O
@,O
TajinderBagga,O
@,O
upma23,O
@,O
crowngaurav,O
@,O
ArvindGaur,O
#,O
BloodMatters,O
Sentence #177,
Urgent,O
Blood,O
Requirement,O
Hospital,O
Name,O
:,O
AIIMS,B-ORG
Delhi,I-ORG
Blood,O
Group,O
:,O
AB+,O
've,O
(,O
10,O
Unit,O
),O
Blood,B-PER
Purposes,I-PER
:,O
Accident,B-ORG
Case,I-ORG
Contact,I-ORG
Number,I-ORG
:,O
7210261140,O
Sentence #178,
-,O
@,O
BloodDonorsIn,O
@,O
BloodAid,O
@,O
Blood4Help,B-LOC
@,O
BloodDonerWorld,O
@,O
docvjg,O
Sentence #179,
Do,O
you,O
really,O
think,O
of,O
raising,O
funds,O
?,O
Sentence #180,
While,O
delhi,B-LOC
AIIMS,B-LOC
is,O
there,O
.,O
Which,O
was,O
established,O
by,O
@,O
INCIndia,O
Even,O
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,O
asked,O
all,O
the,O
hospitals,O
to,O
treat,O
every,O
patients,O
free,O
of,O
cost,O
who,O
just,O
faced,O
any,O
accident,O
.,O
Or,O
it,O
just,O
because,O
some,O
people,O
will,O
eat,O
all,O
the,O
mony,O
of,O
donation,O
Sentence #181,
@,O
CPDelhi,O
Sir,O
connaught,B-LOC
place,I-LOC
police,I-LOC
station,I-LOC
New,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
not,O
register,O
our,O
FIR,O
u/s,O
279,O
&,O
338,O
of,O
Indian,B-GPE
Penal,O
.,O
The,O
date,O
of,O
accident,O
is,O
02.05.2020,O
when,O
my,O
wife,O
on,O
the,O
way,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
for,O
join,O
their,O
duty,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/3f4mPwF8ae,O
Sentence #182,
Here,O
are,O
people,O
wishing,O
that,O
fire,O
accidents,O
.What,O
a,O
shame,O
.He,O
s,O
a,O
resident,O
of,O
Aiims,B-LOC
ENT,O
dept,O
.,O
sick,O
mindset,O
.,O
@,O
AIIMSRDA,O
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
@,O
LtGovDelhi,O
@,O
delhi,B-LOC
pic.twitter.com/Jow1iTDjnu,O
Sentence #183,
My,O
dad,O
's,O
elder,O
brother,O
(,O
3rd,O
),O
worked,O
with,O
WHO,B-ORG
during,O
1960-1993,O
he,O
travelled,O
extensively,O
...,O
I,O
met,O
him,O
only,O
once,O
as,O
a,O
child,O
so,O
could,O
not,O
know,O
his,O
path,O
to,O
WHO,B-ORG
...,O
he,O
died,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
while,O
in,O
Colombo,B-LOC
his,O
family,O
survived,O
...,O
wife,O
a,O
doctor,O
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
passed,O
away,O
recently,O
.,O
Sentence #184,
To,O
battle,O
the,O
increasing,O
cases,O
of,O
coronavirus,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
the,O
All,B-ORG
India,I-ORG
Institute,I-ORG
of,I-ORG
Medical,I-ORG
Sciences,I-ORG
(,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
),O
has,O
decided,O
to,O
convert,O
its,O
Apex,B-LOC
Trauma,I-LOC
Centre,I-LOC
complex,I-LOC
into,O
a,O
dedicated,O
coronavirus,B-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
.,O
The,O
facility,O
currently,O
provides,O
treatment,O
mostly,O
to,O
victims,O
of,O
road,B-LOC
accidents,O
.,O
Sentence #185,
@,O
nitingadkari,O
Most,O
of,O
the,O
accidents,O
are,O
on,O
Crossing,O
but,O
how,O
to,O
make,O
roads,O
crossing,O
free,O
?,O
Therefore,O
please,O
go,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
New,I-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
Little,B-LOC
away,O
from,O
main,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
where,O
you,O
will,O
find,O
U-Turn,O
in,O
middle,O
of,O
the,O
road,B-LOC
where,O
left,O
side,O
permits,O
you,O
to,O
move,O
non,O
stop,O
and,O
U-turn,O
takes,O
you,O
on,O
reverse,O
Sentence #186,
@,O
MoHFW_INDIA,O
@,O
narendramodi,O
pls,O
help,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
I,O
m,O
in,O
trauma,B-LOC
centre,I-LOC
aiims,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
.,O
.,O
.,O
I,O
met,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
at,O
10,O
am,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
PCR,O
has,O
dropped,O
m,O
there,O
but,O
no,O
one,O
is,O
taking,O
care,O
of,O
me,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
#,O
DO_Support,O
Sentence #187,
DGP,B-MISC
J,B-LOC
&,I-LOC
K,I-LOC
Shr,B-PER
Dilbag,I-PER
Singh,I-PER
has,O
expressed,O
grief,O
over,O
sad,O
demise,O
of,O
DySP,O
Shri,O
.,O
Bodh,B-PER
Raj,I-PER
who,O
breathed,O
his,O
last,O
today,B-TIM
morning,I-TIM
at,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
.,O
He,O
&,O
4,O
Jawans,B-GPE
were,O
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
in,O
Keran,O
on,O
Nov,O
16,O
.,O
during,O
Panchayat,O
election,O
duties,O
.,O
He,O
was,O
airlifted,O
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
few,O
days,O
back,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/3uFNyIJlLL,O
Sentence #188,
In,O
my,O
areas,O
there,O
is,O
family,O
whose,O
2,O
member,O
suffered,O
from,O
diseases,O
.,O
one,O
person,O
suffered,O
from,O
bone,O
cancer,O
whose,O
treatment,O
goes,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
NEW,I-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
.,O
Another,O
person,O
hit,O
an,O
accident,O
with,O
cow,O
and,O
suffered,O
from,O
paralysis,O
.,O
They,O
are,O
from,O
BPL,O
family.Plz,O
help,O
Sentence #189,
Five,O
cops,O
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
;,O
DySP,O
Bodh,B-PER
Raj,I-PER
airlifted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
http,O
:,O
//news.statetimes.in/,O
?,O
p=418045,O
Sentence #190,
Five,O
cops,O
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
;,O
DySP,O
Bodh,O
Raj,O
airlifted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
-,O
http,O
:,O
//news.statetimes.in/five-cops-injured-in-road-accident-dysp-bodh-raj-airlifted-to-aiims-delhi/,O
Sentence #191,
Dy.SP,O
Bodh,B-PER
Raj,I-PER
seriously,O
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
airlifted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
https,O
:,O
//vmsnewsonline.com/2018/11/16/dy-sp-bodh-raj-seriously-injured-road-accident-airlifted-aiims-delhi/,O
Sentence #192,
Dy.SP,O
Bodh,B-PER
Raj,I-PER
airlifted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
DGP,I-MISC
J,B-LOC
&,I-LOC
K,I-LOC
IGP,O
Kashmir,B-PER
sees,O
him,O
of,O
at,O
Airport,B-LOC
.,O
Sachnews,B-ORG
Jammu,B-LOC
Kashmir,I-LOC
JAMMU,I-LOC
NOVEMBER,B-TIM
16,I-TIM
:,O
Shri,B-PER
Bodh,I-PER
Raj,I-PER
Dy.SP,O
of,O
IRP,O
4th,B-TIM
Bn,I-TIM
.,O
who,O
was,O
seriously,O
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
...,O
https,O
:,O
//www.facebook.com/254405297978174/posts/2003562819729071/,O
Sentence #193,
DSP,O
injured,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Kupwara,B-LOC
airlifted,O
to,O
AIIMs,B-LOC
New,I-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
https,O
:,O
//theins.in/2018/11/16/dsp-injured-in-accident-in-kupwara-airlifted-to-aiims-new-delhi/,O
pic.twitter.com/1qDiDFoJ7V,O
Sentence #194,
Dy.SP,O
Bodh,B-LOC
Raj,I-LOC
airlifted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
Sentence #195,
DGP,B-MISC
J,B-LOC
&,I-LOC
K,I-LOC
IGP,O
Kashmir,B-LOC
sees,O
him,O
of,O
at,O
Airport,B-LOC
.,O
Sentence #196,
JAMMU,O
NOVEMBER,B-TIM
16,I-TIM
:,O
Shri,B-PER
Bodh,I-PER
Raj,I-PER
Dy.SP,O
of,O
IRP,O
4th,B-TIM
Bn,I-TIM
.,O
who,O
was,O
seriously,O
injured,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
while,O
on,O
election,O
duty,O
...,O
https,O
:,O
//www.facebook.com/TodayInKashmir/posts/2075963449126890,O
Sentence #197,
Dy,O
SP,O
Bodh,B-PER
Raj,I-PER
who,O
was,O
seriously,O
injured,O
in,O
road,O
accident,O
last,O
evening,O
while,O
on,O
election,O
duty,O
airlifted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
.,O
Sentence #198,
DGP,O
Sh,B-PER
Dilbag,I-PER
Singh,I-PER
IGP,O
Sh,B-PER
SP,I-PER
Pani,I-PER
see,O
him,O
off,O
at,O
airport.DGP,O
has,O
wished,O
him,O
speedy,O
recovery,O
&,O
has,O
directed,O
Police,O
officers,O
at,O
Dehli,B-LOC
to,O
provide,O
all,O
assistance,O
pic.twitter.com/SEJqZU6k5M,O
Sentence #199,
Dy,O
SP,O
Bodh,B-PER
Raj,I-PER
who,O
was,O
seriously,O
injured,O
in,O
road,B-LOC
accident,O
last,O
evening,O
while,O
on,O
election,O
duty,O
airlifted,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
.,O
DGP,O
Sh,B-PER
Dilbag,I-PER
Singh,I-PER
IGP,O
Sh,B-PER
SP,I-PER
Pani,I-PER
see,O
him,O
off,O
at,O
airport,O
.,O
DGP,O
has,O
wished,O
him,O
speedy,O
recovery,O
&,O
has,O
directed,O
Police,O
officers,O
at,O
Dehli,B-LOC
to,O
provide,O
all,O
assistance,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/6Zrs9jFMtW,O
Sentence #200,
Verve,O
manikins,O
being,O
used,O
in,O
ASICONMAN,O
in,O
collaboration,O
with,O
Glasgow,B-LOC
RCPS,O
.,O
There,I-MISC
is,O
huge,O
gap,O
BW,O
accident,O
victims,O
requirement,O
&,O
treating,O
docs,O
which,O
cn,O
be,O
covered,O
by,O
training,O
through,O
Simulation,O
.,O
Training,O
was,O
spearheaded,O
by,O
Dr,B-PER
MC,I-PER
Mishra,I-PER
ex,O
Director,O
of,O
Aiims,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
Jpn,I-ORG
trauma,B-LOC
centre,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
pic.twitter.com/szoBkK6PyS,O
Sentence #201,
@,O
SushmaSwaraj,B-PER
respected,O
madam,O
we,O
need,O
your,O
help,O
you,O
are,O
our,O
only,O
hope,O
madam,O
my,O
brother,O
got,O
a,O
major,O
road,I-LOC
accident,O
17,O
days,O
ago,O
.,O
He,O
got,O
major,O
head,O
injury,O
now,O
he,O
is,O
admit,O
in,O
synergy,B-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
Agra,B-LOC
U.P,B-LOC
..,O
now,O
he,O
is,O
in,O
comma,O
madam,O
we,O
want,O
to,O
admit,O
him,O
in,O
aiims,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
so,O
we,O
need,O
your,O
help,O
Sentence #202,
@,O
PMOIndia,O
@,O
narendramodi,B-PER
@,O
ZeeNews,B-ORG
@,O
aajtak,B-ORG
@,O
ndtv,B-ORG
@,O
MoHFW_INDIA,O
@,O
abpnewstv,B-ORG
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,B-PER
@,O
drharshvardhan,B-PER
This,O
is,O
bizziare,O
.,O
It,O
means,O
if,O
a,O
person,O
from,O
Tamilnadu,B-LOC
comes,O
to,O
visit,O
Delhi,B-LOC
and,O
gets,O
through,O
an,O
accident,O
near,O
GTB,B-LOC
Hospital,I-LOC
.,O
Then,O
he,O
will,O
have,O
to,O
move,O
to,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
for,O
treatment,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/UhnaQEACMp,O
Sentence #203,
Respected,O
mam,O
Happy,O
Ganesh,B-PER
Chaturthi,O
to,O
you,O
too,O
.,O
We,O
hre,O
r,O
organizing,O
a,O
conference,O
ANTC,O
2018,O
in,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
New,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
On,I-LOC
behalf,O
of,O
the,O
organizing,O
committee,O
I,O
would,O
lyk,O
to,O
invite,O
u,O
fr,O
inaugural,O
ceremny,O
as,O
our,O
chief,O
guest,O
to,O
deliver,O
few,O
wrds,O
on,O
road,O
trfic,O
accident,O
.,O
Hpng,O
fr,O
ur,O
rply,O
.,O
Thnks,O
Sentence #204,
RT,O
@,O
divyajyoti,O
:,O
About,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
accident-,O
THERE,O
ARE,O
reports,O
that,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
did,O
not,O
take,O
the,O
old,O
man,O
to,O
hospital,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/bZgfEt,O
Sentence #205,
About,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
accident-,O
There,O
are,O
reports,O
that,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Police,I-ORG
did,O
not,O
take,O
the,O
old,O
man,O
to,O
hospital,O
in,O
time,O
.,O
Shameful,O
.,O
Sentence #206,
Fatal,O
accident,O
early,O
in,O
the,O
morning,O
near,O
CWG,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
Akshardham,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
middle,O
aged,O
man,O
on,O
bike,O
gone,O
RIP,O
...,O
Sentence #207,
MAJOR,O
jam,O
opposite,O
akshardham,B-LOC
metro,I-LOC
station,I-LOC
.,O
Fire,O
truck,O
cops,O
in,O
full,O
force,O
crowd,O
...,O
seems,O
like,O
a,O
major,O
accident,O
or,O
something,O
.,O
#,O
delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #208,
Three,O
policemen,O
injured,O
in,O
an,O
accident,O
at,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
early,O
morning,B-TIM
today,I-TIM
.,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #209,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
Road,O
accident,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
last,O
night,B-TIM
two,O
injured,O
.,O
Sentence #210,
Accident,O
caused,O
by,O
a,O
pot,O
holed,O
road/unsafe,O
design/vehicle,O
fault,O
told,O
speeding,O
driver,O
lost,O
control-Police,O
:,O
Akshardham-Delhi,B-LOC
Mumbai-Pune,B-LOC
#,O
RIP,O
Sentence #211,
The,O
parents,O
sends,O
children,O
to,O
study,O
.,O
Kids,O
party,O
at,O
malls,O
get,O
hurt,O
in,O
accidents,O
and,O
dies,O
:,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
accident,O
http,O
:,O
//ln.is/www.ptinews.com/news/cjYej,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #212,
23-year-old,O
woman,O
dies,O
in,O
accident,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
http,O
:,O
//indianexpress.com/article/cities/delhi/twenty-year-old-woman-dies-in-accident-near-akshardham-in-delhi/,O
Sentence #213,
#,O
Delhi,B-PER
Woman,I-PER
killed,O
five,O
injured,O
in,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
car,O
accident,O
:,O
The,O
friends,O
had,O
gone,O
to,O
S,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1Pi5tud,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1mKbocU,O
Sentence #214,
#,O
CommonwealthGames,O
|,O
Twenty-year-old,O
woman,B-PER
dies,O
in,O
accident,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
Just,O
after,O
they,O
crossed,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1Ksos1K,O
Sentence #215,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
NHAISocialmedia,O
The,O
exit,O
to,O
Khelgaon,O
on,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Meerut,B-LOC
Expressway,I-LOC
while,O
coming,O
from,O
old,O
Yamuna,B-LOC
Bridge,I-LOC
is,O
too,O
dangerous,O
.,O
Please,O
make,O
DME,O
entry,O
after,O
yamuna,B-LOC
bridge,I-LOC
as,O
exit,O
to,O
khelgaon/noida/Akshardham,O
and,O
exit,O
for,O
noida,B-LOC
as,O
entry,O
to,O
DME,O
to,O
avoid,O
accidents,O
@,O
nitin_gadkari,O
Sentence #216,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
NHAISocialmedia,O
The,O
exit,O
to,O
Khelgaon,O
on,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Meerut,I-LOC
Expressway,I-LOC
while,O
coming,O
from,O
old,O
Yamuna,B-LOC
Bridge,I-LOC
is,O
too,O
dangerous,O
.,O
Please,O
make,O
DME,O
entry,O
after,O
yamuna,B-LOC
bridge,I-LOC
as,O
exit,O
to,O
khelgaon/noida/Akshardham,O
and,O
exit,O
for,O
noida,B-LOC
as,O
entry,O
to,O
DME,O
to,O
avoid,O
accidents,O
@,O
nitin_gadkari,O
Sentence #217,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
NavGujaratsamay,O
http,O
:,O
//navgujaratsamay.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393205.cms,O
via,O
@,O
navgujaratsamay,O
Sentence #218,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
NavGujaratsamay,O
http,O
:,O
//navgujaratsamay.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393205.cms,O
via,O
@,O
navgujaratsamay,O
Sentence #219,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
Video,O
|,O
Maharashtra,B-LOC
Time,O
http,O
:,O
//maharashtratimes.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393190.cms,O
via,O
@,O
mataonline,O
Sentence #220,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
Video,O
|,O
Maharashtra,B-LOC
Time,O
http,O
:,O
//maharashtratimes.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393190.cms,O
via,O
@,O
mataonline,O
Sentence #221,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
NavGujaratsamay,O
http,O
:,O
//navgujaratsamay.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393205.cms,O
via,O
@,O
navgujaratsamay,O
Sentence #222,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
Video,O
|,O
Maharashtra,B-LOC
Time,O
http,O
:,O
//maharashtratimes.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393190.cms,O
via,O
@,O
mataonline,O
Sentence #223,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
NavGujaratsamay,O
http,O
:,O
//navgujaratsamay.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393205.cms,O
via,O
@,O
navgujaratsamay,O
Sentence #224,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
Video,O
|,O
MT,O
http,O
:,O
//maharashtratimes.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393190.cms,O
via,O
@,O
mataonline,O
Sentence #225,
One,O
person,O
killed,O
in,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
-,O
NavGujaratsamay,O
http,O
:,O
//navgujaratsamay.indiatimes.com/one-person-killed-in-accident-in-delhis-akshardham-area/videoshow/53393205.cms,O
via,O
@,O
navgujaratsamay,O
Sentence #226,
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
A,O
horrific,O
road,O
accident,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
temple,I-LOC
several,O
vehicles,O
collided,O
with,O
each,O
other,O
https,O
:,O
//in.avalanches.com/delhi_delhi_a_horrific_road_accident_near_akshardham_temple_several_vehicles_collided_with_each_other1400_18_09_2019,O
via,O
@,O
avalanches,O
Sentence #227,
Delhi,B-LOC
Traffic,I-ORG
Cops,O
Educate,O
Drivers,O
with,O
Fire,B-ORG
Safety,I-ORG
Lessons,O
After,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Tragedy,O
#,O
BreakingNews,O
#,O
Traffic,O
#,O
ACCIDENT,O
#,O
CarCrash,O
#,O
Fire,O
#,O
safetytips,O
#,O
GMA,O
#,O
ThursdayThoughts,O
http,O
:,O
//www.tourismwings.com,O
pic.twitter.com/Au9RmtvXLT,O
Sentence #228,
Car,O
accident,O
near,O
akshardham,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #229,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
pls,O
monitor,O
NH,B-LOC
24,I-LOC
(,O
Meerut,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
expressway,I-LOC
),O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
many,O
bikers,O
cars,O
take,O
dangerous,O
U,O
turn,O
to,O
come,O
on,O
another,O
lane,O
(,O
which,O
goes,O
towards,O
Kale,B-LOC
Khan,I-LOC
),O
.,O
This,O
can,O
cause,O
a,O
major,O
accident,O
anytime,O
..,O
pic.twitter.com/zYKeqvccs7,O
Sentence #230,
#,O
URGENT,O
DL7S,O
BZ,O
6429,O
Bike,O
Honda,B-LOC
Shine,O
(,O
Rohit,B-PER
Naib,I-PER
:,O
AuthorityName,O
),O
Major,B-LOC
#,O
Accident,O
Hit,B-ORG
&,I-ORG
June,I-TIM
MidNight,I-TIM
12:15,I-TIM
am,O
#,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
To,O
Shastri,B-LOC
Park,I-LOC
Road,I-LOC
Near,O
Geeta,B-LOC
Colony,I-LOC
Road,I-LOC
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
IDENTITY,B-ORG
Not,I-ORG
Available,I-ORG
PCR,O
kisi,B-LOC
Hospital,I-LOC
lekar,O
gayi,O
hai,O
@,O
delhipolice,O
@,O
dtptrafficpic.twitter.com/0hszwhHLUJ,O
Sentence #231,
!,O
Video,O
http,O
:,O
//hindi.eenaduindia.com/States/North/Delhi/NewDelhi/2018/06/06030624/Truck-fall-down-from-Akshardham-Flyover-of-East-Delhi.vpf,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
#,O
TruckAccident,O
#,O
Accident,O
#,O
Akshardhamflyover,I-LOC
#,O
DelhiPolice,O
Sentence #232,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
Pls,O
look,O
into,O
traffic,O
lights,O
under,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Setu,O
NH24,B-LOC
in,O
East,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
.,O
with,O
traffic,O
lights,O
not,O
working,O
it,O
hs,O
bcome,O
accident,O
prone,O
Sentence #233,
@,O
TrafflineDEL,O
huge,O
huge,O
traffic,O
at,O
the,O
flyover,B-LOC
opposite,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
metro,I-LOC
station,I-LOC
...,O
Towards,O
Noida-Delhi,B-LOC
..,O
Some,O
accident,O
has,O
happened,O
.,O
:,O
-/,O
Sentence #234,
``,O
Traffline,O
Delhi/NCR,B-LOC
on,O
Twitter,B-ORG
:,O
``,O
'',O
Accident,O
@,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
.,O
Belongs,O
to,O
Satpal,B-GPE
'',O
D-18,B-LOC
Arya,B-LOC
Nagar,I-LOC
IP,B-LOC
Ext,I-LOC
.,O
Girl,O
i,O
http,O
:,O
//rightrelevance.com/tw/delhiindiarr/090100e113befb5fd221c06a375c7b8d4f76ca4c/New,O
%,O
Delhi/New,B-LOC
%,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #235,O
Jaideep,B-PER
Pandey,I-PER
:,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
.,O
RT,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//www.tweetsnow.in/294880,O
#,O
TweetsNowpic.twitter.com/WZsY49rEll,O
Sentence #236,
``,O
@,O
PandeyJaideep,O
:,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,O
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Need,O
help,O
@,O
TrafflineDEL,O
Sentence #237,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,O
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Need,O
help,O
pic.twitter.com/RqYE3tj5ev,O
@,O
choriketweet,O
'',O
Sentence #238,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,O
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Need,O
help,O
@,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Traffic,I-ORG
Sentence #239,
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Need,O
help,O
@,O
TrafflineDEL,O
pic.twitter.com/9hRlnKvD1m,O
Sentence #240,
``,O
@,O
PandeyJaideep,O
:,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Need,O
help,O
Sentence #241,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Need,O
help,O
@,O
ShashiTharoorpic.twitter.com/Q72IOsLbnL,O
Sentence #242,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
.,O
RT,O
this,O
info,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Help,O
needed,O
@,O
BajpayeeManojpic.twitter.com/8b5SiJNqNl,O
Sentence #243,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Help,O
needed,O
@,O
M_Lekhipic.twitter.com/jw2OYP1d9j,O
Sentence #244,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
Help,O
need,O
@,O
ArvindKejriwalpic.twitter.com/TofdTlbXvn,O
Sentence #245,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
.,O
RT,O
this,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
@,O
GulPanag,O
@,O
TedhiLakeerpic.twitter.com/hE2wZmOsVT,O
Sentence #246,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
..,O
RT,O
this,O
info,O
.,O
Finding,O
Parents,O
need,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
@,O
GulPanagpic.twitter.com/zOmXrd8gH8,O
Sentence #247,
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
An,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
Akshardham,B-LOC
Mandir,I-LOC
..,O
RT,O
this,O
info.Finding,O
Parents,O
need,O
.,O
Girl,O
critical,O
.,O
@,O
tavleen_singhpic.twitter.com/j6376npoqr,O
Sentence #248,
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
are,O
u,O
aware,O
that,O
private,O
bus,O
mafia,O
have,O
damaged,O
boundary,O
wall,O
constructed,O
by,O
Delhi,B-ORG
government,O
on,O
border,O
to,O
enter,O
in,O
UP,O
opposite,O
ISBT,O
Anand,B-LOC
Vihar,I-LOC
.,O
They,O
also,O
forcefully,O
enter,O
UP,O
from,O
the,O
wrong,O
side,O
which,O
one,O
day,O
may,O
the,O
reason,O
for,O
some,O
accident,O
.,O
Sentence #249,
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
are,O
u,O
aware,O
that,O
bus,O
mafia,O
have,O
damaged,O
boundary,O
wall,O
constructed,O
by,O
Delhi,B-LOC
on,O
UP,O
border,O
opposite,O
ISBT,B-LOC
Anand,B-LOC
Vihar,I-LOC
.,O
They,O
also,O
forcefully,O
enter,O
UP,O
from,O
the,O
wrong,O
side,O
which,O
one,O
day,O
may,O
cause,O
some,O
accident,O
.,O
Sentence #250,
Hyundai,B-LOC
Traffic,O
squad,O
at,O
Ashram,B-LOC
New,I-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
cause,O
accidents,O
misbehaves,O
with,O
public,O
today,B-TIM
!,O
Hyundai,O
acts,O
irresponsibly,O
#,O
Hyundai,B-LOC
#,O
Trafficsquad,O
Sentence #251,
delhi24X7,O
Dumper,O
kills,O
2,O
in,O
south,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
:,O
In,O
yet,O
another,O
accident,O
on,O
the,O
killer,O
Ashram,B-LOC
stretch,O
a,O
man,O
and,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/9bWSIE,O
delhi24X7,O
Sentence #252,
ACCIDENT,O
HAPPENED,O
AT,O
DELHI,B-LOC
DARWAJA,B-LOC
CROSS,I-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
CAUSING,O
SOME,O
CONGESTION,O
TOWARDS,O
ASHRAM,B-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
INCOME-TAX,B-LOC
CROSS,I-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/voEAs2Wk,O
Sentence #253,
ACCIDENT,O
HAPPENED,O
AT,O
DELHI,B-LOC
DARWAJA,B-LOC
CROSS,I-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
CAUSING,O
SOME,O
CONGESTION,O
TOWARDS,O
ASHRAM,B-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
INCOME-TAX,B-LOC
CROSS,I-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/Vlpgba5U,O
Sentence #254,
delhi,O
#,O
traffic,O
MAHARANI,B-LOC
BAGH,I-LOC
MATHURA,B-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
NEAR,O
ASHRAM,B-LOC
FLYOVER,I-LOC
TRUCK,O
ACCIDENT,O
CAUSING,O
DELAY,O
TOWARDS,O
ASHRAM,B-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/C575fqcL,O
Sentence #255,
Traffic,O
congestion,O
after,O
DND,B-LOC
towards,O
Delhi,B-LOC
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
at,O
Ashram,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
.,O
Use,O
Barapullah,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
as,O
an,O
alternate,O
route,O
.,O
Sentence #256,
RT,O
capt_ivane,O
:,O
Do,O
not,O
use,O
#,O
DND,B-LOC
to,O
go,O
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Heavy,O
traffic,O
jam,O
due,O
to,O
accident,O
at,O
Ashram,B-LOC
Flyover,I-LOC
.,O
dtptraffic,O
Sentence #257,
Do,O
not,O
use,O
#,O
DND,O
to,O
go,O
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Heavy,O
traffic,O
jam,O
due,O
to,O
accident,O
at,O
Ashram,B-LOC
Flyover,I-LOC
.,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
Sentence #258,
#,O
shame,O
on,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
on,O
ashram,B-LOC
chowk,I-LOC
19,B-TIM
July,I-TIM
container,O
cars,O
#,O
accident,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
thullo,O
ki,O
barat,O
kaha,O
hai,O
...,O
besharmo,O
....,O
Sentence #259,
Stuck,O
at,O
ashram,B-LOC
can,O
any,O
one,O
tell,O
me,O
why,O
the,O
fuck,O
is,O
the,O
traffic,O
so,O
fucking,O
slow,O
here,O
?,O
Any,O
one,O
killed,O
?,O
Any,O
accident,O
?,O
@,O
delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #260,
Accident,O
near,O
Ashram,B-LOC
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
..,O
!,O
Had,O
a,O
narrow,O
escape,O
?,O
pic.twitter.com/oqhtaz66,O
Sentence #261,
@,O
TrafflineDEL,O
There,O
is,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
DND,B-LOC
Towards,O
Maharani,B-LOC
bagh,I-LOC
.,O
Traffic,O
is,O
smooth,O
till,O
ashram,B-LOC
#,O
delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #262,
Retweeted,B-ORG
Delhi,B-ORG
Traffic,I-ORG
Police,I-ORG
(,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
),O
:,O
Sentence #263,
Traffic,O
Alert,O
Obstruction,O
in,O
traffic,O
in,O
the,O
carriageway,O
from,O
Ashram,B-LOC
to,O
Moolchand,B-LOC
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
of,O
a,O
car,O
near,O
Lajpat,B-LOC
Nagar,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
.,O
Kindly,O
avoid,O
the,O
stretch,O
.,O
Sentence #264,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
Obstruction,O
in,O
traffic,O
in,O
the,O
carriageway,O
connecting,O
Sarai,B-LOC
Kale,I-LOC
Khan,I-LOC
to,O
Ashram,B-LOC
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
!,O
2,O
Ambulances,O
stuck,O
!,O
Traffic,O
cops,O
at,O
spot,O
delaying,O
it,O
further,O
.,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #265,
Witnessed,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
ashram,B-LOC
road,I-LOC
delhi,B-LOC
few,O
minutes,O
back,O
on,O
way,O
to,O
my,O
home,O
from,O
office,O
.,O
The,O
head,O
was,O
separated,O
from,O
the,O
body,O
.,O
The,O
police,O
was,O
there,O
.,O
M,O
sure,O
they,O
have,O
contacted,O
ambulance,O
but,O
the,O
body,O
was,O
lying,O
uncovered,O
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
(,O
1/2,O
),O
Sentence #266,
#,O
3Novices,O
:,O
Truck,O
accident,O
on,O
Delhi,B-LOC
`s,O
Barapullah,B-ORG
Flyover,I-ORG
leads,O
to,O
massive,O
traffic,O
jam,O
The,O
roads,O
leading,O
to,O
Sarai,B-LOC
Kale,I-LOC
Khan,I-LOC
Lodhi,B-LOC
Road,I-LOC
have,O
been,O
closed,O
down,O
.,O
The,O
traffic,O
has,O
been,O
diverted,O
towards,O
Ashram,B-LOC
.,O
The,O
commuters,O
have,O
been,O
asked,O
to,O
avoid,O
DND,O
and,O
Barapullah,B-ORG
.,O
#,O
news,O
For,O
In,O
Sentence #267,
Do,O
not,O
take,O
DND,O
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
Heavy,O
jam,O
at,O
Ashram,B-LOC
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
.,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
Sentence #268,
It,O
is,O
clear,O
that,O
what,O
happened,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
was,O
an,O
accident,O
.,O
It,O
could,O
have,O
happened,O
in,O
AP,B-LOC
or,O
at,O
Coimbatore,B-LOC
ashram,I-LOC
or,O
in,O
a,O
church,O
meeting,O
.,O
But,O
when,O
entire,O
Muslim,O
community,O
is,O
targeting,O
based,O
on,O
Delhi,B-LOC
incident,O
it,O
divides,O
people,O
and,O
spreads,O
hate,O
.,O
Sentence #269,
No,O
some,O
accidents,O
happen,O
due,O
to,O
careless,O
attitudes,O
of,O
authorities,O
who,O
do,O
not,O
believe,O
in,O
repairing,O
the,O
roads,O
.,O
@,O
DelhiPwd,O
please,O
have,O
a,O
look,O
at,O
the,O
road,O
just,O
after,O
Ashram,B-LOC
fly,I-LOC
over,I-LOC
while,O
going,O
towards,O
Noida,B-LOC
from,O
delhi,B-LOC
.,O
https,O
:,O
//twitter.com/timesofindia/status/1235775864048152587,O
Sentence #270,
#,O
Azadpur,B-ORG
Delhi,I-ORG
Police,I-ORG
shud,O
check,O
whether,O
the,O
bus,O
met,O
with,O
accident,O
was,O
fitted,O
with,O
speed,O
govrnor,O
or,O
not,O
and,O
book,O
delhi,B-ORG
govt,I-ORG
if,O
not,O
fitted,O
sg,O
Sentence #271,
Police,O
say,O
tyre,O
burst,O
suspected,O
to,O
have,O
led,O
to,O
the,O
bus,O
accident,O
that,O
killed,O
one,O
and,O
injured,O
6,O
others,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Azadpur,B-LOC
.,O
@,O
htTweets,O
@,O
htdelhi,O
Sentence #272,
Today,B-TIM
at,O
azadpur,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
a,O
fatal,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
which,O
lead,O
to,O
great,O
injury,O
of,O
smooth,O
drivers,O
they,O
became,O
bloody,O
mud,O
pie,O
..,O
Moreover,O
the,O
car,O
driver,O
who,O
hit,O
the,O
scooty,O
ran,O
away,O
.,O
I,O
request,O
everyone,O
to,O
driver,O
carefully,O
and,O
cautiously,O
......,O
Sentence #273,
Accident,O
Azadpur,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
Mai,O
Hua,O
Hai,O
Sentence #274,
Im,O
surprised,O
how,O
dis,O
activity,O
is,O
being,O
allowed,O
in,O
d,O
delhi,B-LOC
after,O
so,O
many,O
alarming,O
incidents,O
&,O
accidents,O
caused,O
due,O
2,O
waste,O
http,O
:,O
//dumping.Im,O
Equally,O
amazed,O
to,O
see,O
dat,O
its,O
so,O
near,O
2,O
areas,O
such,O
as,O
Shalimar,B-LOC
Bagh,I-LOC
Azadpur,B-LOC
etc,O
.,O
and,O
no,O
one,O
til,O
now,O
has,O
put,O
dis,O
2,O
notice,O
.,O
Sentence #275,
Obstruction,O
in,O
traffic,O
in,O
the,O
carriageway,O
from,O
Rajouri,B-LOC
Garden,I-LOC
towards,O
Azadpur,B-LOC
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
#,O
PunjabiBagh,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
.,O
Kindly,O
avoid,O
the,O
stretch,O
:,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Traffic,I-ORG
Police,I-ORG
Sentence #276,
@,O
htTweets,O
Six,O
members,O
of,O
a,O
family,O
were,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
near,O
Badarpur,B-LOC
border,I-LOC
in,O
south,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
.,O
Their,O
car,O
was,O
hit,O
by,O
a,O
truck,O
Sentence #277,
On,O
Badarpur,B-LOC
Border,I-LOC
in,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
a,O
car,O
in,O
a,O
politician,O
's,O
entourage,O
had,O
an,O
accident,O
with,O
a,O
commoner,O
.,O
Will,O
#,O
traffic,O
cops,O
do,O
justice,O
to,O
#,O
AamAdmi,O
?,O
Sentence #278,
@,O
PMOIndia,O
Today,B-TIM
one,O
more,O
ruteen,O
accident,O
@,O
railway,B-LOC
crossing,I-LOC
Badarpur,B-LOC
border,I-LOC
new,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
.,O
Sentence #279,
Today,B-TIM
one,O
more,O
ruteen,O
accident,O
@,O
railway,B-LOC
crossing,I-LOC
Badarpur,B-LOC
border,I-LOC
new,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
.,O
Sentence #280,
@,O
sureshpprabhu,O
need,O
foot,O
bridge,O
at,O
shiv,B-LOC
durga,I-LOC
vihar,I-LOC
fatak,O
badarpur,B-LOC
border,I-LOC
nee,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
today,B-TIM
accident,O
3,O
person,O
dead,O
.,O
Manoj,B-PER
yadav9910689987,O
Sentence #281,
Delhi,O
Witnessed,O
deadly,O
Road,B-MISC
Accident,I-ORG
last,O
night,O
at,O
Barakhambha,B-LOC
area,I-LOC
of,O
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
.,O
1,O
died,O
and,O
2,O
seriously,O
injured,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/yjjSxZKHUG,O
Sentence #282,
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
-,O
Traffic,O
movement,O
is,O
slow,O
on,O
Ring,B-LOC
Road,I-LOC
AIIMS,B-LOC
twds,O
Hyaat,B-LOC
..,O
accident,O
between,O
few,O
cars,O
at,O
Bhikaji,B-LOC
Cama,I-LOC
Place,I-LOC
...,O
Sentence #283,
A,O
car,O
catches,O
fire,O
near,O
Bhikaji,B-LOC
Cama,I-LOC
Place,I-LOC
in,O
New,B-LOC
#,I-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
#,O
Accident,O
Sentence #284,
Two,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Metro,I-ORG
trains,O
collided,O
in,O
a,O
freak,O
accident,O
at,O
the,O
Kalindi,B-LOC
Kunj,I-LOC
depot,O
on,O
the,O
yet-to-open,O
Botanical,B-LOC
Garden,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/ZR0TCp19,O
Sentence #285,
Trucks,O
accident,O
on,O
Kalindi,B-LOC
Bridge,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
Bound,O
Traffic,O
effected,O
..,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
have,O
cleared,O
one,O
One,O
more,O
to,O
go,O
.,O
Jam,O
now,O
till,O
botanical,B-LOC
garden,I-LOC
Sentence #286,
Car-bike,O
collision,O
near,O
Central,B-LOC
Secretariat,I-LOC
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
accident,O
pic.twitter.com/DCpyVV7tLw,O
Sentence #287,
First,O
picture,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
fire,O
at,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
Bhagirath,B-LOC
Palace,I-LOC
Electric,B-LOC
Market,I-LOC
#,O
India,B-LOC
#,O
Accident,O
#,O
BreakingNewspic.twitter.com/pbd55aX5,O
Sentence #288,
Major,O
fire,O
at,O
electrical,O
market,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
;,O
22,O
fire,O
tenders,O
rushed,O
to,O
the,O
spot,O
#,O
India,B-LOC
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
#,O
Accident,O
#,O
BreakingNews,O
Sentence #289,
Major,O
fire,O
in,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
's,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
;,O
10,O
fire,O
tenders,O
rushed,O
to,O
the,O
spot,O
#,O
India,B-LOC
#,O
Accident,O
#,O
BreakingNews,O
Sentence #290,
Delhi,B-LOC
streets,O
.,O
I,O
do,O
n't,O
know,O
if,O
the,O
smoke,O
down,O
the,O
street,O
was,O
festive,O
or,O
an,O
accident,O
.,O
@,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
http,O
:,O
//instagr.am/p/SX2H9pOuvv/,O
Sentence #291,
http,O
:,O
//www.hindustantimes.com/mumbai-news/14-killed-in-fire-at-mumbai-building-survivor-says-people-were-running-over-him/story-oiSHXbTMCUVXzI5P1Ow4gP.html,O
Sentence #292,
Are,O
we,O
waiting,O
for,O
Mumbai,B-LOC
like,O
accidents,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
also,O
?,O
?,O
?,O
Have,O
a,O
look,O
at,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
Markets,I-LOC
.,O
@,O
PMOIndia,O
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,O
Sentence #293,
Locals,O
police,O
save,O
lives,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
:,O
The,O
bus,O
accident,O
in,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
could,O
have,O
been,O
worse,O
if,O
not,O
for,O
the,O
tim,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1KnMo6g,O
Sentence #294,
RT,O
AAP,B-ORG
Delhi,I-ORG
Feeds,O
:,O
AAPDelhiFeeds,O
:,O
MLA,B-PER
LambaAlka,O
met,O
victims,O
of,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
low-floor,O
bus,O
accident,O
.,O
http,O
:,O
//dlvr.it/CBcjZ0,O
Sentence #295,
3,O
dead,O
in,O
a,O
freak,O
accident,O
at,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
this,O
afternoon,B-TIM
.,O
Bus,O
mowed,O
them,O
down,O
.,O
Driver,O
of,O
the,O
bus,O
died,O
too,O
of,O
heart,O
attack,O
!,O
Sentence #296,
Fire,O
at,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Chandni,I-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
Fire,B-ORG
force,I-ORG
Fire,B-ORG
Accident,I-ORG
http,O
:,O
//www.deepika.com/News_Latest.aspx,O
?,O
catcode=latestin,O
&,O
newscode=207609,O
#,O
sthash.G9eHgH8O.uxfs,O
Sentence #297,
Accident,O
near,O
#,O
Chandnichowk,B-LOC
#,O
Delhi,B-PER
He,I-PER
met,O
with,O
a,O
very,O
serious,O
accident,O
and,O
rushed,O
by,O
our,O
volunteers,O
to,O
#,O
Sanjaygandhi,B-PER
shelter,O
for,O
treatment,O
.,O
He,O
is,O
on,O
diagnosis,O
and,O
on,O
medications,O
.,O
We,O
are,O
praying,O
for,O
his,O
speedy,O
recovery,O
.,O
#,O
DogRescues,O
pic.twitter.com/Nc91fTlN9U,O
Sentence #298,
@,O
sambitswaraj,O
mahatwapoorna,O
suchna,O
:,O
Sanjay,B-PER
Gandhi,I-PER
was,O
the,O
only,O
secular,O
minded,O
Congress,B-ORG
leader,O
ever,O
born,O
.,O
Proof,O
treating,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
at,O
par,O
to,O
Turkman,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
Delhi,O
.,O
n,O
nasbandi,O
operation,O
of,O
deserving,O
candidates,O
without,O
Jaati,O
-,O
Dharma,O
.,O
n,O
that,O
's,O
what,O
ended,O
his,O
life,O
in,O
a,O
planned,O
accident,O
.,O
Sentence #299,
@,O
narendramodi,O
ji,O
na,O
chandni,B-LOC
chowk,I-LOC
mandir,I-LOC
todne,O
pe,O
bole,O
the,O
na,O
hi,O
delhi,B-LOC
riots,O
par,O
bole,O
the,O
naahi,O
ab,O
sadhuo,O
ki,O
hatya,O
par,O
bolenge,O
.,O
Ye,O
bolte,O
hai,O
jab,O
gau,O
taskar,O
pehlu,O
khan,O
marta,O
hai,O
chor,O
tabrez,O
ansari,O
marta,O
hai,O
jab,O
urban,O
naxal,O
shabhana,O
azmi,O
ka,O
minor,O
accident,O
hota,O
hai,O
.,O
Sentence #300,
@,O
bsesdelhi,O
Near,O
H.,B-LOC
No,I-LOC
.,I-LOC
322,I-LOC
-,I-LOC
324,I-LOC
Kucha,B-PER
Ghasi,I-PER
Ram,I-PER
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
110006,I-LOC
the,O
electric,O
cables,O
are,O
hanging,O
so,O
low,O
that,O
these,O
can,O
cause,O
some,O
fatal,O
accident,O
anytime,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/k7xRRkVnpS,O
Sentence #301,
Mr.,B-PER
@,O
VijayGoelBJP,O
pl,O
make,O
a,O
round,O
of,O
Sadar,B-LOC
Bazar,I-LOC
and,O
Chandni,B-LOC
Chowk,I-LOC
where,O
you,O
lived,O
and,O
contested,O
elections,O
.,O
There,O
are,O
at,O
least,O
1,O
million,O
spots,O
where,O
this,O
type,O
of,O
accident,O
can,O
happen,O
anytime,O
.,O
Stop,O
playing,O
politics,O
over,O
dead,O
bodies,O
.,O
Do,O
something,O
.,O
#,O
DelhiFireAccident,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Sentence #302,
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,O
@,O
drharshvardhan,O
@,O
nitin_gadkari,O
sir,O
with,O
due,O
respect,O
I,O
wrote,O
to,O
many,O
time,O
to,O
Arvind,O
sir,O
as,O
I,O
am,O
located,O
in,O
chawri,B-LOC
bazar,I-LOC
(,O
old,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
110006,B-MISC
),O
road,O
is,O
total,O
damaged,O
cz,O
of,O
that,O
accident,O
happened,O
here,O
so,O
pls,O
make,O
it,O
asap,O
cz,O
now,O
it,O
's,O
lockdown,O
time,O
@,O
5almanqureshi,O
Sentence #303,
Couple,O
jumps,O
on,O
#,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Metro,I-ORG
track,O
in,O
Chhatarpur,B-LOC
injured,O
http,O
:,O
//indiatoday.intoday.in/story/delhi-metro-couple-jumps-before-train-injured/1/373759.html,O
pic.twitter.com/SLkmQc8JrR,O
#,O
news,O
#,O
Delhidiaries,O
#,O
accident,O
Sentence #304,
I,O
uploaded,O
a,O
@,O
YouTube,O
video,O
http,O
:,O
//youtu.be/5CRzOs5jzdg,O
?,O
a,O
Live,O
Train,O
Accident,O
In,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Chhatarpur,B-LOC
Metro,I-LOC
station,I-LOC
-,O
Sentence #305,
met,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
&,O
backbone,O
fractured,O
in,O
#,O
Chhatarpur,B-LOC
#,O
Delhi,O
.,O
Our,O
volunteers,O
shifted,O
it,O
to,O
#,O
Sanjaygandhi,B-PER
shelter,O
for,O
treatment,O
#,O
DogRescuepic.twitter.com/k27lrfqzSc,O
Sentence #306,
@,O
OfficialSdmc,O
SIR,O
IN,O
DELHI,O
POPULATION,O
RESIDING,O
UNDER,O
electricity,O
hightention,O
wire,O
as,O
example,B-MISC
JVTS,I-MISC
GARDEN,I-MISC
C,B-LOC
BLOCK,I-LOC
CHHATARPUR,I-LOC
EXTN,I-LOC
.,I-LOC
KINDLY,O
REMOOVE,O
CONSTRUCTION,O
near,O
birla,B-LOC
farm,I-LOC
where,O
upon,O
wire,O
going,O
on,O
so,O
accident,O
not,O
be,O
happen,O
thanks,O
in,O
advance,O
Sentence #307,
@,O
kesriwal_aap,O
SIR,B-MISC
IN,O
DELHI,O
POPULATION,O
RESIDING,O
UNDER,O
electricity,O
hightention,O
wire,O
as,O
example,O
JVTS,B-LOC
GARDEN,I-LOC
C,B-LOC
BLOCK,I-LOC
CHHATARPUR,I-LOC
EXTN,I-LOC
.,I-MISC
KINDLY,O
REMOOVE,O
CONSTRUCTION,O
near,O
birla,B-LOC
farm,O
where,O
upon,O
wire,O
going,O
on,O
so,O
accident,O
not,O
be,O
happen,O
thanks,O
in,O
advance,O
Sentence #308,
@,O
msisodia,O
SIR,O
IN,O
DELHI,O
POPULATION,O
RESIDING,O
UNDER,O
electricity,O
hightention,O
wire,O
as,O
example,O
JVTS,B-LOC
GARDEN,I-LOC
C,B-LOC
BLOCK,I-LOC
CHHATARPUR,I-LOC
EXTN,I-LOC
.,O
KINDLY,O
REMOOVE,O
CONSTRUCTION,O
near,O
birla,O
farm,O
where,O
upon,O
wire,O
going,O
on,O
so,O
accident,O
not,O
be,O
happen,O
thanks,O
in,O
advance,O
Sentence #309,
@,O
kesriwal_aap,O
SIR,O
IN,O
DELHI,B-LOC
POPULATION,O
RESIDING,O
UNDER,O
electricity,O
hightention,O
wire,O
as,O
example,O
JVTS,B-LOC
GARDEN,I-LOC
C,B-LOC
BLOCK,I-LOC
CHHATARPUR,I-LOC
EXTN,I-LOC
.,O
KINDLY,O
REMOOVE,O
CONSTRUCTION,O
near,O
birla,O
farm,O
where,O
upon,O
wire,O
going,O
on,O
so,O
accident,O
not,O
be,O
happen,O
thanks,O
in,O
advance,O
Sentence #310,
@,O
SIR,O
IN,O
DELHI,B-LOC
POPULATION,O
RESIDING,O
UNDER,O
electricity,O
hightention,O
wire,O
as,O
example,O
JVTS,B-LOC
GARDEN,I-LOC
C,B-LOC
BLOCK,I-LOC
CHHATARPUR,I-LOC
EXTN,I-LOC
.,O
KINDLY,O
REMOOVE,O
CONSTRUCTION,O
near,O
birla,O
farm,O
where,O
upon,O
wire,O
going,O
on,O
so,O
accident,O
not,O
be,O
happen,O
thanks,O
in,O
advance,O
Sentence #311,
@,O
etawahpolice,O
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
I,O
am,O
resident,O
of,O
Delhi,B-LOC
.,O
I,O
met,O
with,O
an,O
accident,O
today,B-TIM
at,O
10:30,B-TIM
pm,I-TIM
near,O
chhatarpur,B-LOC
metro,I-LOC
station,I-LOC
.,O
UP75V7275,O
pic.twitter.com/1Xnq8etfyE,O
Sentence #312,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
there,O
has,O
been,O
an,O
accident,O
in,O
the,O
BRT,O
corridor,O
from,O
chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
to,O
GK,B-LOC
crossing,O
due,O
to,O
which,O
there,O
is,O
heavy,O
traffic,O
Sentence #313,
A,O
TRUCK,O
ACCIDENT,O
ON,O
RING,B-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
NEAR,O
PUNCHSHEELA,B-LOC
FLYOVER,I-LOC
CAUSING,O
CONGESTION,O
FROM,O
CHIRAG,B-LOC
DELHI,I-LOC
TOWARDS,O
DELHI,B-LOC
GATE,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/yzkW0hj3,O
Sentence #314,
A,O
TRUCK,O
ACCIDENT,O
ON,O
RING,B-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
NEAR,O
PUNCHSHEELA,B-LOC
FLYOVER,I-LOC
CAUSING,O
CONGESTION,O
FROM,O
CHIRAG,B-LOC
DELHI,I-LOC
TOWARDS,O
DELHI,B-LOC
GATE,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/15ojNkhsi,O
Sentence #315,
delhi,B-LOC
#,O
traffic,O
A,O
TRUCK,O
ACCIDENT,O
ON,O
RING,B-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
NEAR,O
PUNCHSHEELA,B-LOC
FLYOVER,I-LOC
CAUSING,O
CONGESTION,O
FROM,O
CHIRAG,B-LOC
DELHI,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/12b8zI7zI,O
Sentence #316,
@,O
itweet_chirag,O
@,O
sanjaymanjrekar,O
In,O
Delhi,B-LOC
you,O
would,O
n't,O
have,O
seen,O
the,O
bike,O
in,O
the,O
picture,O
.,O
It,O
's,O
much,O
worse,O
here,O
.,O
Many,O
accidents,O
unreported,O
.,O
Sentence #317,
Traffic,O
is,O
affected,O
near,O
IIT,B-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
while,O
coming,O
from,O
Munirka,B-LOC
to,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
between,O
dumper,O
and,O
car,O
.,O
Sentence #318,
@,O
khurafatinitin,O
serious,O
accident,O
on,O
chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
2,O
cars,O
and,O
2,O
trucks,O
.,O
Sentence #319,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
TrafflineDEL,O
accident,O
on,O
chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
expect,O
delays,O
Sentence #320,
Daughters,O
out,O
to,O
retain,O
Munde,B-LOC
fort,I-LOC
:,O
Five,B-TIM
months,O
after,O
his,O
death,O
in,O
an,O
accident,O
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
BJP,B-ORG
leader,O
Gopinath,B-LOC
M,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//bit.ly/1vdqZ92,O
Sentence #321,
@,O
TrafflineDELOne,O
carriageway,O
on,O
BRT,O
from,O
G.K,B-LOC
1,I-LOC
to,O
Chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
totally,O
blocked,O
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
by,O
2,O
trucks,O
.,O
Brace,O
for,O
massive,O
traffic,O
jams,O
Sentence #322,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
One,O
carriageway,O
on,O
BRT,O
from,O
G.K,B-LOC
1,I-LOC
to,O
Chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
totally,O
blocked,O
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
by,O
2,O
trucks.Brace,O
for,O
massive,O
traffic,O
jams,O
Sentence #323,
One,O
carriageway,O
on,O
BRT,O
from,O
G.K,B-LOC
1,I-LOC
to,O
Chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
totally,O
blocked,O
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
by,O
2,O
trucks,O
.,O
Brace,O
for,O
massive,O
traffic,O
jams,O
Sentence #324,
BRT,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
..,O
Just,O
Witnessed,O
another,O
Accident,O
..,O
The,O
Person,O
lost,O
his,O
Leg,O
!,O
!,O
Sentence #325,
15,O
Minutes,O
Ago,O
I,O
was,O
heading,O
for,O
Lecture,O
but,O
now,O
to,O
Hospital,O
after,O
Accident,O
at,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
Sentence #326,
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
sheikh,B-LOC
Sarai,I-LOC
crossing,O
Big,O
rocks,O
are,O
lying,O
in,O
the,O
middle,O
of,O
the,O
road,O
since,O
months,O
causing,O
accidents,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/6yZIhFy9yg,O
Sentence #327,
Traffic,O
is,O
heavy,O
in,O
the,O
carriageway,O
from,O
Nehru,B-LOC
Place,I-LOC
to,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
due,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
near,O
C.R.,B-LOC
Park,I-LOC
Red,I-LOC
Light,I-LOC
.,O
Kindly,O
avoid,O
the,O
stretch,O
.,O
Sentence #328,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
DelhiTrafficPol,O
Jai,B-MISC
Hind,I-MISC
!,O
DANGEROUS,B-MISC
IRON,I-MISC
PLATES,I-MISC
in,O
middle,O
of,O
Road,O
is,O
causing,O
accidents,O
at,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
crossing,O
.,O
Pls,O
take,O
NA,O
.,O
Sentence #329,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
car,O
accident,O
near,O
chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
on,O
outer,O
ring,B-LOC
road,I-LOC
...,O
Pl,O
do,O
needful,O
Sentence #330,
@,O
Saurabh_MLAgk,O
Horrific,O
accident,O
at,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
starting,O
point,O
PWD,O
department,O
shld,O
get,O
Gas,B-ORG
Agency,I-ORG
Subway,B-LOC
removed,O
&,O
alignment,O
done,O
Sentence #331,
Part1/2,O
..,O
Traffic,O
Alert,O
Obstruction,O
in,O
traffic,O
on,O
Outer,B-LOC
Ring,I-LOC
Road,I-LOC
in,O
the,O
carriageway,O
from,O
IIT,B-LOC
towards,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
due,O
to,O
accident,O
of,O
an,O
Sentence #332,
.,O
@,O
msisodia,O
pls,O
do,O
something,O
about,O
an,O
open,O
manhole,O
at,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
Flyover,I-LOC
chauraha,O
.,O
Vehicles,O
get,O
stuck,O
daily,O
causing,O
accidents,O
#,O
PotHolespic.twitter.com/pPow5jrdYH,O
Sentence #333,
Pipeline,O
leakage,O
made,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
accident,O
prone,O
area,O
.,O
@,O
Saurabh_MLAgk,O
@,O
KapilMishraAAP,O
@,O
sandhyatimes4u,O
@,O
NBTDillipic.twitter.com/infA2h778U,O
Sentence #334,
@,O
SatyendarJain,O
Sir,O
pls,O
either,O
remove,O
BRT,O
ASAP,O
or,O
fix,O
it,O
(,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
),O
.,O
Everyday,O
there,O
are,O
accidents,O
as,O
the,O
road,O
dividers,O
are,O
broken,O
Sentence #335,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
large,O
construction,O
stone,O
caused,O
puncture,O
at,O
chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
leading,O
to,O
panschsheel,B-LOC
.,O
Nearly,O
caused,O
bad,O
accident,O
.,O
Sentence #336,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
crossing,O
lights,O
not,O
working,O
from,O
more,O
than,O
an,O
hour,O
..,O
can,O
cause,O
major,O
accident,O
Sentence #337,
You,O
must,O
look,O
after,O
delhi,B-LOC
and,O
specifically,O
your,O
constituency,O
.,O
Encroachment,O
on,O
pwd,O
roads,O
around,O
savitri,B-LOC
nagar,I-LOC
is,O
happening,O
causing,O
severe,O
jams,O
.,O
Chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
where,O
you,O
live,O
is,O
no,O
exception,O
.,O
Pwd,O
roads,O
must,O
be,O
immediately,O
widened,O
and,O
authoriswd,O
parking,O
started,O
.,O
Daily,O
accidents,O
are,O
on,O
Sentence #338,
@,O
DCPSouthDelhi,O
Sir,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
fly,O
over,O
is,O
creating,O
traffic,O
jam,O
.,O
Request,O
please,O
help,O
.,O
Thanks,O
Sentence #339,
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
Sir,O
an,O
accident,O
on,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
fly,O
over,O
is,O
creating,O
traffic,O
jam,O
.,O
Pls,O
help,O
thanks,O
Sentence #340,
Hello,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
please,O
note,O
due,O
to,O
no,O
restrictions,O
ppl,O
r,O
driving,O
their,O
vehicles,O
on,O
high,O
speed,O
they,O
are,O
driving,O
dangerously,O
.,O
Especially,O
Lal,B-LOC
Bahadur,I-LOC
Shashtri,I-LOC
Road,I-LOC
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
to,O
Kalkaji,B-LOC
road,I-LOC
.,O
Sentence #341,
Car,O
and,O
SUV,O
cars,O
are,O
unstoppable,O
and,O
leading,O
accidents,O
Sentence #342,
Req,O
u,O
pls,O
do,O
the,O
needful,O
Sentence #343,
Did,O
any,O
one,O
see,O
the,O
photograph,O
of,O
Rajesh,B-PER
Pilot,I-PER
car,O
accident,O
in,O
delhi-jaipur,B-LOC
road,I-LOC
.,O
All,O
the,O
sons,O
of,O
above,O
noble,O
souls,O
of,O
senior,O
congress,B-ORG
leaders,O
who,O
were,O
close,O
friends,O
of,O
RG,O
have,O
now,O
been,O
rewarded,O
with,O
ministerial,O
post,O
to,O
wash,O
the,O
sins,O
of,O
catholic,O
lady,O
as,O
ordered,O
by,O
confession,O
box,O
Sentence #344,
@,O
DCPSouthDelhi,O
My,O
request,O
please,O
close,O
U,B-ORG
turn,O
opposite,O
DDA,B-LOC
park,I-LOC
PANCHSHEEL,I-LOC
as,O
it,O
is,O
too,O
much,O
of,O
inconvenience,O
for,O
traffic,O
coming,O
from,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
going,O
towards,O
Moolchand,B-LOC
because,O
people,O
take,O
left,O
turn,O
towards,O
SRI,B-LOC
FORT,I-LOC
road,I-LOC
it,O
might,O
result,O
in,O
serious,O
accident,O
if,O
it,O
is,O
not,O
closed,O
Sentence #345,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
heavy,O
jam,O
on,O
chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
crossing,O
coming,O
from,O
Sangam,B-LOC
vihar,I-LOC
http,O
:,O
//side.is,O
it,O
an,O
accident,O
or,O
vip,O
movement,O
.,O
Stuck,O
here,O
in,O
1,O
km,O
stretch,O
for,O
more,O
then,O
an,O
hour,O
Sentence #346,
Wrong,O
side,O
driving,O
.,O
Near,B-PER
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
metro,I-LOC
station,I-LOC
gate-1,O
.,O
Date,O
:,O
20th,B-TIM
Dec'19,I-TIM
.,O
Time,O
:,O
around,O
9:20am,O
.,O
Guy,O
in,O
white,O
scooty,O
almost,O
caused,O
an,O
accident,O
.,O
@,O
dtptrafficpic.twitter.com/hVYJvTMSF9,O
Sentence #347,
I,O
met,O
with,O
2,O
fatal,O
accidents,O
.,O
1,O
on,O
highway,O
near,O
Sirhind,B-LOC
(,O
PB,O
),O
n,O
2nd,O
at,O
chirag,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
lights,O
15,B-TIM
years,O
back,O
.,O
Had,O
I,O
not,O
been,O
wearing,O
Helmet,O
somebody,O
else,O
would,O
be,O
telling,O
this,O
.,O
Sentence #348,
#,O
thread,O
#,O
delhipolice,O
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
@,O
CPDelhi,O
My,O
friend,O
and,O
I,O
were,O
going,O
towards,O
Aurobindo,B-LOC
Market,I-LOC
from,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
when,O
our,O
car,O
was,O
hit,O
by,O
a,O
truck,O
that,O
skipped,O
the,O
signal,O
under,O
Malviya,B-LOC
Nagar,I-LOC
Flyover,I-LOC
around,O
9:30,O
pm,O
.,O
Fortunately,O
none,O
of,O
us,O
was,O
hurt,O
in,O
this,O
accident,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/s4IEIa5zMQ,O
Sentence #349,
There,O
is,O
a,O
dangerous,O
road,O
object,O
a,O
green,O
tarpaulin,O
over,O
a,O
striped,O
barricade,O
and,O
there,O
are,O
no,O
streetlights,O
.,O
I,O
almost,O
got,O
hit,O
.,O
This,O
is,O
on,O
the,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
road,I-LOC
.,O
Please,O
remove,O
it,O
so,O
that,O
there,O
are,O
no,O
accidents,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
@,O
CPDelhi,O
Sentence #350,
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,O
@,O
LtGovDelhi,O
@,O
pwddelhi,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
What,O
happened,O
to,O
promise,O
to,O
construct,O
FOB,O
at,O
Chirag,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
&,O
Sheikh,B-LOC
Sarai,I-LOC
2,I-LOC
junctions,O
on,O
BRT,B-LOC
road,I-LOC
pl,O
act,O
fast,O
people,O
r,O
getting,O
killed/injured,O
in,O
accidents,O
.,O
Traffic,O
police,O
most,O
unhelpful,O
Sentence #351,
@,O
DelhiAirport,O
Is,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Airport,I-LOC
aware,O
of,O
an,O
accident,O
that,O
took,O
place,O
recently,O
near,O
AEROCITY,B-LOC
?,O
Sentence #352,
@,O
moefcc,O
@,O
wti_org_india,O
There,O
was,O
an,O
open,O
area,O
in,O
front,O
of,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Aerocity,I-LOC
metro,I-LOC
station,I-LOC
with,O
lots,O
plants,O
and,O
trees,O
.,O
It,O
was,O
home,O
of,O
peacocks,O
and,O
Neel,O
gai,O
.,O
Now,O
Aerocity,O
is,O
clearing,O
it,O
for,O
their,O
use,O
.,O
The,O
animals,O
may,O
die,O
because,O
of,O
road,B-LOC
accidents,O
or,O
lack,O
of,O
food,O
.,O
Please,O
relocate,O
them,O
pic.twitter.com/MlybagkcGx,O
Sentence #353,
Im,O
happy,O
to,O
have,O
inaugurated,O
the,O
'21st,O
Annual,O
Conference,O
of,O
Indian,B-LOC
Society,B-LOC
of,I-LOC
Neuroradiology,I-LOC
',O
today,B-TIM
at,O
Aerocity,B-LOC
New,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
.,O
Neuroradiology,O
helps,O
us,O
in,O
a,O
wide,O
spectrum,O
of,O
situations,O
from,O
triaging,O
road,O
accident,O
patients,O
to,O
diagnosing,O
brain,O
tumours,O
.,O
@,O
PMOIndia,O
@,O
MoHFW_INDIA,O
@,O
WHOSEAROpic.twitter.com/AbkdE8wyLr,O
Sentence #354,
#,O
BREAKING,O
|,O
Speeding,O
Audi,B-ORG
runs,O
over,O
soldier,O
Naik,B-PER
Ram,I-PER
Swaroop,I-PER
Rajput,I-PER
in,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Cantonment,I-LOC
.,O
Soldier,O
was,O
crossing,O
road,O
at,O
the,O
time,O
of,O
accident,O
Sentence #355,
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
met,O
with,O
accident,O
near,O
delhi,B-LOC
cantonment,I-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
.,O
The,O
driver,O
of,O
ecosport,O
said,O
do,O
whatever,O
you,O
want,O
i,O
will,O
not,O
pay,O
for,O
damage,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/SM8CVTPT4W,O
Sentence #356,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
LtGovDelhi,O
sir,B-LOC
faulty,O
traffic,O
signals,O
are,O
adding,O
more,O
congestion,O
chaos,O
&,O
accident,O
prone,O
area,O
at,O
the,O
traffic,O
signal,O
of,O
thimayya,O
park,O
crossing,O
in,O
delhi,B-LOC
cantonment,I-LOC
area,I-LOC
.,O
Green,O
signal,O
turns,O
into,O
red,O
in,O
2,B-TIM
seconds,O
who,O
came,O
from,O
base,O
hospital,O
going,O
towards,O
Kirby,B-LOC
place,I-LOC
.,O
Sentence #357,
People,O
says,O
various,O
stories,O
about,O
the,O
ghost,O
lady,O
of,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Cantonment,I-LOC
.,O
It,O
is,O
said,O
that,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Cantt,I-LOC
is,O
a,O
shelter,O
of,O
a,O
lady,O
ghost,O
who,O
supposedly,O
killed,O
in,O
a,O
car,O
accident,O
.,O
Many,O
people,O
who,O
have,O
visited,O
the,O
area,O
have,O
experienced,O
her,O
existence,O
over,O
.,O
#,O
Hauntedplaceindelhi,B-PER
#,O
Delhicanntpic.twitter.com/zLb8LhJDrs,O
Sentence #358,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
Please,O
save,O
human,O
life,O
need,O
road,O
bumps,O
at,O
this,O
chowk,O
to,O
control,O
the,O
traffic,O
at,O
Delhi,B-LOC
cantonment,I-LOC
Base,I-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
cantonment,I-LOC
road,I-LOC
red,O
light,O
chowk,O
this,O
chowk,O
very,O
dangerous,O
today,B-TIM
again,O
major,B-LOC
accident,O
on,O
this,O
chowk,O
.,O
https,O
:,O
//twitter.com/mohitkannu/status/1139327490323709952,O
Sentence #359,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
Please,O
save,O
human,O
life,O
need,O
road,O
bumps,O
at,O
this,O
chowk,O
to,O
control,O
the,O
traffic,O
at,O
Delhi,B-LOC
cantonment,I-LOC
Base,I-LOC
hospital,I-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
cantonment,I-LOC
road,I-LOC
red,O
light,O
chowk,O
this,O
chowk,O
very,O
dangerous,O
today,B-TIM
again,O
major,B-LOC
accident,O
on,O
this,O
chowk,O
.,O
Sentence #360,
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,O
Thimayya,B-LOC
Marg,I-LOC
.,O
T1,B-LOC
terminal,I-LOC
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Cantonment,I-LOC
road,I-LOC
condition,O
by,O
@,O
AamAadmiParty,O
Well,O
done,O
guys,O
for,O
such,O
a,O
pathetic,O
road,O
.,O
@,O
CPCB_OFFICIAL,B-ORG
Reason,I-ORG
for,O
daily,O
jam,O
and,O
accidents,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/sMfKx80CpZ,O
Sentence #361,
A,O
brave,O
#,O
cop,O
saves,O
the,O
life,O
of,O
an,O
unconscious,O
man,O
lying,O
in,O
a,O
fired,O
vehicle,O
after,O
an,O
accident,O
near,O
#,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
.,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Dilwalon,O
Ki,I-ORG
!,O
!,O
Sentence #362,
A,O
TRUCK,O
ACCIDENT,O
ON,O
RING,B-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
NEAR,O
PUNCHSHEELA,B-LOC
FLYOVER,I-LOC
CAUSING,O
CONGESTION,O
FROM,O
CHIRAG,B-LOC
DELHI,I-LOC
TOWARDS,O
DELHI,B-LOC
GATE,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/yzkW0hj3,O
Sentence #363,
A,O
TRUCK,O
ACCIDENT,O
ON,O
RING,B-LOC
ROAD,I-LOC
NEAR,O
PUNCHSHEELA,B-LOC
FLYOVER,I-LOC
CAUSING,O
CONGESTION,O
FROM,O
CHIRAG,B-LOC
DELHI,I-LOC
TOWARDS,O
DELHI,B-LOC
GATE,I-LOC
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/yzkW0hj3,O
Sentence #364,
@,O
anujkg25,O
What,O
Sonia,O
was,O
doing,O
with,O
Madhavrao,B-PER
when,O
Car,O
accident,O
happned,O
in,O
dec,O
.,O
82,O
near,O
by,O
IIT,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
at,O
2AM,B-TIM
midnight,I-TIM
.,O
Sentence #365,
@,O
Mrityunjoykjha,O
Amitabh-Rati,O
Film,O
Coolie,B-MISC
Na,I-MISC
tu,O
ne,O
signal,O
dekha,O
na,O
maine,O
signal,O
dekha,O
accident,O
ho,O
gaya,O
(,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
par,O
),O
Sentence #366,
@,O
gsurya,O
@,O
bindibrigade,O
@,O
Swamy39,O
@,O
indiantweeter,O
Ohh,O
IITD,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
rat,O
ke,O
1:30,O
par,O
accident,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
Sidhiya,O
yad,O
aaya,O
beta,O
?,O
Sentence #367,
@,O
giniromet,O
night,O
at,O
2,O
AM1982,O
Madhav,I-PER
Scindia,I-PER
and,O
Sonia,B-PER
Gandhi,I-PER
were,O
caught,O
alone,O
together,O
when,O
their,O
car,O
met,O
an,O
accident,O
near,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
Sentence #368,
#,O
MediaFreedom,O
never,O
discussed,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
Car,I-LOC
accident,O
who,O
was,O
in,O
the,O
car,O
...,O
Sentence #369,
``,O
@,O
MrsGandhi,O
@,O
priyankac19,O
or,O
for,O
that,O
matter,O
that,O
of,O
Nehru,B-LOC
?,O
or,O
that,O
car,O
accident,O
involving,O
Scindia,B-LOC
and,O
a,O
certain,O
``,O
'',O
lady,O
'',O
'',O
near,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
?,O
'',O
Sentence #370,
jara,O
batao,O
IIT,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
pe,O
kiska,O
accident,O
hua,O
tha,O
?,O
Sentence #371,
@,O
Kaalateetham,B-LOC
@,O
kailashkaushik8,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
No.-1,I-LOC
accident,O
at,O
2,B-TIM
AM,I-TIM
.,O
Sentence #372,
Avoid,O
CP,B-LOC
to,O
Delhi,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
route,O
.,O
Blocked,O
.,O
Radio,B-ORG
tells,O
me,O
bike,O
rider,O
killed,O
following,O
minor,O
spat,O
related,O
to,O
car,O
accident,O
@,O
TrafflineDEL,O
Sentence #373,
@,O
ShrrinG,O
@,O
sushmitadevmp,O
@,O
SouleFacts,O
@,O
BagariaR,O
@,O
vanandca,O
on,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
on,O
that,O
night,O
sucking,O
something,O
leading,O
to,O
accident,O
.,O
Sentence #374,
Please,O
search,O
Nehru,B-PER
were,O
was,O
he,O
born,O
Search,O
Mohammed,I-PER
Younis,I-PER
Sharhayar,B-LOC
Khan,I-LOC
Search,O
whose,O
accident,O
took,O
place,O
near,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
Sentence #375,
1982,O
:,O
SG,B-LOC
&,O
M,B-PER
Scindia,I-PER
were,O
in,O
an,O
accident,O
near,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
while,O
driving,O
a,O
car,O
at,O
2,B-TIM
AM,I-TIM
.,O
Sonia,O
was,O
the,O
only,O
other,O
passenger,O
.,O
@,O
ggiittiikkaa,O
Sentence #376,
Accident,O
at,O
Delhi,B-ORG
Gate-,I-ORG
photo,O
taken,O
by,O
UT,O
reporter,O
Sohail,B-PER
Khan,I-PER
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/7AMvimU3S,O
Sentence #377,
@,O
nitin_gadkari,O
many,O
cuts,O
on,O
NH24,O
between,O
ABSE,B-ORG
Engg,O
college,O
crossing,O
and,O
delhi,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
no,O
police,O
action,O
departmental,O
action,O
causes,O
accidents,O
jam,O
Sentence #378,
Another,O
major,O
fatal,O
accident,O
at,O
the,O
capital,O
:,O
Ambulance,O
carrying,O
a,O
patient,O
hit,O
by,O
a,O
speeding,O
car,O
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
patient,O
killed,O
@,O
TOIDelhi,O
Sentence #379,
:,O
This,O
is,O
a,O
good,O
idea,O
.,O
ROAD,O
ACCIDENT,O
DATA,O
be,O
shown,O
ON,O
A,O
GIANT,O
SCREEN,O
ON,O
LINE,O
IN,O
AIIMS,B-LOC
X-ING,O
CON,O
.,O
PL.,O
DELHI,B-LOC
GATE,I-LOC
DHOLA,B-LOC
KUAN,I-LOC
ITO,B-LOC
ISBT,O
Sentence #380,
Retweeted,O
#,O
GauravPradhan,O
(,O
@,O
DrGPradhan,O
),O
:,O
Sentence #381,
What,O
is,O
truth,O
of,O
Sonia,B-LOC
Gandhi,I-LOC
in,O
1982,O
car,O
accident,O
at,O
IIT,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
@,O
...,O
http,O
:,O
//fb.me/2JiKX2yAX,O
Sentence #382,
@,O
DCPSWestDelhi,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
@,O
DelhiPolice,O
@,O
CPDelhi,O
@,O
ravishndtv,O
@,O
ndtvindia,O
najafagrh,O
road,O
(,O
delhi,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
najafgarh,B-LOC
near,O
najafgarh,B-LOC
metro,I-LOC
station,I-LOC
),O
has,O
declare,O
one,O
side,O
but,O
battery,O
ricksaw,O
and,O
traffic,O
move,O
in,O
wrong,O
directon,O
resul,O
in,O
massive,O
jam,O
&,O
accident,O
.,O
request,O
u,O
to,O
intervene,O
urgently,O
pic.twitter.com/IDeEmfmcZ9,O
Sentence #383,
@,O
DCPSWestDelhi,O
@,O
dtptraffic,O
This,O
santro,O
car,O
is,O
parked,O
on,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
bus,O
stand,O
for,O
last,O
one,B-TIM
week,O
at,O
Gaishala,B-ORG
Road,O
.,O
Passengers,I-ORG
are,O
suffering,O
from,O
typical,O
problem.Bus,O
is,O
also,O
stopping,O
in,O
middle,O
of,O
running,O
road,O
.Any,O
type,O
of,O
injury,O
or,O
accident,O
can,O
cause,O
here,O
please,O
remove,O
it,O
from,O
here,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/zG00bYu9V7,O
Sentence #384,
BJP,O
should,O
demand,O
inquiry,O
into,O
the,O
alleged,O
accident,O
near,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
while,O
M,B-PER
Sindhia,I-PER
was,O
driving,O
with,O
an,O
Italian,B-GPE
lady,O
..,O
Sentence #385,
@,O
dm_ghaziabad,O
Mam,O
delhi,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
flyover,I-LOC
par,O
Ghanta,O
ghar,O
utarte,O
samay,O
Wahan,B-PER
Yellow,I-PER
Flasher,I-PER
light,O
Honi,B-LOC
chahiye,O
Fog,O
me,O
bhaut,O
Truck,O
accidents,O
hote,O
hai,O
wahan,O
Pls,B-PER
Mam,I-PER
Sentence #386,
@,O
CP_SuratCity,O
Traffic,O
brigade,O
being,O
busy,O
on,O
phone,O
at,O
delhi,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
junction,O
instead,O
of,O
managing,O
traffic,O
.,O
And,O
an,O
auto,O
is,O
going,O
on,O
wrong,O
side,O
from,O
the,O
back,O
of,O
TB,O
but,O
who,O
cares,O
.,O
Such,O
small,O
mistakes,O
causes,O
huge,O
accidents,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/Qya9T60wBI,O
Sentence #387,
Here,O
all,O
the,O
citizen,O
fall,O
there,O
garbage,O
near,O
delhi,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
chowk,I-LOC
&,O
here,O
it,O
is,O
prohibited,O
to,O
fall,O
the,O
garbage,O
.,O
After,O
this,O
animals,O
like,O
cows,O
dogs,O
etc,O
eat,O
these,O
things,O
and,O
many,O
accidents,O
occur,O
here,O
due,O
to,O
this,O
garbage,O
and,O
many,O
type,O
of,O
diseases,O
occurs,O
which,O
create,O
many,O
health,O
problems,O
.,O
Sentence #388,
@,O
dtptraffic,O
this,O
is,O
at,O
the,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
signal,O
near,O
Shaheedi,B-LOC
Park,I-LOC
.,O
Please,O
ask,O
the,O
concerned,O
TI,O
to,O
have,O
a,O
look,O
.,O
The,O
other,O
signal,O
at,O
the,O
crossing,O
is,O
switched,O
off,O
.,O
Will,O
lead,O
to,O
an,O
accident,O
if,O
left,O
like,O
this,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/P8Birljygl,O
Sentence #389,
Kya,O
pata,O
Priyanka,O
ka,O
DNA,B-MISC
Jyoti,O
se,O
match,O
ho,O
jaye,O
...,O
after,O
all,O
there,O
was,O
an,O
accident,O
near,O
iit,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
...,O
ambassador,O
car,O
...,O
occupants,O
were,O
Madhav,O
n,O
Antonio,B-PER
Maino,I-PER
...,O
fun,O
time,O
spent,O
together,O
Sentence #390,
There,O
r,O
many,O
no,O
of,O
large,O
potholes,O
which,O
should,O
be,O
immediately,O
fill,O
to,O
avoid,O
any,O
accident,O
...,O
1,O
large,O
no,O
of,O
pothole,O
in,O
front,O
of,O
PNB,O
najafarh,B-LOC
2,I-LOC
pot,O
hole,O
in,O
front,O
of,O
gaushala,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
njf,O
3,O
no,O
of,O
pothole,O
at,O
T,B-ORG
intersection,O
near,O
Dhasa,O
stand,O
@,O
CPCB_OFFICIAL,O
@,O
DelhiPwd,O
@,O
kgahlot,O
Sentence #391,
Motorbike,O
riders,O
&,O
the,O
pillion,O
was,O
E-challaned,O
by,O
Delhi,B-LOC
traffic,O
police,O
at,O
the,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
due,O
to,O
not,O
wearing,O
a,O
helmet,O
.,O
People,O
on,O
empty,O
roads,O
are,O
taking,O
a,O
chance,O
during,O
the,O
lockdown,O
as,O
there,O
are,O
lean,O
traffic,O
but,O
this,O
can,O
lead,O
to,O
a,O
major,O
accident,O
.,O
pic.twitter.com/zVIs2MXjzZ,O
Sentence #392,
He,O
was,O
in,O
a,O
wrong,O
party,O
@,O
INCIndia,O
.,O
Sentence #393,
He,O
knew,O
lots,O
of,O
inner,O
secrets,O
of,O
Sonia,O
.,O
Remember,O
the,O
late,O
night,O
car,O
accident,O
near,O
IIT,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
in,O
1980s,B-TIM
carrying,O
Sonia,O
&,O
him,O
.,O
Sentence #394,
His,O
death,O
was,O
definitely,O
a,O
conspiracy,O
.,O
Sentence #395,
Servant,O
is,O
a,O
lie,O
.,O
But,O
there,O
was,O
an,O
accident,O
in,O
front,O
of,O
iit,B-LOC
delhi,I-LOC
gate,I-LOC
where,O
these,O
two,O
were,O
said,O
to,O
be,O
involved,O
.,O
Sentence #396,
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
Accident,O
:,O
:,O
3,O
http,O
:,O
//nbt.in/pCSr7Y,O
?,O
bga,O
Sentence #397,
Delhi,B-PER
Gate,I-PER
Accident,O
:,O
:,O
3,O
https,O
:,O
//navbharattimes.indiatimes.com/metro/delhi/other-news/three-teenagers-who-died-near-delhi-gate-kin-face-prosecution-new-mv-act/articleshow/72327466.cms,O
?,O
utm_source=twitter,O
&,O
utm_campaign=nbtmobile,O
&,O
utm_medium=referral,O
Sentence #398,
@,O
rohitaapsharma,O
In,O
last,O
2,B-TIM
months,O
we,O
seen,O
3,O
accidents,O
at,O
night,O
due,O
to,O
a,O
divider,O
without,O
reflectors,O
.,O
Location,O
:,O
Havelli,O
/,O
power,O
house,O
Najafghar,B-LOC
.,O
Complete,O
road,B-LOC
is,O
without,O
reflectors,O
on,O
divider,O
from,O
sai,O
baba,O
till,O
Delhi,B-LOC
gate,I-LOC
..,O
Hope,O
someone,O
help,O
@,O
msisodia,O
@,O
kgahlot,O
@,O
ArvindKejriwal,O
Sentence #399,
Three,O
Minors,O
Riding,O
Without,O
Helmets,O
Killed,O
in,O
Road,O
Accident,I-ORG
Near,I-ORG
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
https,O
:,O
//www.news18.com/news/india/three-minors-riding-without-helmets-killed-in-road-accident-near-delhi-gate-2407087.html,O
Sentence #400,
#,O
3Novices,O
:,O
Three,O
two-wheeler-borne,O
boys,O
die,O
in,O
road,O
mishap,O
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
parents,O
allege,O
hit-and-run,O
Three,O
two-wheeler-borne,O
minor,O
boys,O
between,O
the,O
ages,O
15-17,O
died,O
in,O
a,O
road,O
accident,O
on,O
late,O
Saturday,B-TIM
night,I-TIM
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
in,O
Dariyaganj,B-ORG
police,I-ORG
station,I-ORG
area,I-LOC
.,O
#,O
news,O
For,B-ORG
Infor,I-ORG
Sentence #401,
Careless,O
driving,O
of,O
children,O
near,O
Delhi,B-LOC
Gate,I-LOC
red,O
light,O
@,O
ZeeNewsHindi,B-LOC
Delhi,I-LOC
police,O
is,O
helpless,O
or,O
careless,O
responsible,O
for,O
this,O
accident,O
allow,O
children,O
to,O
drive,O
dangerously,O
I,O
am,O
crossing,O
that,O
redlight,O
regularly,O
Sentence #402,
@,O
